<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 20:40:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: It's OKAY to end relationships / friendships over POLITICS]]></title><description><![CDATA[Contrary to popular opinion, politics is more than just a difference in what to
do with taxes. It's also NOT some innocuous, neutral attribute akin to
ethnicity, gender, or sexual orientation. Your political affiliation is a
reflection of your core values, and your core values IS the content of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocyx3j/cmv_its_okay_to_end_relationships_friendships/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocyx3j/cmv_its_okay_to_end_relationships_friendships/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 19:32:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular opinion, politics is more than just a difference in what to do with taxes. It&amp;#39;s also NOT some innocuous, neutral attribute akin to ethnicity, gender, or sexual orientation. Your political affiliation is a reflection of your core values, and your core values IS the content of your character; and isn&amp;#39;t the content of your character the only reasonable thing that is up for judgement? Not only that, who you decide to vote for has REAL implications on the rest of us, should that person be elected into power. In the course of your political expression, people are allowed to reassess their friendship / relationship with you when they realize your core values are not compatible with theirs. In fact, it&amp;#39;s GOOD that people are choosing to end friendships / relationships rather than stew in a passive-aggressive, resentful dynamic with people whom they no longer like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Instagram has lost its edge and will die out eventually]]></title><description><![CDATA[Instagram is on the decline, and will continue to do so for the next few years
until they finally die out. Here are my reasons for believing that.

One - Instagram is losing its niche

Instagram had a successful niche as a photo-sharing platform, and that is still
ultimately what most creators and…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocvz3l/cmv_instagram_has_lost_its_edge_and_will_die_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocvz3l/cmv_instagram_has_lost_its_edge_and_will_die_out/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 12:56:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram is on the decline, and will continue to do so for the next few years until they finally die out. Here are my reasons for believing that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One - Instagram is losing its niche&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram had a successful niche as a photo-sharing platform, and that is still ultimately what most creators and users use it for. Users use it because they want to see photos and engage with them. However, Instagram is now moving to attempt to compete with YouTube and TikTok, which will ultimately fail because those platforms are already occupying their respective niches, and doing a good job at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two - Instagram isn&amp;#39;t showing people what they want to see&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe that most casual users of Instagram are like myself - we follow pages that we want to use, which usually includes our friends and pages of interest that we are interested in. Instagram&amp;#39;s attempt to push people to look at pages that they don&amp;#39;t even follow at the expense of pages that they do is driving users away and lowering users&amp;#39; interest in the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these reasons, I think that Instagram will eventually die out, and pretty soon at that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: We should tax the "externalization" of a cost, and the tax should be high enough to make it NOT worth it in the first place.]]></title><description><![CDATA[For example, it's cheaper to transport chicken from the USA to China, where it
will be processed (it's cheaper due to lower wages and other reasons) and
shipped back to the USA. This is a monstrous practice, that creates a lot more
pollution due to trans-oceanic transportation and takes capital out…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocw144/cmv_we_should_tax_the_externalization_of_a_cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocw144/cmv_we_should_tax_the_externalization_of_a_cost/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 12:56:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, it&amp;#39;s cheaper to transport chicken from the USA to China, where it will be processed (it&amp;#39;s cheaper due to lower wages and other reasons) and shipped back to the USA. This is a monstrous practice, that creates a lot more pollution due to trans-oceanic transportation and takes capital out of a nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end product is cheaper to manufacture so the corporation can increase its profits, and the costs are externalized: someone else will have to clean the oceans in the future, and someone else misses out on a job that&amp;#39;s outsourced to another nation. Net gain for the corporation, net loss for everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need taxes in place so that this practice is a net loss for the corporation. It&amp;#39;s ruining the country and the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Undercover Police and "Infiltrators and Entrapment" sound very Unconstitutional because they amount to a search without Warrant or probable cause.]]></title><description><![CDATA[If police set out a truck of shoes with the intent of it being stolen, logically
that means they were giving things away to the public because it was purchased
with taxpayer dollars.

Also undercover cops, vans, cruisers being used for routine traffic enforcement
seem blatantly unconstitutional…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocsila/cmv_undercover_police_and_infiltrators_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocsila/cmv_undercover_police_and_infiltrators_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 08:41:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If police set out a truck of shoes with the intent of it being stolen, logically that means they were giving things away to the public because it was purchased with taxpayer dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also undercover cops, vans, cruisers being used for routine traffic enforcement seem blatantly unconstitutional because they amount to a search of the public without warrant or probable cause. Crime can happen anywhere, behind closed doors or on the streets and nothing is preventing police from enforcing traffic laws in plainly marked vehicles. Using unmarked vehicles is the same thing as policing an area without a warrant to search &amp;#39;looking for probable cause&amp;#39;. The warrant is already there, police have some function to protect the public, but hiding that warrant, which is the police presence, goes beyond legal limits placed on government by the bill of rights. Police in an area already amounts to a search, you cant hide the fact you are there and still call yourself law enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same goes for undercover police infiltrating freely associated groups, as they have no probable cause and the state cannot sanction the search of a group of people. People also cannot &amp;#39;surrender&amp;#39; that right or any other right, depending on which platform is used. I believe that act is also unconstitutional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Equal pay pertaining to women's football (soccer) is not realistic.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Don't take this out of context. Equal pay in other stuff is reasonable like
doing the same office job. But in the context of sports, I dont see equal pay in
women's football being realistic in the current women's market.

From my general knowledge of sports. Salary for players are usually…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc567x/cmv_equal_pay_pertaining_to_womens_football/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc567x/cmv_equal_pay_pertaining_to_womens_football/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 01:41:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t take this out of context. Equal pay in other stuff is reasonable like doing the same office job. But in the context of sports, I dont see equal pay in women&amp;#39;s football being realistic in the current women&amp;#39;s market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my general knowledge of sports. Salary for players are usually determined by the total revenue of the league divided between the player&amp;#39;s salary, the owners, and the league&amp;#39;s administration. As an example, the NFL distributes is revenue by giving 49% to the profits for player&amp;#39;s salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I believe the real reason women don&amp;#39;t get equally paid in football is mainly due to the lack of revenue in women&amp;#39;s soccer. The best women&amp;#39;s soccer player wants to be paid the same as Messi or ronaldo. But the question is do they generate as much money as those two soccer giants? I believe the lack of revenue generated in women&amp;#39;s football leagues will limit their salaries. They need more demand where people want to pay just as much as mens league to watch and of course have the same amount of people willing to pay the same price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the whole movement seems weak because by paying the same wage as men they are bankrupting their own league. Where is the money coming from? Because they don&amp;#39;t generate enough revenue for equal pay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an example, women&amp;#39;s tennis generates high revenue. There is a reason they are the highest paid female athletes. They bring in fans and money. Not quite equal to the male tennis wage, but the gap is much smaller compared to other sports. Hence, revenue generated = higher salaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this entire movement was based on unfair percentage split then I am supporting them. But the issue is the absolute revenue is just so low compared to men. Sports is essentially entertainment. You get paid by the demand of people wanting to spend to watch you. Women&amp;#39;s football league just doesn&amp;#39;t have the demand comparable to the men&amp;#39;s league. They should focus on increasing that demand and revenue rather than asking for something that is not even available. Cause there is not enough money available to pay all the women football players the same as men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Field sobriety tests should not be up to the opinion of just an officer]]></title><description><![CDATA[I understand that someone can be intoxicated on something other than alcohol, so
I know why they're in place. However I do not like that an officer with no
training gets to decide to actually charge you with the crime, I believe at most
a driver should be taken to the drunk tank and then released…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocacpo/cmv_field_sobriety_tests_should_not_be_up_to_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocacpo/cmv_field_sobriety_tests_should_not_be_up_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 18:34:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I understand that someone can be intoxicated on something other than alcohol, so I know why they&amp;#39;re in place. However I do not like that an officer with no training gets to decide to actually charge you with the crime, I believe at most a driver should be taken to the drunk tank and then released (WITH vehicle) and if the blood tests come back negative, then they can charge them and set up a court date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw this because years ago I was pulled over and apparently failed a field sobriety test. I was not on anything, my car was impounded for 30 days, and I had to miss work sometimes due to lack of ride, as well as going to multiple court dates because they kept scheduling them before they had the results, so I would wait all day in court only to be called up and rescheduled because they don&amp;#39;t have the blood work back. Finally I go and they say &amp;quot;oh your blood work was negative, you&amp;#39;re free to leave&amp;quot; but of course no refund for paying close to $2000 to get my car out of impound or anything. I&amp;#39;m not sure what should be the exact solution to this, but I do know that something needs to change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Suicide prevention rallies/social media posts/5ks and stuff are complete bullshit to make the living feel better]]></title><description><![CDATA[Full disclosure, have lost a few friends to suicide, one of which still cuts me
deep to this day... it is the driving force behind my view. People made
T-shirts, had a 5k run, put up social media posts about suicide prevention and
stuff like that. Who the hell is this helping? If someone is…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc4vkm/cmv_suicide_prevention_ralliessocial_media/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc4vkm/cmv_suicide_prevention_ralliessocial_media/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 13:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full disclosure, have lost a few friends to suicide, one of which still cuts me deep to this day... it is the driving force behind my view. People made T-shirts, had a 5k run, put up social media posts about suicide prevention and stuff like that. Who the hell is this helping? If someone is suicidal, none of this will help them. Yes, raising money for suicide hotlines is a noble cause, but guess what- the people that off themselves DO NOT CALL THEM! I know how bitter I sound, I still have a lot of residual anger over my friend&amp;#39;s death, but it just stinks like desperate bullshit people tell themselves to make them feel better. And full disclosure, I have been down some pretty dark roads and no one reaches out to you, nobody cares until it is too late. It is sometimes an impossible thing to see coming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: People should not have received their driver's licenses during the pandemic without taking their road tests.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is happening in the United States. I know multiple people who got their
driver's licenses without taking their road test. This was a ridiculous choice
the government made during the pandemic. Yes, it would have sucked for people
who couldn't get their licenses right away, but for the safety of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1guc/cmv_people_should_not_have_received_their_drivers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1guc/cmv_people_should_not_have_received_their_drivers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 07:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is happening in the United States. I know multiple people who got their driver&amp;#39;s licenses without taking their road test. This was a ridiculous choice the government made during the pandemic. Yes, it would have sucked for people who couldn&amp;#39;t get their licenses right away, but for the safety of the public this shouldn&amp;#39;t have been allowed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people getting these licenses are not good drivers. I know a few who simply couldn&amp;#39;t pass their road test in the past (SpongeBobs) and the pandemic gave them their license despite their lack of skills, all they had to do was fill out some paper work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know three people who got their licenses and got into accidents less than two months after getting them. Our governments are failing us right now in this way and causing more accidents by allowing these licenses to be handed out without road test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV: People should not have received their driver&amp;#39;s licenses during the pandemic without taking their road tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: certain hairstyles do not belong to certain cultures]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've seen POC getting upset on youtube/tiktok for a white person wearing a
hairstyle that they believe should only be worn by their culture and I dont
really understand it.

I was watching a YouTube video of a European women showing how to do a
Nordic/Viking style braid. She braided two cornrows…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obywd5/cmv_certain_hairstyles_do_not_belong_to_certain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obywd5/cmv_certain_hairstyles_do_not_belong_to_certain/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:50:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen POC getting upset on youtube/tiktok for a white person wearing a hairstyle that they believe should only be worn by their culture and I dont really understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was watching a YouTube video of a European women showing how to do a Nordic/Viking style braid. She braided two cornrows (she called them cornrows but I think they were really Dutch braids) on both sides of her head, and then did a big braid on top, gathered all the braids together into a pony in the back. Some people were upset in the comments though, saying that she is appropriating black culture by doing these small Dutch braids, even though this hairstyle was done by vikings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another example, I saw a tiktok of these white girls at a pool, and they all were wearing a silk scarf on their head. People in the comments were upset by this, and claimed they were appropriating black culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just dont understand how a culture can own a certain style of braid or a certain way to tie a scarf to your head. If someone is wearing their hair like that, and they aren&amp;#39;t doing it to be racist, I dont see the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone please explain this to me. I hope this doesn&amp;#39;t come off as racist or ignorant, I&amp;#39;m not trying to be I just dont understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: A person should not be able to be charged with a DUI or DWI unless you are actually driving.]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I was in college a roommate went out drinking one night, got in an
arguement with someone in the bar, and decided to leave. He realized that he had
had too much to drink, so he called a ride. It was mid August and super hot
outside, so while he was waiting on his ride he sat in in his truck and…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1c0n/cmv_a_person_should_not_be_able_to_be_charged/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1c0n/cmv_a_person_should_not_be_able_to_be_charged/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 05:32:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was in college a roommate went out drinking one night, got in an arguement with someone in the bar, and decided to leave.  He realized that he had had too much to drink, so he called a ride.  It was mid August and super hot outside, so while he was waiting on his ride he sat in in his truck and ran the A/C.  A police officer saw him and took him in for a DWI and he was convicted.  It effected his employment and schooling for the next couple of years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never liked the guy much, but I always thought he got a raw deal. He was doing the right thing and got the same penalty as if he decided to drive home.  You should be able to sleep it off in your car without fear of consequence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have heard the argument that if the officer saw a drunk sitting in their car and just walked away from it, the person could start driving at any moment.  I argue that it would be just as easy to take the person home as it would be to take them to jail, and it doesnt ruin their life. The police could even take them to the jail to dry out for the night just to be sure, but there is no reason to suspend their license, fine, and imprison a person for simply sitting in their car with the keys in their possession, or even sitting in a running vehicle. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To head off the first argument I see coming, this doesn&amp;#39;t apply to a vehicle in a lane of traffic, obviously if you are passed out at a stop sign or something you deserve a DWI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: In Breaking Bad, there are some serious Meth Math problems with Walter and Jessie's 3 month job working for Gus]]></title><description><![CDATA[1.) They are making 200 pounds of meth a week for 3 months. (source: The show)

2.) The meth sells at $40 an ounce. (Source:

Jessie keeps saying, "He's selling at 40 a pound". I see 3 possibilities for
this:

A.) He mean $40 a pound. For all the risk they are taking to make Meth, that
seems like…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obt46b/cmv_in_breaking_bad_there_are_some_serious_meth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obt46b/cmv_in_breaking_bad_there_are_some_serious_meth/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 01:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.) They are making 200 pounds of meth a week for 3 months.  (source: The show)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) The meth sells at $40 an ounce. (Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessie keeps saying, &amp;quot;He&amp;#39;s selling at 40 a pound&amp;quot;.  I see 3 possibilities for this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A.) He mean $40 a pound.  For all the risk they are taking to make Meth, that seems like too small of revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B.) Me meant $40,000 a pound.  This sounds like astronomically too high.  How could Meth junkies ever afford their meth if 1 pound sells for 1 years minimum wage salary?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;C.) He mis-poke, and meant $40 an ounce.  This sounds most plausible to me, as it means they are making some decent money from their risk and Meth junkies can still afford to buy their meth.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.) There are 16 ounces in a pound. (Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?client=firefox-b-1-d&amp;amp;q=ounces+in+a+pound&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.) They are working for 13 weeks.  (Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assuming ~31 days in a month, ~31 x 3 = ~93 days in 3 months.  ~93/7 = ~13 weeks in 3 months)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5.)  Conclusion: The meth they make for Gus during the 3 months can sell for ~1.5 million dollars.  (Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$40 (per ounce) x 16 (ounces per pound) x 200 (pounds per week) x 13 (weeks in the job) = $1,664,000, or ~1.5 million dollars)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now lets get down to the problems here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gus is losing money&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gus is paying 3 million dollars for these two guys to make product that he will sell for 1.5 million dollars.  That&amp;#39;s 1.5 million dollars down the drain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walter and Jessie are bad at Math&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessie and Walter both come to the conclusion that Gus is making 93 million off their 3 month job.  Given all the information we have, they should have come to 1.5 million.  Jessie I could understand making a mistake somewhere in this math.  But Walter is supposed to be the smart guy.  How could he also make this mistake?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would change my view&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) Show me a way to interpret the information in the show in such a way that the job is profitable for Gus while still being based in reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) Explain why both Walter and Jessie made such bad math mistakes in their calculations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus points if you can do both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What wouldn&amp;#39;t change my view&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This was a mistake the show-writers made.&lt;/em&gt;  If this is the case I apologize since it means there isn&amp;#39;t really a view to be changed here.  However, I have hope that there is something I am missing that explains this mess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edits/deltas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gus is doing this venture as a long term plan.  Once he has Walt&amp;#39;s formula, he can start making money again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The math at $40k a pound checks out for Walter and Jessie&amp;#39;s calculation if you assume 12 weeks instead of 13 weeks.  12 instead of 13 weeks seems like a simple enough mistake if you assume the 4 weeks per month as many people do.  $40k a pound for meth seems unrealistic to me, but at least that is a flaw in the world building rather than Walter or Jessie&amp;#39;s character.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Junkies buy in teenths (1/16 of an ounce), which makes selling Meth at $40k a pound more reasonable.  Also, $40k a pound checks out with how much money Walter and Jessie were making when they cooked in their RV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Real Meth sells at about the $40k per pound value.  Looks like the show was actually being very realistic after all!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: The line should be drawn at they/them]]></title><description><![CDATA[I Was looking at Instagram the other day and someone im following posted on
their story a post containing multiple slides with pronouns I have never heard
of before, I swear one of them was viv/vov and one was xe/xer. I see 0 reason
why we need to have these in our society and what benefit they…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwzwl/cmv_the_line_should_be_drawn_at_theythem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwzwl/cmv_the_line_should_be_drawn_at_theythem/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 01:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I Was looking at Instagram the other day and someone im following posted on their story a post containing multiple slides with pronouns I have never heard of before, I swear one of them was viv/vov and one was xe/xer. I see 0 reason why we need to have these in our society and what benefit they have: Maybe their is people who actually suffer from gender dysphoria and theirs people who don&amp;#39;t feel like they identify with the gender binary. But why would anyone need to use these pronouns for any reason other than to feel special? this seems to me like nothing more than progression for the sake of progression, call me homophobic all you want but I refuse to call anyone by any pronouns other than him, they or her. Its not like viv/vov people have been oppressed for hundreds of years like gay people. The sad thing is, is most people who share this an opinion with me get &amp;quot;canceled&amp;quot; because criticizing lgbt is some godforsaken sin now a days. I hope this subreddit will understand my POV and give me genuine reasons for why &amp;quot;neopronouns&amp;quot; need to exist and not accuse me of being homophobic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: adult programs and songs shouldn't be censored as they are intended for adults]]></title><description><![CDATA[Corporations shouldn't have to parent your child. You are their parent and it is
your responsibility to raise them. If you don't want your kids to see or hear a
programming then that should be on you. When I hear a song on the radio with 50
different little distorted parts it makes me laugh. If it's…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwn05/cmv_adult_programs_and_songs_shouldnt_be_censored/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwn05/cmv_adult_programs_and_songs_shouldnt_be_censored/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corporations shouldn&amp;#39;t have to parent your child. You are their parent and it is your responsibility to raise them. If you don&amp;#39;t want your kids to see or hear a programming then that should be on you. When I hear a song on the radio with 50 different little distorted parts it makes me laugh. If it&amp;#39;s so inappropriate why is it on a channel meant for all audiences? If it&amp;#39;s so inappropriate why let your child listen to begin with? Do you really think the swear words are the only controversial thing in these songs? Why not simply parent your child and make sure they aren&amp;#39;t consuming content you don&amp;#39;t see fit for your child?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also ruins songs and programs for us adults. There have been parts that are so heavily censored that the joke is basically how censored it is cause you&amp;#39;ll never hear the actual words. You just hear bleep bleep bleeeep bleep bleep bleep and some bleep bleep and then everyone around the character is just shocked and I&amp;#39;m just pissed. Why can I see a character get brutally killed in the most horrific way possible but not hear fuck? Why can I watch a character get sexually assaulted or even raped but as long as I don&amp;#39;t see a dick or a nipple then I&amp;#39;m good? I can watch mass genocide or listen to hate speech but can&amp;#39;t hear cunt?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dumbest part of all of this is 99% of us know exactly what is being censored. It doesn&amp;#39;t actually work as censoring if your mind fills in the blanks. Sure if the screen went completely black whenever nudity or sexual content came on or you censored the whole sentence instead of just the &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; word then yeah it&amp;#39;d work but we don&amp;#39;t do that. It feels like we simply do the level of censoring we do to make the 0.001% of the population who would be lose their shit happy but why the fuck do we care what they think? They aren&amp;#39;t watching the fucking shows! No way you are a stick up the butt prude and like watching South Park and rick and morty and you draw the line at nipples and fucks. Why do we pander to the extreme minority? We could uncensore every adult program and nothing would happen and everyone who watches these programs or listens to these songs would still listen and watch and the only mad ones would be people who don&amp;#39;t even consume that media&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: Woman who demand both equality and chivalry are hypocrites]]></title><description><![CDATA[Now to star I want to clarify what I mean by chivalry. I dont mean treating
people with respect or holding the door open, those are just traits of a decent
human. What I mean is the man asking the woman out , having to plan the date,
pay for it and any further other(since she will hold it againts…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obp7da/cmv_woman_who_demand_both_equality_and_chivalry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obp7da/cmv_woman_who_demand_both_equality_and_chivalry/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 20:43:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now to star I want to clarify what I mean by chivalry. I dont mean treating people with respect or holding the door open, those are just traits of a decent human. What I mean is the man asking the woman out , having to plan the date, pay for it and any further other(since she will hold it againts him if he dosnt) and generally having to ,, woo her,, while she stays passive. The main reason for this post is a coment I read on one of the dating subs(looking trought the controversial section on them is a guilty pleasure when I&amp;#39;m bored). It was a woman comenthing how when a guy dosnt pay for the date he shows that he is cheap and lazy and yet saying that she never pays for a date. This really annoyed me because it really reminds me of ,, modern day femenist,,. I belive that if a woman want equality ( which everyone should want) then she must accept both the benefits and the responsibility that come with it. You cant just say well I reject the gender norms in this and this area since they hinder me but I want to keep them in this and this are since I benefit from them. If you want to be intellectually honest you either chose equality,  both the good and the bad, or choose old school. Meaning that you demand that the guys is the archetype of the old school gentleman, but you also have to be the archetype of the old school woman(staying in the house, cooking, cleaning and taking care of his sexual needs whenever he wants). Now there isnt anything wrong with either of the options( different tastes for different people) but anything in between and your just a hypocrite who wants to have their cake and eat it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Biden's claim that you would need F15s and Nukes to fight the government was incorrect]]></title><description><![CDATA[View is related to this statement:

https://youtu.be/SHLHkmWoYDU

Rationale:

America pretty much lost the Iraq war. Sure they got rid of Saddam, but they
didnt subdue the militant Islamists and ex-Iraqi army militias at all. Once they
left Isis had the strength to not only conquer large swathes of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/objxpa/cmv_bidens_claim_that_you_would_need_f15s_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/objxpa/cmv_bidens_claim_that_you_would_need_f15s_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:48:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View is related to this statement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/SHLHkmWoYDU&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/SHLHkmWoYDU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rationale:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America pretty much lost the Iraq war. Sure they got rid of Saddam, but they didnt subdue the militant Islamists and ex-Iraqi army militias at all. Once they left Isis had the strength to not only conquer large swathes of Iraq, but the middle east proper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America has 7x the population of Iraq and something like 10x the guns, plus a populace with a ludicrously high rate of firearm profficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add to that the radically different levels of desertion, and more importantly sabotage. You think fragging was bad in Nam, see what happens when you invade Texas lmfao.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add to that the logistical nightmare that is protecting US infrastructure, literally 10s of millions of unguardable targets, and the whole thing starts looking unwinnable for the government very fucking fast.  US geography is also an extremely daunting challenge with regards to suppressing rebellion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there is the foreign actor concern. Allies would put pressure on to stop the killing of civilians (which would be a necessary collateral outcome of fighting your own people). Enemies would gleefully support the rebels in any way they could as hard as they could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government would never fucking glass its own territory and people with nukes, its fucking ridiculous to suggest such a thing. Even conventional bombing would be asking to feed into desertion and further rebellion. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not wanting to invade due to a rifle behind every blade of grass isnt just something for foreign armies to ponder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American citizens should be sickened by his words here, they are deeply unAmerican and downright terrifying to be coming from the top executive in the land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus CMV:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden is straight up lying about the &amp;#39;types of weapons&amp;#39; claim, you could absolutely own cannons as a private citizen. Privateers used them all the time and 2A allowed for their legal ownership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tl:dr&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2A practically ensures the US populace a reasonable if not favored chance against their own government. Not many countries can say that, and none of them have a military as daunting as the yanks. Biden&amp;#39;s cute little comment was pure unadulterated bluff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 1:&lt;/strong&gt; gee whiz its hard to run so many arguments at once. I should have done this with access to my pc instead of just my shitty phone with a cracked screen. I apologise to anybody left waiting, im trying to answer as quickly as possible, im literally sweating!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 2:&lt;/strong&gt; use of the Iraq war as example was just that. Whether that war counted as victory or defeat is not all that relevant to my opinion here, my point was just that the insurgent population was never subdued despite the overwhelming technological advantage wielded by the US military. The Taliban or viet kong might have been better to go with, but thats not exactly comparable because they are militaries themselves at the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 3:&lt;/strong&gt; I will add one argument. The top US military brass have said on many occassions that they are beholden to the constitution first and foremost. I tend to take them at their word, they generally seem like very principled and proud individuals willing to do anything necessary to uphold their oath. That means the President cant just decide to glass entire cities or States that contain innocent civilians in amongst an insurgency or guerilla network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 4:&lt;/strong&gt; I think many here are failing to appreciate the ticking clock the government would be put under during a popular uprising, especially if many people stopped working and paying taxes. The US military is insanely expensive, an insurgency is very cheap. As the Taliban say: &amp;#39;you have the watches, we have the time&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: In a layman conversation, nitpicking on wording is rarely done by people with actually deep knowledge or expertise in a field, and serves little useful purpose.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Whatever your expertise, I'm sure you've had this experience. Someone correcting
a psychologist on an inaccurate use of a term like "fetish". Correcting people
doing an economics PhD on "you can't say free because nothing is free". A
physicist on the usage of "weight", and so on. Or a personal…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obldx3/cmv_in_a_layman_conversation_nitpicking_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obldx3/cmv_in_a_layman_conversation_nitpicking_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:48:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your expertise, I&amp;#39;m sure you&amp;#39;ve had this experience. Someone correcting a psychologist on an inaccurate use of a term like &amp;quot;fetish&amp;quot;. Correcting people doing an economics PhD on &amp;quot;you can&amp;#39;t say free because nothing is free&amp;quot;. A physicist on the usage of &amp;quot;weight&amp;quot;, and so on. Or a personal favorite, focusing on a pronunciation mistake as a way to dismiss the knowledge (translated personal experience: &amp;quot;if you can&amp;#39;t say &lt;em&gt;gratuit&lt;/em&gt; correctly surely you can&amp;#39;t know that much about finance&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My view is that we should strive, in the context of a normal conversation or discussion, to be understandable by the lay public&lt;/strong&gt;, as experts in their fields should strive for us to understand. But to just &amp;quot;nitpick&amp;quot; on the fact that an expert or trained professional uses a more understandable, not perfectly accurate term, is pointless. The chances they know what they are saying are high, and that they know more than whoever is commenting even higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think there is a point in such a context to do this? As it&amp;#39;s something I hear almost daily about many fields and with many colleagues from various backgrounds complaining about this, I figured I should ask myself if maybe it actually could be useful. Am I wrong in preferring more approachable terms?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The less you focus on things out of your control, the happier you will be]]></title><description><![CDATA[For some people they worry about sports or romantic relationships. People waste
a lot of energy hoping their favorite sports teams win the big title or that
cute someone likes them back when it is almost always outside of their control
of what happens there.

For me, it's the stock market, politics,…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obe27y/cmv_the_less_you_focus_on_things_out_of_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obe27y/cmv_the_less_you_focus_on_things_out_of_your/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some people they worry about sports or romantic relationships. People waste a lot of energy hoping their favorite sports teams win the big title or that cute someone likes them back when it is almost always outside of their control of what happens there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, it&amp;#39;s the stock market, politics, religion and cars. Thankfully, I&amp;#39;ve learned to accept the ebbs and flows of the bear and bull days. At this rate I&amp;#39;m going probably going to be in a middle class job where it would be a pipe dream for me to own a Ferrari or Lamborghini so I&amp;#39;ve stopped caring about what the newest hypercar will be like because I might only drive it in a Las Vegas supercar experience once every few years when I can afford it. With politics, I as a single person have little influence on who becomes president or who controls congress yet I still find myself reading political news everyday as if I am addicted to political news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: Piracy CAN be justified]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, yes i think piracy can be justified for various reason.

First of all, if a person has the money to legally pay for a service (movies,
animes, games etc) and they don't do it because they think entertainment should
be free, yes, then piracy can't be justified.

Also i think pirating services…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obh4kl/cmv_piracy_can_be_justified/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obh4kl/cmv_piracy_can_be_justified/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, yes i think piracy can be justified for various reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, if a person has the money to legally pay for a service (movies, animes, games etc) and they don&amp;#39;t do it because they think entertainment should be free, yes, then piracy can&amp;#39;t be justified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also i think pirating services such as games that are made by indie companies and are available to buy for a cheap price, also can&amp;#39;t be justified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that out of the way, let me tell you my reasons :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reston number one: some people are poor. I have heard people say &amp;quot; WeLl iF yOu ArE pOor ThAT doEsNt jUStify sTeAling&amp;quot;, and i consider that bullshit cause, being really poor can also justify stealing in some conditions, if a homeless child steals one apple to steal alive, that isn&amp;#39;t wrong, human life values a lot more than an apple, if a person steals a loaf of bread to feed his family, it&amp;#39;s not something wrong, because again, human life values a lot more than a loaf of bread. So yes, i think stealing can be justified if the person they&amp;#39;re stealing from isn&amp;#39;t poor himself, also don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, i don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s a good thing to steal but if someone&amp;#39;s life depends on it, it can be justified. And for piracy, of course someone&amp;#39;s life doesn&amp;#39;t depend on watching movies, but i think if a poor person pirates some movie, it can lead to that person support the industry when he&amp;#39;s able to, that can also lead to free marketing some people are not able to pay for entertainment and i think it&amp;#39;s OK to pirate as long as it&amp;#39;s not possible to pay, of course as long as they choose to pay when they have the ability to. And also I&amp;#39;ve heard people say &amp;quot; eNtertAinMEnt iS a LuXurY&amp;quot;, and my answer to that is, what does a rich kid do to deserve to have that luxury that a poor broke kid doesn&amp;#39;t? The answer is, nothing, it just depended on their luck. So yes i think pirating can be justified as long as the person pays for it when they can&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2- legally paying for entertainment doesn&amp;#39;t always support the creators. Half the time that you buy something, the money doesn&amp;#39;t actually really go to the actual creators, usually the big company receives the money and not the actual creators. And that happens a lot especially in the Anime/manga industry. The industry has been growing, and that growth leads to more money for the creators, so why are animators still underpaid af? I think when a big company doesn&amp;#39;t pay their employees enough, they deserve their products pirated, at least until they decide to change&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3- it may be impossible to pay for entertainment. You might be confused, this is more of a personal reason but it&amp;#39;s literally impossible for people such as me to pay for entertainment legally. So let me explain, i live in Iran, and in Iran, international banking doesn&amp;#39;t exist, it&amp;#39;s not possible for an iranian person to pay for any service that&amp;#39;s outside of iran, and there&amp;#39;s no service that legally sells entertainment products like movies and animes, even the big streaming services pirate their stuff, so yeah it&amp;#39;s impossible for me to pay for something like Netflix. Also most of the entertainment services have banned iran, so doesn&amp;#39;t that mean they don&amp;#39;t want our money? And also it is possible to buy games, but they are so expensive that it&amp;#39;s possible to pay the rent with the money &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s all I&amp;#39;m going to say, i might be a bit biased, keep in mind that these are my opinions and i don&amp;#39;t count them as objective facts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Social Media is Toxic to Society]]></title><description><![CDATA[It may seem ironic for me to decry social media on a social media site, but I
think it's appropriate --

In my opinion, social media has been a horrific accelerator of humankind's worst
tendecies, and is toxifying our society.

Chronic judgments, superficial lies, and echo chambers of misinformation…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obfpgz/cmv_social_media_is_toxic_to_society/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obfpgz/cmv_social_media_is_toxic_to_society/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may seem ironic for me to decry social media on a social media site, but I think it&amp;#39;s appropriate --&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, social media has been a horrific accelerator of humankind&amp;#39;s worst tendecies, and is toxifying our society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chronic judgments, superficial lies, and echo chambers of misinformation have amplified our negativity, as well as distracted many Americans and other members of industrial societies from real crises like Climate Change, World Hunger, Global Peace, or Social Justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean is, people online are nasty &amp;amp; carry that nastiness into real life. If you aren&amp;#39;t pretty, funny, or witty, no one values you in the digital world &amp;amp; the culture of people who learn this way likewise treat you cruelly in real life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even more scary, actual life-or-death needs are tragically ignored by bad info on FaceBook, InstaGram, Twitter, or even Reddit etc. We see vaccine lies lead to people dying ; we also see violent white supremacists organize domestic terror ; and we see junk science like alternate &amp;quot;climate&amp;quot; hypotheses spread as though they&amp;#39;re scientific theories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So with so much global ugliness emanating from online, what good is there to the tech of social media?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: It is socially acceptable to make fun of white people, as well as Americans.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Title could have been worded better. I’m not saying it ‘should’ be socially
acceptable, I’m saying that I believe it is currently (subconsciously) accepted,
and it shouldn’t be. I’m asking you to convince me that it is not socially
accepted.

Before anyone misinterprets this, this does not mean that…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obbfc0/cmv_it_is_socially_acceptable_to_make_fun_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obbfc0/cmv_it_is_socially_acceptable_to_make_fun_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title could have been worded better. I’m not saying it ‘should’ be socially acceptable, I’m saying that I believe it is currently (subconsciously) accepted, and it shouldn’t be. I’m asking you to convince me that it is not socially accepted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before anyone misinterprets this, this does not mean that other races and nationalities do not face racism and discrimination. I know that they face it much worse than whites and Americans, and I understand systematic racism and white privilege.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My point is that if you were to make a negative remark about a white person, it is not socially frowned upon. And that same remark made by a white person towards any person who isn’t white would have you labeled a racist. I’ll give an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;White person recommends going to a bar that is predominantly white. Response is “I don’t really want to be around that many white people haha”. Socially acceptable, even possibly a joke. No outrage. If it’s reversed and the comment is “I don’t really want to be around that many black people haha”. You are a racist, and a comment like that would destroy relationships. Replace black with literally any other race, and the comment is equally as racist, but made towards a white it’s like whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen the term “wypipo” for white people. No one says it’s racist, it just is what it is. If white people had a nickname for black people that black people did not like, you would be shunned for using it. Something like “they don’t like being called that, so stop”. But if white people don’t like being called wypipo? Doesn’t seem like it matters…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example about Americans. (Living as an American in another country has made me realise this over and over again, it never ends). A comment overheard in public “Americans are so annoying”. Everyone supports it (except for Americans of course), but the response is not “Wow that was actually racist”. Everyone openly agrees, it’s socially acceptable. Even if they don’t agree, you aren’t shunned for it. Same comment but replace Americans with literally any other nationality. “Japanese people are so annoying”, heads would turn and you’d be labeled a racist instantly, and rightfully so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: previous examples are xenophobic , not racist, but same idea of the discrimination. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been afraid to discuss this sentiment among peers, so before you change my view, can you please also let me know if I’m way out of line, or if it has some merit of truth, but the discussion itself may not even be socially acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: also to be clear, I don’t think that people are ‘intentionally’ accepting of this, it seems like more of a subconscious thing, not realising that there is anything wrong with being said&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: Inserting nonwhite characters into stories based on old European culture or mythology does not help promote diversity and should not be encouraged.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I saw a clip from frozen 2 recently and noticed a pretty significant number of
non white characters, to my surprise. I don’t understand the logic these
additions. Frozen is set hundreds of years ago In Scandinavia. Is it just
shallow attempts at diversity?

My favorite show of all time is Avatar:…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obdava/cmv_inserting_nonwhite_characters_into_stories/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obdava/cmv_inserting_nonwhite_characters_into_stories/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 07:33:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw a clip from frozen 2 recently and noticed a pretty significant number of non white characters, to my surprise. I don’t understand the logic these additions. Frozen is set hundreds of years ago In Scandinavia. Is it just shallow attempts at diversity?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite show of all time is Avatar: the Last Airbender. It’s world is based on old Asian and Inuit culture and mythology. There are no white people in it and there shouldn’t be. I don’t see why the same logic shouldn’t apply to other stories like Frozen, Lord of the Rings, the Witcher, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only do these insertions seem forced and awkward, they take away from what could be. How many great mainstream fantasy stories are there based on old African mythology and culture? I can’t really think of any.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: San Jose's new "gunowners pay for gun violence" policy is wrong]]></title><description><![CDATA[San Jose has enacted a new policy that will force everybody who wishes to
exercise their 2nd amendment right to purchase insurance that will be used to
pay victims of gun violence.

I think it's wrong. Imagine this equivalent scenario to understand why I feel
this way:

"Everyone who exercises their…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob61pw/cmv_san_joses_new_gunowners_pay_for_gun_violence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob61pw/cmv_san_joses_new_gunowners_pay_for_gun_violence/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 02:39:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Jose has enacted a new policy that will force everybody who wishes to exercise their 2nd amendment right to purchase insurance that will be used to pay victims of gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;#39;s wrong. Imagine this equivalent scenario to understand why I feel this way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Everyone who exercises their first amendment rights by speaking or writing should be required to pay libel/slander insurance to the government to pay damages for all the victims of illegal speech.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should rub you the wrong way... Or at least it does me. But I would like to hear from people who support this policy, since it is popular in many online circles, to see what I&amp;#39;m missing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Countries such as the UK that have Egyptian artifacts have no obligation to give those artifacts back, and the Egyptian government has no more claim over the ownership of those artifacts than any other government on the planet]]></title><description><![CDATA[I often hear about how countries "plundered" these artifacts from Egypt that
they have no right to have, and that this is wrong and they should return these
artifacts, but I disagree with this for several reasons. While I can understand
this reasoning for many of the existing cultures that had their…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaybaw/cmv_countries_such_as_the_uk_that_have_egyptian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaybaw/cmv_countries_such_as_the_uk_that_have_egyptian/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:38:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often hear about how countries &amp;quot;plundered&amp;quot; these artifacts from Egypt that they have no right to have, and that this is wrong and they should return these artifacts, but I disagree with this for several reasons. While I can understand this reasoning for many of the existing cultures that had their artifacts taken in recent memory, my primary contention with this for Egypt specifically is that they&amp;#39;re incredibly old. The Egyptians that created these artifacts and all their ancestors are long dead, and the people and government that currently live in Egypt are just the conquerors of the conquerors of the conquerors of the people who did create this artifacts. The British and others took these artifacts from the people who took them from the people who took them from the people who lived there thousands of years ago, their claim doesn&amp;#39;t really seem any less reasonable than those of the current Egyptian people or government. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I don&amp;#39;t really believe these artifacts should sit concentrated at a few European museums either, I believe when it comes to things this old they should be considered to be part of our shared heritage as a species and should be equally distributed around the world to all stable countries that could reasonable house them (I could make another argument about how Egypt is not the best place for these artifacts on the basis of the instability of the government alone), so that as many people as possible could see them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So CMV, why should these artifacts return to Egypt?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: I don't find libertarianism to be all that crazy or unreasonable]]></title><description><![CDATA[Naturally, an individual libertarian can be unreasonable. And any political
viewpoint will look insane when taken to its logical extremes.

At it's most basic form, a libertarian believes that a person or group of people
in government are not capable of knowing what's best for me as an individual,…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob1x57/cmv_i_dont_find_libertarianism_to_be_all_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob1x57/cmv_i_dont_find_libertarianism_to_be_all_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:38:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, an individual libertarian can be unreasonable. And any political viewpoint will look insane when taken to its logical extremes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At it&amp;#39;s most basic form, a libertarian believes that a person or group of people in government are not capable of knowing what&amp;#39;s best for me as an individual, or you as an individual. This is at it&amp;#39;s worse at the federal level, and gets slightly better as government gets more local.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, a libertarian wants to reduce the power of government to &lt;strong&gt;only what&amp;#39;s necessary.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is where individual libertarians would have discussions and debate, around what is necessary and what is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, a libertarian could absolutely be for universal healthcare. They might compare what we pay right now on average to the NHS, and see that we actually pay more than they do. Then there could be a discussion that the free market isn&amp;#39;t working right with healthcare because people don&amp;#39;t know what they will pay for the service, and the service is often times non-optional. Thus, it is necessary for the government to fund healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think where leftists and libertarians most often disagree is actually around the framing of the discussion. If the subject is social safety nets for example, the leftist will enter the conversation on the assumption that government is the one and only option for providing help to those that need it. The libertarian does not enter the conversation with this assumption. So the conversation is doomed from the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They aren&amp;#39;t disagreeing about helping people, they are disagreeing about the method of doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my view is that libertarianism isn&amp;#39;t any more or less crazy than conservatism or liberalism. Both of the latter philosophies wish to use the government to enforce their views, while libertarianism does not. I don&amp;#39;t find that to be an unreasonable political philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: As someone who generally identifies as pretty far left, I am actually struggling to see how Transracial and Trangender are fundamentally different]]></title><description><![CDATA[Throwaway because I've noticed that this can be a pretty inflammatory topic, but
I am trying to be curious, honest, open, and earnest. That said, I have a pretty
privileged background and none of these issues have impacted my life directly,
so I will definitely have pretty big gaps in my…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay9ks/cmv_as_someone_who_generally_identifies_as_pretty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay9ks/cmv_as_someone_who_generally_identifies_as_pretty/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:32:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throwaway because I&amp;#39;ve noticed that this can be a pretty inflammatory topic, but I am trying to be curious, honest, open, and earnest. That said, I have a pretty privileged background and none of these issues have impacted my life directly, so I will definitely have pretty big gaps in my understanding. I have made what I think is an honest effort to understand both sides of this debate (which seems to have been set off by a couple recent reddit/twitter posts and the Oli London video), and I feel like I&amp;#39;m reaching a completely different conclusion to the people close to me (and online) that I tend to agree with, so I want to challenge my thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general I am 100% fine with people being cisgender, transgender, non-binary, gender-fluid, transsexual, or whatever else as long as they are doing it in good faith.* Not everybody thinks this way, obviously, so we have this big cultural change underway as people come to grips with gender identity.  Big cultural shifts tend to create really challenging social/cultural knock-on effects. In my mind, this question about racial identity and being transracial is one of them. I don&amp;#39;t think there are easy answers for a lot of these questions, but I think we owe it to eachother to listen, explore, communicate, and compromise. The conversations that I&amp;#39;ve seen so far on the topic of racial identity are far from honest, with arguments like: &amp;quot;Gender dysphoria is a part of psychology [and racial dysphoria isn&amp;#39;t]&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ToiletPaperUSA/comments/o9svvj/called_it/h3daui1?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;0&lt;/a&gt; (Gender dysphoria wasn&amp;#39;t either, 50 years ago); &amp;quot;Culture and heritage however is lived through communities. It can be  appropriated and abused. A white British person claiming to be  trans-Korean diminishes the experiences and burdens of actual Korean people and communities.&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ToiletPaperUSA/comments/o9svvj/called_it/h3dc4wt?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt; (Gender has a massive cultural component), &amp;quot;Race and Ethnicity is Rooted in Ancestry… You Can’t Just Pick and Choose&amp;quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/verve-up/transracial-is-not-the-new-transgender-why-race-and-gender-are-not-synonymous-b2c688ef0fae&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt; (sounds a lot like the &amp;#39;gender is rooted in biology&amp;#39; argument to me) and &amp;quot;We also think that, as a result of this asymmetry, transgender identities deserve social uptake and so-called “transracial”  identifications as Black almost always do not. (We leave space for  unique circumstances in which someone who has deeply invested in a Black community and been forthcoming about their racial history is nevertheless accepted within that community as Black.)&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bostonreview.net/race-philosophy-religion-gender-sexuality/robin-dembroff-dee-payton-why-we-shouldnt-compare&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2015/jun/16/transracial-definition-destructive-rachel-dolezal-spokane-naacp&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt; (there&amp;#39;s obviously massive differences, but this argument isn&amp;#39;t fundamentally different to arguing that trans women aren&amp;#39;t women because they haven&amp;#39;t grown up having periods, experiencing sexism, etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting aside (for now) the existing use of &amp;#39;transracial&amp;#39; used in the context of adopted children raised outside of their biological parents&amp;#39; ethnic/racial cultures, I think that being transracial is similar in a lot of ways to being transgender or transexual, and I don&amp;#39;t see how that de-legitimizes either of those things. I think there&amp;#39;s a lot of fear on the left that this comparison makes the transgender/transsexual struggle look somehow ridiculous or absurd by association &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ToiletPaperUSA/comments/o9svvj/called_it/&quot;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt; and I guess I can see why people might think that, but it feels like either an unhelpful gut reaction, or (being a bit pessimistic) an overly political/strategic reaction which looks a lot like &lt;a href=&quot;https://thomasnastcartoons.com/2015/01/06/throwing-down-the-ladder-by-which-they-rose-23-july-1870/&quot;&gt;throwing the ladder down&lt;/a&gt;. Every new cultural idea is uncomfortable at first, but we don&amp;#39;t know if it has any merit if we don&amp;#39;t explore it in good faith. I think it&amp;#39;s also a missed opportunity to better understand trans/identity in general&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the other (original) definition of transracial -- adopted children raised outside their biological parents&amp;#39; culture/race -- I think it&amp;#39;s a really interesting bridge between transsexual identity politics and transracial (the other/new definition) identity politics, because there are hundreds of thousands of cases of transracial adoption, and I&amp;#39;m sure we could learn a lot about culture and identity if we asked them about it.  I expect some of these children experience very real, very complicated dysphoria [citation needed, obviously].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know if the likes of Rachel Dolezal, Oli London, Ja Du, Ekundayo, etc are charlatans or people in genuine turmoil deserving of, if not our sympathy, at least our patience. What I do know is that this kind of tectonic cultural shift has happened enough times throughout history that I think I want to hedge my bets and at least be kind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Quick aside:  I don&amp;#39;t say &amp;quot;as long as it isn&amp;#39;t hurting anyone&amp;quot; because I&amp;#39;ve observed that change hurts, and a lot of people are experiencing real pain caused by this big cultural shift in favor of trans rights and that&amp;#39;s unavoidable. However, I think there will always be charlatans out there who take advantage of the opportunity that any big disruption creates, so that&amp;#39;s why I say &amp;#39;in good faith&amp;#39;. You can pick your example of this, from people &amp;#39;playing the race card&amp;#39; to children setting their screen names to &amp;#39;Connecting...&amp;#39; to get out of zoom/skype classes during a pandemic. Big changes create opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: There exists a period of lockdown (perhaps 2 years years, perhaps 5, perhaps 75, but some duration), extension beyond which is not justified even by saving lives]]></title><description><![CDATA[The rise of the delta variant has got me thinking:

Let's start with an extreme case: lockdown for the entire natural lives of
people born today.

Would anyone disagree that this period of lockdown would not be justified even
if scientifically established to save lives?

I think not.

So then the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oag13m/cmv_there_exists_a_period_of_lockdown_perhaps_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oag13m/cmv_there_exists_a_period_of_lockdown_perhaps_2/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:32:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of the delta variant has got me thinking:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s start with an extreme case: lockdown for the entire natural lives of people born today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would anyone disagree that this period of lockdown would not be justified even if scientifically established to save lives? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think not. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So then the question becomes what IS the maximum duration of lockdown that is justified even if scientifically established to save lives?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there a meaningful difference between &amp;quot;permanent&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;indefinite&amp;quot;? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that some maximal threshold should be debated and agreed upon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: Political Debates should modernize by requiring sources and figures, in order to force accountability for claims]]></title><description><![CDATA[The way the US currently runs political debates is kinda a clusterfuck.
Politicians are throwing numbers around left and right. After the debate is over
you have another 30-45 minutes of programming dedicated to fact-checking what
they said, again without any sources.

As part of a political debate,…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay3cb/cmv_political_debates_should_modernize_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay3cb/cmv_political_debates_should_modernize_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The way the US currently runs political debates is kinda a clusterfuck. Politicians are throwing numbers around left and right. After the debate is over you have another 30-45 minutes of programming dedicated to fact-checking what they said, again without any sources. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of a political debate, politicians should be allowed to prepare a presentation for each of the big questions that are released beforehand. These should be backed up by easily accessible sources, so that the viewers can verify the claims if they want to, while they are watching the debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it goes into the shorter rapid-fire debates between two candidates this obviously isn&amp;#39;t feasible. Instead, I feel like the respective campaigns should be forced to put out a statement afterward citing sources for as many of the points their candidate made as is possible. If they said something that can&amp;#39;t be backed up, then they issue an apology and a clarification. This would preferably be done at the next debate or some other televised event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that this is far from perfect and that it&amp;#39;s possible to find sources supporting most opinions. However, politicians have been known to just spout random &amp;quot;facts&amp;quot; that are later proven false. I think this would go a small way to deter this type of behavior, without decreasing the viewability or essence of a political debate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: Nutrition, sleep, and other ‘physical’ aspects of self care are extremely underrated in improving mental health]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let me start off by saying that I am beyond the point in my interests of
nutrition and sleep where I think they are end all be all determiners of health.

BUT… I do strongly believe that the connection between how you feel (your
energy, outlook, emotions, cognition, decision making abilities) is not…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaw37t/cmv_nutrition_sleep_and_other_physical_aspects_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaw37t/cmv_nutrition_sleep_and_other_physical_aspects_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 14:33:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by saying that I am beyond the point in my interests of nutrition and sleep where I think they are end all be all determiners of health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BUT… I do strongly believe that the connection between how you feel (your energy, outlook, emotions, cognition, decision making abilities) is not brought to the forefront of solving issues like depression, unproductiveness, and aggression like it should. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everybody is willing to acknowledge that diet and sleep have profound effects on health but very few seem to actually realise it and apply it to themselves. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More often than not I feel as though that ‘tiring job’ or ‘draining relationship’ is more a result of a poor diet and sleep regime than it is actual social interactions having an effect. No, you are not tired on Saturday because you ‘just finished an exhausting work week’, you are tired because you eat and sleep like shit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong, hormones can be influenced by social interactions, but over a long period of time I see their effects as minimal in comparison to a good regime. (I’m saying this to attribute more of the effect to diet and sleep, I’m not saying that severe events like a loved one’s passing can’t sometimes overpower the effects of diet and sleep). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mind you, I’m in the prime of my life physically and I don’t expect the entire population to have my level of energy or sharpness so I realise my bias, but I don’t think people without prexisting conditions are doomed to things like midday lethargy and morning grogginess. On a good day of eating and sleeping I have energy throughout and feel cognitively present at all times, regardless of my social context. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah, also, what is with normalising things like lethargy, headaches, and brain fog?? I constantly see people accept things like post-meal lethargy as concrete and unchangeable. People literally plan their days around when they’ll be lethargic instead of actually trying to fix the problem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me started on the neurodepressive effects of eating and sleeping like garbage. Not saying all cases of depression can be solved with those two things alone, but they can certainly be greatly ameliorated by them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realisation translates into action. 2/3rds of the American popular is overweight, if that doesn’t show that this isn’t an unpopular sentiment I don’t know what does. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Kick me down a peg I’ve been lurking pubmed and NCBI for too long. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Also this isn’t intended to invalidate other aspects of self care)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: as a Mexican: People from "my culture" living in the US get way too mad about things that don't really bother us to an extent it is actually offensive.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Seeing "latino culture" defended by people as far from it as any other around
them because it "belongs to them" just because of their ancestry has made me
look into it as people pushing towards stereotypes harder than everyone else.
Someone from another culture wants their tacos made in a way that…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oapwcp/cmv_as_a_mexican_people_from_my_culture_living_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oapwcp/cmv_as_a_mexican_people_from_my_culture_living_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 09:46:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing &amp;quot;latino culture&amp;quot; defended by people as far from it as any other around them because it &amp;quot;belongs to them&amp;quot; just because of their ancestry has made me look into it as people pushing towards stereotypes harder than everyone else. Someone from another culture wants their tacos made in a way that they like? We get to see a buzzfeed article or video from a &amp;quot;Mexican&amp;quot; (who has clearly never been in Mexico) get mad about it while we eat carne asada sushi. As most of the countries in the continent, we have a wide mix of ancestors and races and some people just ignore that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Cultural Appropriation is not a real issue]]></title><description><![CDATA[It can be corny or hurt someone’s feelings, but that is the extent of it. The
only negative consequence i can think of is that it would make someone upset.
But, i think their reason for being upset is not legitimate.

If a white person opens a Jamaican restaurant, that would be considered…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oamfqf/cmv_cultural_appropriation_is_not_a_real_issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oamfqf/cmv_cultural_appropriation_is_not_a_real_issue/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 06:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be corny or hurt someone’s feelings,  but that is the extent of it. The only negative consequence i can think of is that it would make someone upset. But, i think their reason for being upset is not legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a white person opens a Jamaican restaurant, that would be considered cultural appropriation. If they have no clue what they’re doing, the business will fail. If they are excellent Jamaican cooks, the business will do well. Both situations seem just to me. So there is no issue with them appropriating Jamaican culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that’s all i have to say about that. Just meeting the character count&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Standardized tests actually do a pretty decent job of evaluating a combination of learned knowledge and cognitive ability.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have tutored many of the American standardized tests (SAT, ACT, GRE, LSAT,
etc) for years. They're actually pretty good.

The reading sections of the SAT/ACT perhaps leave the most to be desired. Being
able to parse text from 300 years ago is to a large degree a function of having
experience…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oahqlj/cmv_standardized_tests_actually_do_a_pretty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oahqlj/cmv_standardized_tests_actually_do_a_pretty/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 05:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have tutored many of the American standardized tests (SAT, ACT, GRE, LSAT, etc) for years. They&amp;#39;re actually pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reading sections of the SAT/ACT perhaps leave the most to be desired. Being able to parse text from 300 years ago is to a large degree a function of having experience reading text from 300 years ago. So, when you get a reading passage like that, it&amp;#39;s testing if you read older books a lot. There&amp;#39;s also the matter of questions that start to venture into a certain bit of subjectivity. &amp;quot;Choose the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; answer&amp;quot; they say, and I&amp;#39;ve come upon times where I didn&amp;#39;t entirely agree with what they thought was the &amp;#39;best answer&amp;#39;. This is why I personally would be able to get a perfect score on math sections time and time again, but might get 1 or 2 wrong in the reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The grammar sections are better. Gone are the old &amp;#39;this is to that and that is to...&amp;#39; questions, which tested raw vocabulary, and instead it&amp;#39;s mostly testing to see if you understand English. Yes, language evolves, but every needs to learn how to write and speak well in the formal standard of our times, as a practical thing. We want to prepare people to go into job interviews and the like and be able to be well-spoken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The math sections really didn&amp;#39;t need that many changes, as they are entirely solid. They do exactly what they should: Take material from school, and give it a little bit of a twist that tests a deeper understanding. Excellent. This simultaneously tests a bit of what you learned, and how well you can think. I might give a certain amount of more difficult questions on the SAT, but overall I think it&amp;#39;s a very good evaluation tool. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the proof of that is that you can&amp;#39;t really &amp;#39;crack the code&amp;#39; - I&amp;#39;ve had parents in the past who unfortunately wanted me to arrive with some sort of secret formula to a high score, and the reality is that there isn&amp;#39;t one, because the test is well designed. The secret to a better score is &amp;quot;learn the material, and beyond that have a high IQ&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other tests are different, but in a proper way. The GRE kind of abandons the idea of testing your high school learning, because it knows you just spent 4 years in college in who knows what major. Better to test you in ways that don&amp;#39;t require a lot of rote math knowledge, but more reasoning skills that are universal - and that&amp;#39;s exactly what it does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The LSAT, for law school admission, is the closest to a pure IQ test. I kinda gave up on tutoring it, because the reality was there was only so much I could do for people...because it&amp;#39;s an IQ test! I would have gotten above 170 the first time I ever saw the material, because I have a very high IQ, and experience with the questions over time brings me up another 5 points probably. Nothing I can teach you is going to bring you from a 140 to a 180. Nothing. It&amp;#39;s an IQ test. And that&amp;#39;s fitting for law school, where you&amp;#39;re going to want a difficult test for elite-level cognitive and reasoning ability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So are these tests perfect? No, and they couldn&amp;#39;t be. Are they generally pretty good though? Yes, absolutely. Do they give you a very solid baseline impression of the student you would be getting for your school or program? Totally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I think people who dislike them tend to do so for the simple reason that they find them hard and don&amp;#39;t score well on them. And to address some other concerns:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aren&amp;#39;t the tests culturally biased?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, they&amp;#39;re not. Even decades ago, where you might occasionally get a question about a &amp;quot;silo&amp;quot; or something that had disparate familiarity to different regions or people, that effect would have been small. Now they&amp;#39;ve gotten very careful about such things. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only way you can get to cultural bias now is if you go to crazy town where math itself is culturally biased, or the very concept of correct empirical answers is a symptom of white patriarchy. Yeah, there are people who go there, sadly, but they certainly shouldn&amp;#39;t be listened to by anyone serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But isn&amp;#39;t IQ testing is flawed, and aren&amp;#39;t there are multiple kinds of intelligence?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. At least, certainly not to the degree that gets around, again, spread by people with a certain agenda. The reality is that IQ testing is incredibly robust and predictive, possibly more so than any other psychological metric available. I crush basically all standardized tests, and always have, because the cognitive ability I apply to a test translates super readily through sections of that test, and to all the other tests as well. In high school I got a perfect score on sections of the SAT and ACT without any studying. And equivalently, I tend to score like 140 or so on IQ tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Doesn&amp;#39;t that kind of invalidate your job?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bit, yes. Like I said, I gave up teaching the LSAT because I felt full of shit. But I can certainly teach someone the rote math and grammar rules they need for the high school tests, and improve their score. Again, no one is going from a 430 to an 800 on an SAT section, but a 600 might be in the cards with some work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So why do people dislike these tests so much?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mostly, because they themselves aren&amp;#39;t very good at them, or their kids don&amp;#39;t do well on them, and that makes them feel bad. So they try to say they don&amp;#39;t measure anything. There&amp;#39;s also a larger cultural movement that tries to dismantle all of these things if it&amp;#39;s shown that results are disparate among different races or sexes, because then that could only be the fault of the test being wrong and evil to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What could we do better?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I was designing it from the ground up, I would have one test that was pure cognitive/IQ, and other tests that were tests of learned knowledge. You also want the math testing to have a harder curve into more difficult questions, because as it is getting a perfect on the math SAT or ACT is actually quite easy, and so there are students who might be exceptionally capable whose abilities won&amp;#39;t show up. The Korean CSAT is actually an awesome test - the English section is literally better than our English section, and the math section shows a nice road map to me of the level we should be both be teaching advanced students to, and testing them at.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Just because a couple does not marry, does not mean that they are not as committed to each other as a married couple]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just because a couple doesn’t want to have a wedding or sign any documentation,
that does not mean that they are any less committed to each other than a couple
that chooses do so. It also does not mean that they will not be together
long-term or even forever......because they still could. I mean, I…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oag3um/cmv_just_because_a_couple_does_not_marry_does_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oag3um/cmv_just_because_a_couple_does_not_marry_does_not/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:13:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just because a couple doesn’t want to have a wedding or sign any documentation, that does not mean that they are any less committed to each other than a couple that chooses do so. It also does not mean that they will not be together long-term or even forever......because they still could. I mean, I know a couple who has lived together for 25 years. They live together, are monogamous, travel together, bond with other’s families, and don’t seem to have any signs of breaking up anytime soon. They just don’t feel like they need a piece of paper to prove their love. You mean to tell me that they have less commitment than what society considers, “married”?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And also, traditional marriage also feels like a scam. I mean, If it doesn’t workout, it only leave you more debt if you can’t afford a prenup. These other legal benefits is unfair  because why is it that only married couples can visit each other in the hospital and get have marital tax deductions and all that? Their love is no more special than the couple I mentioned in the first paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: All the US flag apparel people wear and use around July 4th disrespects the flag itself]]></title><description><![CDATA[Background: -US Federal Law Code says the flag isn’t to be used for clothing.
The code isn’t enforceable because of the 1st amendment. -American Legion says
it’s okay to have the flag resembled on clothing.

The flag is something to be honored and respected. It’s colors and design is not
something…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaixvf/cmv_all_the_us_flag_apparel_people_wear_and_use/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaixvf/cmv_all_the_us_flag_apparel_people_wear_and_use/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 01:14:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background: 
-US Federal Law Code says the flag isn’t to be used for clothing. The code isn’t enforceable because of the 1st amendment. 
-American Legion says it’s okay to have the flag resembled on clothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flag is something to be honored and respected. It’s colors and design is not something you should use to cloth yourself. It’s not patriotic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Socks? You’re feet are on the ground, get dirty, and smell. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underwear/Swimsuits? You’re putting the flag’s colors and design next to your “netherlands”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shirts? Your pits stink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pants? You sit on them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paper napkins/plates? You eat off that, wipe your face with it, and throw it away. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t even taking into consideration all of this “patriotism” is really just commercialization of the flag and drives revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not just let the flag fly the way it’s supposed to? (you know… like a FLAG)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Police purposely putting incorrect information into a report should be a criminal offense.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I think if it can be proven beyond a reasonable doubt, that an officer purposely
put the wrong information in a report, they should be imprisoned for that
conduct.

Now I know human memory can be fickle. Remembering something exactly as it
happened even 5 hours prior can prove to have some…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaeb14/cmv_police_purposely_putting_incorrect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaeb14/cmv_police_purposely_putting_incorrect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 21:35:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think if it can be proven beyond a reasonable doubt, that an officer purposely put the wrong information in a report, they should be imprisoned for that conduct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I know human memory can be fickle. Remembering something exactly as it happened even 5 hours prior can prove to have some inconsistencies. It would be up to the DA’s Office to pull past reports from the officer, other reports from serving officers, available eye witness testimony and video evidence to show that this was not a case of remembering something incorrectly… but a blatant attempt to make the situation different than it was to excuse/condone the cops behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not many cases of false reports come to my head at the moment. However, I recently saw one in New Jersey where a cop beat a guy in a hallway. He claimed the guy failed to raise his hands once told and also attacked the cop. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another one was a few years ago in a more high profile case, McDonald in Chicago. Several cops wrote in their report something that was incorrect once seen on camera. If one guy remembers something in correctly. Understandable…. If multiple remember something that didn’t happen but in the same manner… something is up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These actions alone (regardless of any other actions by the cop or suspect) should be enough for time behind bars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Only having private companies for necessities fundamentally doesn't work for public-good]]></title><description><![CDATA[For systems that are needed by people, like public transport, access to food and
healthcare, there is no competition. When the customer doesn't have the ability
to abstain from the system as a whole, companies aren't incentivised to higher
quality and lower prices, they're incentivised to just be…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oa8td7/cmv_only_having_private_companies_for_necessities/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oa8td7/cmv_only_having_private_companies_for_necessities/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:04:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For systems that are needed by people, like public transport, access to food and healthcare, there is no competition. When the customer doesn&amp;#39;t have the ability to abstain from the system as a whole, companies aren&amp;#39;t incentivised to higher quality and lower prices, they&amp;#39;re incentivised to just be equal with &amp;quot;competitors&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would Apple sell their phone as competitively as possible when they and Samsung can just double the price and 50/50 the market? Same thing with healthcare; why would someone charge less for an MRI when the hospital across the road can price-gouge with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surely, there needs to be a good-faith alternative that has the primary goal of low-cost-high-quality to drive competition?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Youtube, Twitter and other western social media networks blocked in China should ban CCP accounts and Chinese state run media]]></title><description><![CDATA[A quick search on youtube reveals CGTN news, which is Chinese state run news.
Youtube is a banned website in China, so why is China posting on youtube? Two
reasons, one to spread their propaganda to the west to indoctrinate followers.
Two, in China there is a massive gray area, and many Chinese…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9ui5q/cmv_youtube_twitter_and_other_western_social/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9ui5q/cmv_youtube_twitter_and_other_western_social/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A quick search on youtube reveals CGTN news, which is Chinese state run news.  Youtube is a banned website in China, so why is China posting on youtube? Two reasons, one to spread their propaganda to the west to indoctrinate followers.  Two, in China there is a massive gray area, and many Chinese people have VPNs and brouse western websites such as youtube.  If China broadcasts their message on western websites which Chinese users have to download a VPN and enter a legal gray area to view, it will further drive home the message the CCP is right.  This is why if you search up Chinese youtube content, you can quickly find numerous channels run by westerners in China who are straight up CCP apologists.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wb-MNi8E-TA&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wb-MNi8E-TA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s an example of straight up propaganda, with the CCP trying to cover up their genocidal camps.  I&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s pretty easy to find CCP officials on twitter as well, here&amp;#39;s two examples &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/zlj517?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/zlj517?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lijian Zhao&amp;#39;s bio says he&amp;#39;s a spokesman in the Chinese foreign affairs agency&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SpokespersonCHN&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/SpokespersonCHN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hua Chunying is another spokesperson for the Chinese foreign affairs agency.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scrolling through their twitter feeds, I can find numerous examples of CCP propaganda, such as deflecting from the genocide in Xinjiang by criticizing the recent news in Canada about bodies found at reform schools.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is this stuff allowed? Twitter and Youtube are literally banned in mainland China, so why are CCP government officials allowed on these platforms? They should be banned right back, All their presence does is spew misinformation and lies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: We should cure disabilities if we can despite the effects it would have on Disability culture.]]></title><description><![CDATA[TLDR; Why shouldn't we try to cure preventable disabilities if possible?

Some background; I'm reading this book 'No Pity' for a class. I have not
finished the book but in the first chapter there are some claims I disagree
with. I feel ablest for holding these views but they seem to be right to me.…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9pyz7/cmv_we_should_cure_disabilities_if_we_can_despite/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9pyz7/cmv_we_should_cure_disabilities_if_we_can_despite/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 01:00:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TLDR; Why shouldn&amp;#39;t we try to cure preventable disabilities if possible?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some background; I&amp;#39;m reading this book &amp;#39;No Pity&amp;#39; for a class. I have not finished the book but in the first chapter there are some claims I disagree with. I feel ablest for holding these views but they seem to be right to me. So here I am. I have my degree in philosophy and I&amp;#39;m fairly progressive so I feel I am open to opposing view points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The disabled as a minority group are very interesting because they are the only minority group that anyone can join and virtually any time. For very many people it is inevitable as they climb into old age. So when thinking of the plights of this minority group one must understand this can be them tomorrow if not with in 10, 20, or even 30 years from now. They could be your children or eventually your parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it were a possibility wouldn’t you want to prevent any and all of these people, including yourself, from these conditions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cannot help but to see it as a necessarily better condition to be in an able body than a disabled one. Ignoring this count I really don&amp;#39;t think I hold any other prejudices against any disabled person. I do not judge anyone by their disability. I think part of the government&amp;#39;s job is to account for the differences in the biological lottery. Thus it’s part of the government&amp;#39;s job to provide services for the disabled so they can live as independently as possible. Just the same as the government does for low income individuals. It’s all a part of the social safety net. The disabled population has a lot of untapped skills and talent because of people&amp;#39;s prejudices and that is a shame. A disabled person doesn&amp;#39;t have to be Steven Hawking to have a positive influence on the culture and society. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to my point; In the book people are quoted saying to the effect that if a miracle cure was developed overnight would they take it? And all of them say no. This way I can understand your whole experience and identity is wrapped up in your material experience. Of course you don&amp;#39;t want to change who you are. Change is hard and who says this change is necessarily worth it if you have your life together already. Being able to see or walk or hear wouldn&amp;#39;t necessarily make you a ‘better’ person. If anything, being abled will serve to alienate you from your community. As much as I don&amp;#39;t agree, I can respect this opinion and understand that my opinion really is meaningless to this point. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I am having a really hard time understanding is this; “Most stunning was the finding announced in 1992 of the precise DNA location of the gene that caused myotonic dystrophy. Yet, once again, these breakthroughs were not cures so much as prevention measures. And to the new disability rights movement prevention had ominous overtones. Many activists fear that with the growth of such predictive tests, pregnant women will be expected or coerced to abort fetuses when there is an indication of disability. Others worry that if genetic engineering can one day wipe out an illness, a person who already has that disability will be seen as a freak or devalued as a preventable mistake.” I understand wanting to prevent social stigma that is always a fight worth having. But if we can make it so no one ever has to deal with a particular disability again then why not do preventable treatments with genetic engineering? For example if we find a miracle cure for mental retardation then why not utilize it? On the note of abortions I think that it is the women’s choice. She should not be convinced of a decision; she should make the choice herself. No one can tell anyone what to do with their bodies plain and simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please convince me otherwise if you can. I am very interested to see some opposing arguments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: we should raise the minimum age to engage in sex work to 21.]]></title><description><![CDATA[While I am perfectly fine with 18 being the age of consent in general, I think
the minimum age to engage in the sex work economy (e.g., stripping, porn, etc.)
should be 21. I know many people will say, "well, like it or not, you're an
adult at 18." But we've determined as a society, in the US at…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9twgc/cmv_we_should_raise_the_minimum_age_to_engage_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9twgc/cmv_we_should_raise_the_minimum_age_to_engage_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 23:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;While I am perfectly fine with 18 being the age of consent in general, I think the minimum age to engage in the sex work economy (e.g., stripping, porn, etc.) should be 21. I know many people will say, &amp;quot;well, like it or not, you&amp;#39;re an adult at 18.&amp;quot; But we&amp;#39;ve determined as a society, in the US at least, that some adults (i.e., those under 21) cannot consume alcohol or cannabis (and even tobacco now in many places); thus, we already have exceptions when it comes to liberties one enjoys at age 18. This isn&amp;#39;t without precedent. And just so it&amp;#39;s explicit, I think this should apply to all genders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am making this argument for three main reasons. First, on a societal level, I think having 18 and 19 year olds in the sex work industry promotes ephebophilia in our culture (think about the popularity of the search term &amp;quot;teen&amp;quot; across many porn platforms...). Raising the age to 21 would at least reduce this widespread fantasy of someone &amp;quot;fresh out of high school.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second reason is that I think raising the minimum age of workers could help mitigate some of the coercion and predatory practices that can unfortunately co-occur in the industry (e.g., what was shown in Hot Girls Wanted). I think as people get older, especially after working a job or two, they tend to get a better sense of their self-worth, both as an individual and as a worker. Again, I know this would not eliminate bad actors in the industry, but I do think raising the average age of workers would act as a buffer to some of the more unsavory practices that can accompany sex work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, and somewhat related to the point above, I honestly think many people are not mature enough to make a potentially life-altering career decision at such a young age as 18. Based on personal experience being acquainted with people who have done some form of sex work (mostly stripping) and interviews with some pornstars/escorts I have seen, it strikes me that some people are cut out for it and some people are simply not. And, sadly, I think it can lead to a lot of regret and pain if you get too deep into it before knowing you&amp;#39;re not the type of person who can engage in the act of trading some sort of sexual service for money. Not to mention the fallout from doing (and later regretting) something like porn where there is a potentially permanent electronic record of your work. The short but developmentally critical transition period from adolescence to young adulthood (i.e., 18-21) should be about exploring your sexuality on your own personal terms before deciding you want to monetize and make a career of it for a while. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see that people may think this comes off as too paternalistic or sex-negative. Maybe it is, but again, we already do this in varying degrees in other domains in our society, so I&amp;#39;m not sure why this should be any different. I suppose you could change my view by presenting me some data to suggest that this would be impossible/ineffective or by enlightening me about some aspect or nuance of sex work that I&amp;#39;m ignoring or misunderstanding (insight from people who have worked in the industry would be especially welcome).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change my view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: You can't be offended on behalf of another race, for what someone of that race says about that particular race.]]></title><description><![CDATA[For perspective. I am half chinese/half white. My mom is 100% Chinese, born in
Hong Kong. My fiancee is 100% white (for lack of a better term).

We were all playing golf and saw an older Asian couple playing a second round.
The course attendant asked if they paid for a second round. They said…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9pqhm/cmv_you_cant_be_offended_on_behalf_of_another/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9pqhm/cmv_you_cant_be_offended_on_behalf_of_another/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 21:30:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For perspective.  I am half chinese/half white.  My mom is 100% Chinese, born in Hong Kong.  My fiancee is 100% white (for lack of a better term).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were all playing golf and saw an older Asian couple playing a second round.  The course attendant asked if they paid for a second round.  They said they didn&amp;#39;t think they needed to since no one else was using the course and already paid once.  He said they can&amp;#39;t do that, they paid for 1 round and only 1 round.  They were free to play again, they would just have to pay for another round.  I would think once you got caught, you&amp;#39;d say &amp;quot;my bad&amp;quot; and leave the course, but apparently the guy had to keep explaining why they can&amp;#39;t play for free just because there&amp;#39;s no one behind them.  They were still talking by the time we got to our car and pulling out like 5 minutes later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mom said something along the lines of &amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s such a Chinese thing to do&amp;quot;.  My fiancee said we can&amp;#39;t say things like that, because it personally offends her.  I&amp;#39;m confused how someone of an unrelated race can be personally offended on behalf of another race for something said within that race.  I&amp;#39;d like to hear your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the record, I&amp;#39;ve also played extra holes at a course.  But you do that in the middle like holes 5-7.  And if I got talked to about it, I&amp;#39;d take the rightful blame, say I was in the wrong, and leave.  I&amp;#39;d never start at hole #1 like this couple did, that&amp;#39;s just asking to be talked to by the staff.  It&amp;#39;s also very obvious when last tee time is 7-730pm, and this couple is starting at hole #1 at like 8:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:  I said it below in another comment and after seeing what people said I should have used &amp;quot;shouldn&amp;#39;t be offended&amp;quot; instead of &amp;quot;can&amp;#39;t be offended&amp;quot;.  And again that&amp;#39;s my opinion/view.  But anyone can be offended about anything, that&amp;#39;s their right.  Whether any change comes of it once that opinion if brought up is another story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still think it would be out of place for me to have a stance that I would tell someone of a different race/gender what they can/can&amp;#39;t say about that particular race/gender that I&amp;#39;ve never been associated with or been a part of.  Especially when that statement is not intentionally derogatory, or mean spirited, more of &amp;quot;yup, that doesn&amp;#39;t surprise me, based on my personal experiences of being part of that group&amp;quot;.  I wouldn&amp;#39;t tell a black person what it means to other black people when certain things are said, like I wouldn&amp;#39;t tell someone that identifies as a woman that they can/can&amp;#39;t say things about other woman since I don&amp;#39;t know how it feels to be in that particular group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Claiming to hear/see a deity is part of an illness]]></title><description><![CDATA[People who claim to have heard a deity speak to them, or who have claimed to see
one, have hallucinations. The definition of hallucination is "a sensory
experience that appears real, but is created by the mind". - paraphrased from
Healthline. This is often a symptom of several illnesses, so we can…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9nj29/cmv_claiming_to_hearsee_a_deity_is_part_of_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9nj29/cmv_claiming_to_hearsee_a_deity_is_part_of_an/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:33:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who claim to have heard a deity speak to them, or who have claimed to see one, have hallucinations. The definition of hallucination is &amp;quot;a sensory experience that appears real, but is created by the mind&amp;quot;. - paraphrased from Healthline. This is often a symptom of several illnesses, so we can conclude that the person who claims to see/hear a deity has an illness, because nobody else can perceive what the other hears/sees. I think that claiming to see/hear a deity has no basis in reality, whatsoever, can potentially cause the person to do dangerous things and is very strange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I perfectly accept that it is not in their control, and it is perfectly OK to have an illness, whether that be of mind or body, but why isn&amp;#39;t people claiming to see/hear deities viewed as an illness by doctors? Serious question. Any attempts to change my view, &lt;strong&gt;especially&lt;/strong&gt; from anybody working in the medical field will be greatly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: In the long run, I believe outright banning racist jokes will do more harm than good for groups who are the targets of such jokes.]]></title><description><![CDATA[As a fan of various politically incorrect comedians, I don't think they are
racist beyond their complete ignorance of the line that divides jokes between
what is a little on the nose and what is more racist than humerous. I can see
some potential harm stemming from this type content in the form of a…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9p52f/cmv_in_the_long_run_i_believe_outright_banning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9p52f/cmv_in_the_long_run_i_believe_outright_banning/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:33:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a fan of various politically incorrect comedians, I don&amp;#39;t think they are racist beyond their complete ignorance of the line that divides jokes between what is a little on the nose and what is more racist than humerous. I can see some potential harm stemming from this type content in the form of a small percentage of their audiences who not only get enjoyment from reinforcing racial stereotypes but use it as an excuse to negatively discriminate or harm minorities. But in the long run I don&amp;#39;t see how pushing the comedic no go zone further and further towards what is politically correct is the most beneficial option. Ignorant people are everywhere, and trying to force society into a utopian world free of racism is a pipe dream which may only exacerbate racial issues. I think this type of racially stereotypical comedy gives these small minded people an opportunity to vent their prejudices openly for others to criticize rather than in a manner that is much more organized, insidious and underground. This type of comedy is the lesser of two evils, resulting in I believe nothing more than some hurt feelings and oftentimes bad comedy, whereas removing such an avenue may result in something similar to the beer halls of 20th century Germany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The argument shouldn't be that the draft/selective service in the US is sexist the argument should be that they are outdated and shouldn't exist at all. And most people who flip out about the draft wouldn't be drafted anyway.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am saying this as a woman who was in the military. I've thought about this for
a while so I would like to see how my argument can be challenged and if possibly
I am not looking at this the right way or haven't taken something into
consideration.

The draft should be entirely abolished it's not…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9n36h/cmv_the_argument_shouldnt_be_that_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9n36h/cmv_the_argument_shouldnt_be_that_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:33:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am saying this as a woman who was in the military. I&amp;#39;ve thought about this for a while so I would like to see how my argument can be challenged and if possibly I am not looking at this the right way or haven&amp;#39;t taken something into consideration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The draft should be entirely abolished it&amp;#39;s not needed, it&amp;#39;s outdated, and it isn&amp;#39;t a working model in the US military. The military doesn&amp;#39;t even want to have to use the draft. It&amp;#39;s a shit institution that doesn&amp;#39;t work in the US. Compulsory service works in other countries but not ours. My reasonings are as followed with supporting links or as many as I could find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sss.gov/history-and-records/induction-statistics/&quot;&gt;They&amp;#39;ve statistically used it less each time&lt;/a&gt; during ww1 over 50% were draftees. By Vietnam era, it was less than 30% across all four branches and less than 20% of the draftees were sent to combat or hot zones.  Culminating in only 676 individuals being drafted in 1973. Little historical fact we even drafted people on both sides during the civil war. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.) Vietnam gave rise to the professional or career soldier, we have one of the strongest volunteer forces in the world. The military is not hurting for people they turn people away every day and give out pink slips to people who are in Military Occupations that are overcrowded or phases out because it&amp;#39;s obsolete. Example of this would be barbers, yes king of the hill was accurate on that they did once exist. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wearethemighty.com/articles/6-awesome-army-jobs-that-no-longer-exist/&quot;&gt;List of six jobs (though there are more) that no longer exist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s easier to be disqualified than qualified for service and women on average are more qualified than men. Which is just one of the reasons that they opened up the combat arms military occupational specialties to women to broaden the pool from which they can recruit. There are several factors of why this is but, &lt;a href=&quot;https://militarybenefits.info/army-height-weight-requirements/&quot;&gt;weight and height&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.military.com/join-armed-forces/disqualifiers-medical-conditions.html&quot;&gt;general health&lt;/a&gt;, less likely to have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thebalancecareers.com/us-military-enlistment-standards-3354006&quot;&gt;criminal record&lt;/a&gt;, better scores on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.military.com/join-armed-forces/asvab/asvab-test-explained.html&quot;&gt;ASVAB (armed service aptitude battery test)&lt;/a&gt;, etc to name a few. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3.) Draftees are bad for &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unit_cohesion#:%7E:text=Unit%20cohesion%20is%20a%20military,despite%20combat%20or%20mission%20stress%22.&quot;&gt;unit cohesion (may not seem important but it is a very important component for a functioning military)&lt;/a&gt; and the emotional health of those around them. They also can be extremely dangerous and end up getting themselves or someone else killed. We learned this during Vietnam. They tend to be undisciplined, unmotivated, poorly trained because it&amp;#39;s about quantity not quality ,and let&amp;#39;s add-in you&amp;#39;re taking people who don&amp;#39;t want to be somewhere training them to kill, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iza.org/publications/dp/5172/drawn-into-violence-evidence-on-what-makes-a-criminal-from-the-vietnam-draft-lotteries&quot;&gt;then handing them a loaded weapon&lt;/a&gt;. What could go wrong? Look up friendly fire and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.historynet.com/the-hard-truth-about-fragging.htm&quot;&gt;fragging incidents&lt;/a&gt; that happened during Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.) The US military has backups with more backups in place to avoid using the draft at all costs. Everyone that signs an enlistment contract agrees to double time. For example, you sign a four-year contract with the US Army to be a 13b (cannon crew member in field artillery) what you owe them is 8 years. 4 years active, and upon release of service you owe 4 more years in the IRR or inactive ready reserve. During which time you can be recalled to active duty. Some specialized jobs allow up to 10 years. It&amp;#39;s cheaper, cost and time effective to bring back people who already have been trained and just give them a refresher course versus the time and money it takes to train a new recruit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If in the event another 9/11 happened they would &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A.) first recall all IRR at any given time that&amp;#39;s over a million people at any given time that fall within the window. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;B.) The next step they would take is lowering the standards for entrance. In point 2 I mentioned it&amp;#39;s difficult well now all those people that would ordinarily be turned away for hand tattoos, face tattoos, low scores on the ASVAB, that person that had therapy one time as a kid, that individual that had a bit of a criminal record, etc are now being taken. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.) They activate the National Guard of each state and the Reservists of each branch placing them on active duty orders. (We have tons of these).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;D.) Stop loss is initatied any service members contracts that were about to expire are now extended preventing force loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;E.) And if all of that fails to provide enough then and only then is the draft activated by Congress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there is a catch, if you&amp;#39;re overweight, have a history of mental illness, health problems, too short, under 18, in your mid-30s, in college, can&amp;#39;t meet even the lowered standard on the ASVAB which shows you are cannot be  trained (not joking there are people that try on this test and want to be in who score below the minimum 31 out of 99 there are people who score in the single digits), that ASVAB you took in high school already let them know of you were qualified or not so if you bombed it your name wouldn&amp;#39;t even be up for consideration of the draft board, a single parent and you have full custody of your kid, you&amp;#39;re not going to get drafted. As it stands right now with no draft and no lowered standard males of 18-34(?) only 49% of the them are deemed fit for service. Females the numbers are at 51% is qualified. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5.) We don&amp;#39;t fight the way we used to fight, warfare has evolved we aren&amp;#39;t just throwing body after body at targets. &lt;a href=&quot;https://ciaotest.cc.columbia.edu/olj/sa/sa_99anv02.html&quot;&gt;We use technology&lt;/a&gt; that has allowed us to go from 2.7 million during the height of the Vietnam War to 1.4 million with us fighting on two fronts. Technology has cut the need in half because we are able to use it as a force multiplier vs using actual physical bodies. Not to mention all the other operations that take place every day that the general public is unaware of. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;6.) Draftees legally are only required to serve a year deployed. Ie one tour, it costs more money using the draft because they have to get a fresh batch in every year as opposed to regular volunteer enlisted members who they can use what&amp;#39;s called stop-loss where they involuntarily extend the service members contract. It costs approximately $90,000 to train and equip one infantryman in the military and their training is only 22 weeks un the Army. That&amp;#39;s just through training, now imagine that plus not to mention the wasted money and man-hours spent chasing down draft dodgers. The draft is not cheap nor is it a sustainable model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The draft is not needed, it&amp;#39;s outdated, ineffective, and the military DOES NOT want draftees there because historically they cause more problems and are a hindrance. It shouldn&amp;#39;t include women it should be completely abolished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: There has never been a better time in human history to be alive.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s not strange to think the world is a horrible place. That's all you see in
the new, on social media and especially on Reddit . My view is that there has
never ever been a better time to be alive. For anyone, anywhere.

 * Food has never been more plentiful, despite increasing populations.…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9gikx/cmv_there_has_never_been_a_better_time_in_human/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9gikx/cmv_there_has_never_been_a_better_time_in_human/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 14:33:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not strange to think the world is a horrible place. That&amp;#39;s all you see in the new, on social media and especially on Reddit . My view is that there has never ever been a better time to be alive. For anyone, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food has never been more plentiful, despite increasing populations. Almost every key resources are plentiful despite record populations. The share of income spent on food has steeply declined as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A higher percentage of children make it through childhood today than ever before.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to knowledge has never been easier, and cheaper.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Air quality world wide has never been better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Global poverty is at an all time low. Child labor world wide is on a steep decline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Global literacy rate is at an all time high.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal freedom is most countries is also at an all time high.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standards of living in almost every country has drastically increased. In developed countries, you have access to news, entertainment, food, flights, games at the press of a few buttons.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medicine.&lt;/strong&gt; I don&amp;#39;t think anyone needs convincing how much better modern medicine has made the world.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s never been more accessible for the average person to start a business or make money from personal projects or creative works, eg on Youtube, Instagrams or small online stores. Small side gigs have never been so profitable and accessible (Uber, DoorDash etc) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has been been more possibilities available to the average person on Earth. And more people than ever before have access to this level of leisure time.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And most importantly, technological innovations are on the rise, promising even better medicine, education and living standards in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Social media companies are trying to manipulate and distract us from real issues in the world.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Often you'll see some great outrage sweep across tiktok or twitter, and a lot of
it seems fine upon first glance, but a lot of it is just fluff that doesn't hold
up to scrutiny and isn't really a new issue, just a variant of a different
issue, but the secret sauce is to just call people a bigot of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9a9dy/cmv_social_media_companies_are_trying_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9a9dy/cmv_social_media_companies_are_trying_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 05:30:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often you&amp;#39;ll see some great outrage sweep across tiktok or twitter, and a lot of it seems fine upon first glance, but a lot of it is just fluff that doesn&amp;#39;t hold up to scrutiny and isn&amp;#39;t really a new issue, just a variant of a different issue, but the secret sauce is to just call people a bigot of some kind when they argue against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time there&amp;#39;s a fresh outrage we get more bans, more restrictions and more of a political divide between groups of people, the platforms control you a little more and everyone distracts each other with congratulations on an outrage well done. Meanwhile the big boys up top continue to seize more and more control without us ever really noticing. They don&amp;#39;t care one bit about your politics or your feelings, they just see an opportunity to exploit this current political environment to seize control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have no clue how these algorithms work and they&amp;#39;re starting to get pretty spooky. I believe we&amp;#39;re perched in a very precarious state right now with no clear out. It&amp;#39;s impossible to trust anything because you really never know why you&amp;#39;re being shown something and you don&amp;#39;t know where it originated from. Especially on TikTok, we truly have no idea what TikTok does, it&amp;#39;s completely opaque and hails straight from China. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How could you not take advantage of such a perfect situation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Uber is an unethical company, and should be avoided]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1. They severely undercut prices to put taxi companies out of business so that
    they can have a monopoly on the market, and eventually increase fares and
    cut wages for their employees
 2. They regularly oppose legislation that would force them to provide their
    full time drivers with…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9780j/cmv_uber_is_an_unethical_company_and_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o9780j/cmv_uber_is_an_unethical_company_and_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 02:07:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They severely undercut prices to put taxi companies out of business so that they can have a monopoly on the market, and eventually increase fares and cut wages for their employees &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They regularly oppose legislation that would force them to provide their full time drivers with health insurance and other essentials that come with full time jobs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They underpay their employees &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on these 3 facts, Uber is an unethical company and goes beyond the pursuit to acquire customers, but this company is actively harming the livelihoods of employees that work with them and will eventually hurt customers as they gradually start to increase fares&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The term African-American is racist and is actively segregating black people from white people and others.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am not American.

For the longest time I have believed that the term African-American is racist
for the following reasons:

 1. It lumps all black people into the same category as being African. The
    person being referred to as African may be from Trinidad and Tobago,
    Barbados, Jamaica, the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o91yx1/cmv_the_term_africanamerican_is_racist_and_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o91yx1/cmv_the_term_africanamerican_is_racist_and_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 19:35:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not American.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the longest time I have believed that the term African-American is racist for the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It lumps all black people into the same category as being African. The person being referred to as African may be from Trinidad and Tobago, Barbados, Jamaica, the Solomon Islands etc., or their grandparents or great-grandparents were from there. They may have no closer ancestry to any area in Africa than a white American with English ancestry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term becomes useless as soon as the person is in America but not American. Then what are they called? Black. So I don’t see the point in calling someone African-American instead of black when the next black person who isn’t American you have to use a term for, you call them black anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It segregates different colours for absolutely no reason and is totally unnecessary. What do they call a black German person? Do they call them African-German? No, they’re just German. They’re as German as anyone else. Calling someone African-American instead of just American suggests that they’re not the same as a white American, which they are. They’re born in the United States or are naturalised, they might never have been to Africa in their lives and have no African relatives, so they’re not African-American, they’re just American. Otherwise any white American needs to be referred to as English-American or Irish-American or Slovakian-American, instead of being categorised as white.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s a more polite way of saying someone is black, or a categorisation or any other use of the term, it just seems racist to me to call someone ‘African’ because they’re black regardless of what their background or heritage is, and no other country I can think of categorises their black citizens or any other BAME people as ‘African’ or ‘Asian’ or anything else. Germans are Germans, Australians are Australians, Americans should be Americans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: I think it’s wrong to expect homeless people to take food being offered to them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let me start out by saying, it really bothers me when I see people “helping” the
homeless by offering their half eating food and then getting sad and confused on
why the homeless man didn’t take their food.

I’ve never been homeless nor poor, I’m upper middle class. However, I never look
down on the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o91m9c/cmv_i_think_its_wrong_to_expect_homeless_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o91m9c/cmv_i_think_its_wrong_to_expect_homeless_people/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 18:30:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me start out by saying, it really bothers me when I see people “helping” the homeless by offering their half eating food and then getting sad and confused on why the homeless man didn’t take their food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been homeless nor poor, I’m upper middle class. However, I never look down on the homeless and give them money instead of outright giving food to them. I feel the only people who get butthurt are those who offer food just to boost their ego. If I were homeless, I’d never take someone’s half eaten food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see so many posts saying “I only ever offer food because the money will go to drugs”. That’s not why you’re not giving money…I’m sick of people bullshitting with that excuse to not give money. Besides, don’t people ever think that maybe the homeless guy just ate? Or he can’t carry 100 McDonald’s sandwiches that people offer him? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because he turns down your food that you thought was gourmet, doesn’t mean he’s a choosy beggar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I think it’s perfectly fine to give someone food if they ask for it. What I have a problem with is the people who go up to homeless offering their leftovers, then getting angry when the homeless guy turns the food down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: What I mean by leftovers is half eaten food/spoiled food&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: It's better to be an athiest than someone who is religious in name only]]></title><description><![CDATA[For perspective, this is coming from someone who is religious.

I'm trying to improve myself and follow the teachings of my religion, but it
seems like some people don't even TRY to follow the teachings of the religion
that they claim to be a part of. They don't attend religious services often…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o8r4ar/cmv_its_better_to_be_an_athiest_than_someone_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o8r4ar/cmv_its_better_to_be_an_athiest_than_someone_who/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 15:46:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For perspective, this is coming from someone who is religious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m trying to improve myself and follow the teachings of my religion, but it seems like some people don&amp;#39;t even TRY to follow the teachings of the religion that they claim to be a part of. They don&amp;#39;t attend religious services often when it is expected of them, break many commandments that their religion has and so on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I realize that the teachings of many religions talk about being accepting of those who are trying to improve themselves and to not be too judgmental of those who choose to &amp;quot;sin&amp;quot;, but there has to be a point where the  religious devotions they do offer every once in a while could be seen as mocking in a way towards the higher power they profess to believe in and worship, but they spend MUCH more time thinking of the next one night stand, cookout, night out with their friends binge drinking, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would think that they would be more comfortable embracing a belief system that excludes a higher power and religious devotion so they don&amp;#39;t feel like they&amp;#39;re stuck in a devotion system that they aren&amp;#39;t truly involved with. You&amp;#39;re outwardly expressing the beliefs you have on the inside of yourself. Sure, you may disappoint friends and family you have who are religious, but it beats the inner turmoil of being in a part of a belief system you begrudgingly accept for one reason or another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: The concept of non-binary genders is harmful to how gender is viewed.]]></title><description><![CDATA[If someone decides their gender identity doesn’t correlate with their assigned
sex, they are assuming that cisgender people HAVE to follow the stereotypes
according to their birth sex. For example, if an individual who is female by sex
decides they are non-binary, they are compartmentalizing the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o8oarr/cmv_the_concept_of_nonbinary_genders_is_harmful/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o8oarr/cmv_the_concept_of_nonbinary_genders_is_harmful/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 13:30:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone decides their gender identity doesn’t correlate with their assigned sex, they are assuming that cisgender people HAVE to follow the stereotypes according to their birth sex. For example, if an individual who is female by sex decides they are non-binary, they are compartmentalizing the definition of a woman. What does it mean to be a woman? Dresses and makeup? If you said yes to the previous question, you are stereotyping. Not all women wear dresses, not all women wear makeup, not all women have vaginas, and not all women “feel” like women. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened to having pride in being a woman, even if you don’t follow the stereotype? Even if you prefer a boyish haircut and a “not-so-feminine” voice and plaid button-ups, you can have pride in being part of the diversity of women. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand that non-binary is a liberation of the self and breaking free from society’s definitions of man and woman, but removing yourself from your gender label emphasizes that men and women must follow their conventional roles, making the situation even worse. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would rather live in a world where being called he or she doesn’t connotate stereotypes than in a world where a myriad of pronoun possibilities nuance the non-women and non-man qualities and force harsher stereotypes on those who are called he or she. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** I would like to clarify that I am discussing non-binary genders. Transgender (ftm or mtf) is something else since they are not alienating their assigned sex/gender because they don’t feel “manly” enough to be male; they identify with the other gender because they identify with the other gender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: Diversity quotas are not the best way to tackle under representation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi reddit,

Let me be clear from the beginning. I think that anyone who is against fairness
or equal chances should significantly rethink their life philosophy. Being
discriminated based on gender / race / etc is horrible and we should do
everything in our power to change that.

Now, from what I…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o8c7rx/cmv_diversity_quotas_are_not_the_best_way_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/o8c7rx/cmv_diversity_quotas_are_not_the_best_way_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi reddit,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me be clear from the beginning. I think that anyone who is against fairness or equal chances should significantly rethink their life philosophy. Being discriminated based on gender / race / etc is horrible and we should do everything in our power to change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, from what I notice, the number one initiative to tackles this issue is to impose a diversity quota. You all see this : we commit to have 50% of our board members females, or x% of our workforce latino, etc (depends on the geography as well).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My assumption is that this strategy is to “force” change, by setting these targets. In essence, any organization with such a target needs to do everything in their power to change the way they recruit and promote talent to reach that target.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also assume this kind of initiatives happen mostly in highly skilled white collar workforce organizations. I don’t see anyone advocating we increase the % of men as hairdressers, % of women as bricklayers, % of blacks in sports, or even ridiculous things like a quotas for prisons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, I think that these type of policies have the opposite effect than intended. What happens is that companies blindly promote and recruit based on diversity rather than best talent. This leads to more conflict as we are creating environments where employees feel treated unfair since whatever population is underrepresented is privileged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are we not rather focusing on creating equal chances? Blind CVs, better maternity/paternity rules, inclusion trainings, etc. If we treat the process fair, why care if the result is 70%women- 30%men , or whatever you want to measure?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very curious what you have to say!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Really interesting conversations! Thanks for the people who took their time to answer. While I do think a lot of the comments are going off topic, I definitely learned more about this issue. In reading more about the topic, I came across some interesting materials. Have a look if you are interested:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/business/2018/02/17/ten-years-on-from-norways-quota-for-women-on-corporate-boards&quot;&gt;https://www.economist.com/business/2018/02/17/ten-years-on-from-norways-quota-for-women-on-corporate-boards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IIb3uyTPrk8&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IIb3uyTPrk8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gender-equality_paradox&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gender-equality_paradox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still not convinced that gender quotas is the right way to go forward, and do believe that there are unintended consequences. However, I am optimistic for the future and hope all of us who feel under represented will see better days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>