<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 20:47:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[TRUMP SUPPORTERS WHO OVERRAN CAPITOL FACE TEN YEARS IN PRISON THANKS TO BLM RIOT ERA TRUMP EXECUTIVE ORDER TO PROTECT STATUES #]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347761131549585411</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347761131549585411</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 20:41:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>TRUMP SUPPORTERS WHO OVERRAN CAPITOL FACE TEN YEARS IN PRISON THANKS TO BLM RIOT ERA TRUMP EXECUTIVE ORDER TO PROTECT STATUES #</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TSLA to the fucking moon]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktsl2i/tsla_to_the_fucking_moon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktsl2i/tsla_to_the_fucking_moon/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 20:41:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why We Are at the Major Late-Stage Bubble, Possibly the Biggest in History]]></title><description><![CDATA[Before I begin, I came across this article written by Jeremey Grantham, who is a
British investor and co-founder and chief investment strategist of GMO, also
regarded as a highly knowledgeable investor particularly due to his prediction
of various historic stock market bubbles.

In his article…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktu07v/why_we_are_at_the_major_latestage_bubble_possibly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktu07v/why_we_are_at_the_major_latestage_bubble_possibly/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 20:41:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I begin, I came across this article written by Jeremey Grantham, who is a British investor and co-founder and chief investment strategist of GMO, also regarded as a highly knowledgeable investor particularly due to his prediction of various historic stock market bubbles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his article titled &amp;quot;Waiting for the Last Dance&amp;quot;, he outlines multiple points why he thinks we are in a major late-stage bubble. I will summarize below the key points discussed, but will also leave a link to the article in case you want to read the full version.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gmo.com/americas/research-library/waiting-for-the-last-dance/&quot;&gt;https://www.gmo.com/americas/research-library/waiting-for-the-last-dance/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The long, long bull market since 2009 has finally matured into a fully-fledged epic bubble, and he believes this event will be recorded as one of the great bubbles of financial history along with the South Sea bubble, 1929, and 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The single most dependable feature of the late stages of the great bubbles of history has been really crazy investor behaviour, especially on the part of individuals. For the first 10 years of this bull market, we lacked such wild speculation. But now we have it. (he provides examples such as Hertz, K*d*k, Nikola, and especially, Tesla)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The &amp;quot;Buffett indicator,&amp;quot; total stock market capitalization to GDP, broke through its all-time-high 2000 record. In 2020, there were 480 IPOs (including an incredible 248 SPACs) – more new listings than the 406 IPOs in 2000. There are 150 non-micro-cap companies (market cap of over $250 million) that have more than tripled in the year, which is over 3 times as many as any year in the previous decade. The volume of small retail purchases, of less than 10 contracts, of call options on U.S. equities has increased 8-fold compared to 2019, and 2019 was already well above long-run average.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- This time, more than in any previous bubble, investors are relying on accommodative monetary conditions and zero real rates extrapolated indefinitely ... Now once again the high prices this time will hold because…interest rates will be kept around nil forever, in the ultimate statement of moral hazard – the asymmetrical market risk we have come to know and depend on. The mantra of late 2020 was that engineered low rates can prevent a decline in asset prices. Forever! But of course, it was a fallacy in 2000 and it is a fallacy now. In the end, moral hazard did not stop the Tech bubble decline, with the NASDAQ falling 82%. Yes, 82%!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Nothing in investing perfectly repeats. Certainly not investment bubbles. Each form of irrational exuberance is different; we are just looking for what you might call spiritual similarities. Even now, I know that this market can soar upwards for a few more weeks or even months – it feels like we could be anywhere between July 1999 and February 2000. Which is to say it is entitled to break any day, having checked all the boxes, but could keep roaring upwards for a few months longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- My best guess as to the longest this bubble might survive is the late spring or early summer, coinciding with the broad rollout of the COVID vaccine. At that moment, the most pressing issue facing the world economy will have been solved. Market participants will breathe a sigh of relief, look around, and immediately realize that the economy is still in poor shape, stimulus will shortly be cut back with the end of the COVID crisis, and valuations are absurd. “Buy the rumor, sell the news.” But remember that timing the bursting of bubbles has a long history of disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Even with hindsight, it is seldom easy to point to the pin that burst the bubble. The main reason for this lack of clarity is that the great bull markets did not break when they were presented with a major unexpected negative. The great bull markets typically turn down when the market conditions are very favorable, just subtly less favorable than they were yesterday. And that is why they are always missed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The combination of timing uncertainty and rapidly accelerating regret on the part of clients means that the career and business risk of fighting the bubble is too great for large commercial enterprises. So, don&amp;#39;t wait for the Goldmans and Morgan Stanleys to become bearish: it can never happen. For them it is a horribly non-commercial bet. Perhaps it is for anyone. Profitable and risk-reducing for the clients, yes, but commercially impractical for advisors. Their best policy is clear and simple: always be extremely bullish. It is good for business and intellectually undemanding. It is appealing to most investors who much prefer optimism to realistic appraisal, as witnessed so vividly with COVID. And when it all ends, you will as a persistent bull have overwhelming company. This is why you have always had bullish advice in a bubble and always will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested to see more of his arguments, I strongly advise you to go and read the full article. I am currently 100% on equities, and very bullish for stocks as all of you probably are. But I think it&amp;#39;s also important to have a balanced perspective, especially when everyone around you is extremely bullish. Ultimately, we are investing for the long run for our retirement. Everyone is a fucking genius in a bull market, and I think a lot of people in the sub, whether a newcomer or an experienced investor, should listen to bearish predictions and advices and not become a victim of confirmation bias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pesticide believed to kill bees is authorised for use in England]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25701144</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25701144</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 20:41:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Capitol Attack Doesn’t Justify Expanding Surveillance]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25701999</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25701999</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 20:06:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senator Lindsey Graham urges Congress to repeal Section 230.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Copied text from Facebook

“Twitter may ban me for this but I willingly accept that fate: Your decision to
permanently ban President Trump is a serious mistake.

The Ayatollah can tweet, but Trump can’t! Says a lot about the people who run
Twitter.

I’m more determined than ever to strip Section 230…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktsiqg/senator_lindsey_graham_urges_congress_to_repeal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktsiqg/senator_lindsey_graham_urges_congress_to_repeal/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 19:02:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Copied text from Facebook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Twitter may ban me for this but I willingly accept that fate: Your decision to permanently ban President Trump is a serious mistake. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ayatollah can tweet, but Trump can’t! Says a lot about the people who run Twitter. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m more determined than ever to strip Section 230 protections from Big Tech (Twitter) that let them be immune from lawsuits. Big Tech are the only companies in America that virtually have absolute immunity from being sued for their actions, and it’s only because Congress gave them that protection. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is now time for Congress to repeal Section 230 and put Big Tech on the same legal footing as every other company in America. Legal accountability.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Akin's Laws of Spacecraft Design]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25698990</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25698990</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 19:02:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ask HN: Show me your half baked project]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25700135</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25700135</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 19:02:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gain porn for you degenerates. Go long!]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktducc/gain_porn_for_you_degenerates_go_long/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktducc/gain_porn_for_you_degenerates_go_long/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 18:20:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sriwijaya Air flight SJ182, a Boeing 737, has disappeared from radar]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25699338</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25699338</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 18:20:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1999 all over again?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Good afternoon

The current market has some obvious similarities with the internet bubble in the
2000s at the moment:

1) Sectoral bubble

Electric Vehicle stocks, Renewable energy stocks, crypto and possibly even
fintech stocks have skyrocketed to insane levels in 2020. A PE ratio of 100-200
for…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktslbf/1999_all_over_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktslbf/1999_all_over_again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current market has some obvious similarities with the internet bubble in the 2000s at the moment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Sectoral bubble&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electric Vehicle stocks, Renewable energy stocks, crypto and possibly even fintech stocks have skyrocketed to insane levels in 2020. A PE ratio of 100-200 for stocks in these sectors is considered &amp;quot;cheap&amp;quot; right now, that&amp;#39;s what &amp;quot;investors&amp;quot; before the dotcom crash thought aswell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Historic low interest rates&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the biggest catalyst for the creation of an insane bubble, very low interest rates. Just like in the 2000s, we currently have historic low interest rates, which makes stocks the only game in town. The big myth here is that people think stocks only go up, with interest rates close to 0. That&amp;#39;s absolutely not true and that&amp;#39;s the scary part in my opinion, because even professionals and analysts think that. The market doesn&amp;#39;t stay disconnected from the economy forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) IPO mania and speculation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We haven&amp;#39;t seen more IPO&amp;#39;s in 2020 since the dotcom bubble. This on itself isn&amp;#39;t a big deal, but the valuations these IPO&amp;#39;s get are beyond insanity. Any company that gets linked to EV in some way, automatically gets a 100%+ boost to their stock price, without even having a product or sales number. 1999 all over again?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) &amp;quot;New paradigm&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s be honest, at least 80% of the people in any financial subreddit (excluding WSB, +-99% there) thinks that Tesla is the new paradigm that will take over the world. Trust me, it is not. I&amp;#39;ve been doing some math on Tesla valuation, and I have no fitting word for its current valuation. I won&amp;#39;t go in the details why, because I could write a whole book about this. I still firmly believe that growing positive cashflows should be the main catalyst of a stock that goes up, and a company with a negative cashflow (THAT ONLY GROWS AT A 25% RATE) shouldn&amp;#39;t get a 1t valuation, that&amp;#39;s too disrespectful for companies such as Google, Microsoft, Amazon and Apple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Greed and FOMO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone wants to jump on this train, no one wants to miss out, but I can assure you, these valuations are absurd and those who can&amp;#39;t get out early enough, will be left holding the (empty) bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kind regards and stay safe (physically and financially)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here's a quick tour of WSB for the new kids.]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kt7guj/heres_a_quick_tour_of_wsb_for_the_new_kids/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kt7guj/heres_a_quick_tour_of_wsb_for_the_new_kids/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley Boosts Stake In MicroStrategy To 10.9%]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investment Bank Morgan Stanley has boosted its stake in MicroStrategy
[https://bitcoinmaximalist.net/morgan-stanley-boosts-stake-in-microstrategy-to-10-9/]
($MSTR) and now owns 10.9% of the Bitcoin rich company.

Bitcoin has been on a rip since March last year up over 800%, so what will it
take for…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktldld/morgan_stanley_boosts_stake_in_microstrategy_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktldld/morgan_stanley_boosts_stake_in_microstrategy_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investment Bank Morgan Stanley has &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmaximalist.net/morgan-stanley-boosts-stake-in-microstrategy-to-10-9/&quot;&gt;boosted its stake in MicroStrategy&lt;/a&gt; ($MSTR) and now owns 10.9% of the Bitcoin rich company. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin has been on a rip since March last year up over 800%, so what will it take for any doubters to come around?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TSLA 1103% gain. Never selling]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktr2op/tsla_1103_gain_never_selling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktr2op/tsla_1103_gain_never_selling/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ask HN: What are decentralized Twitter alternatives?]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25695682</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25695682</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 17:16:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jane Besos on her way to claim richest woman in the world and seducing Elon]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktpyym/jane_besos_on_her_way_to_claim_richest_woman_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktpyym/jane_besos_on_her_way_to_claim_richest_woman_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Michael Burry (‘Big Short’) Has Another Huge Short Position on $TSLA]]></title><description><![CDATA[(From Twitter)

“Well, my last Big Short got bigger and Bigger and BIGGER too....$TSLA $60
billion increase in market cap today alone...1 GM, 2 Hersheys, 3 Etsys, 4
Dominos, 10 Vornados...enjoy it while it lasts.”]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktne7q/michael_burry_big_short_has_another_huge_short/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktne7q/michael_burry_big_short_has_another_huge_short/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(From Twitter)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well, my last Big Short got bigger and Bigger and BIGGER too....$TSLA $60 billion increase in market cap today alone...1 GM, 2 Hersheys, 3 Etsys, 4 Dominos, 10 Vornados...enjoy it while it lasts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIO Partners with NVIDIA to Develop a New Generation of Automated Driving Electric Vehicles]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIO just did it, and so did NVIDIA!!

> At NIO Day, the company’s annual customer event, the EV maker revealed its
> NVIDIA DRIVE Orin-powered supercomputer, dubbed Adam, which will first appear
> in the ET7 sedan that will ship in China starting in 2022....
> 
> ... As the first of NIO’s EVs to…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktrnpo/nio_partners_with_nvidia_to_develop_a_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktrnpo/nio_partners_with_nvidia_to_develop_a_new/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NIO just did it, and so did NVIDIA!!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At NIO Day, the company’s annual customer event, the EV maker revealed its NVIDIA DRIVE Orin-powered supercomputer, dubbed Adam, which will first appear in the ET7 sedan that will ship in China starting in 2022....   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;... As the first of NIO’s EVs to feature Orin, the flagship ET7 is a high-performance vehicle that accelerates from zero to 100km in only 3.9 seconds. It also features a new 150kw battery for extended mileage range.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/01/09/2155851/0/en/NIO-Partners-with-NVIDIA-to-Develop-a-New-Generation-of-Automated-Driving-Electric-Vehicles.html&quot;&gt;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/01/09/2155851/0/en/NIO-Partners-with-NVIDIA-to-Develop-a-New-Generation-of-Automated-Driving-Electric-Vehicles.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What exactly happens when an stock market bubble "bursts".]]></title><description><![CDATA[With all of the talk floating around on pretty much any investing related
subreddit of the bubble that we are likely in, it is always mentioned that this
bubble will inevitably burst and it is always said that is coming soon. I am
somewhat new to investing and I don't understand what happens when it…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktou8n/what_exactly_happens_when_an_stock_market_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktou8n/what_exactly_happens_when_an_stock_market_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all of the talk floating around on pretty much any investing related subreddit of the bubble that we are likely in, it is always mentioned that this bubble will inevitably burst and it is always said that is coming soon. I am somewhat new to investing and I don&amp;#39;t understand what happens when it bursts. What drives the prices down so dramatically in almost the entire stock market? I understand that it is probably not as simple as one thing every time, but in history, what has been the causes and what could likely be the cause for our future bubble burst?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When Tesla hits $1,000]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktqy0k/when_tesla_hits_1000/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktqy0k/when_tesla_hits_1000/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Twitter suspends Sci-Hub account amid Indian court case]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25695357</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25695357</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 14:53:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ARKG or ARKK for long term gains?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m 24, I live in Arkansas. My expenses are very low (>$500 a month.) I make
about $3,500 a month and I am looking into these two ETFs for long term gains. I
have about $2000 that I plan on investing Monday, and I also plan to add to
these funds* consistently. Possibly a large portion of my monthly…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktmnxn/arkg_or_arkk_for_long_term_gains/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktmnxn/arkg_or_arkk_for_long_term_gains/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 14:30:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 24, I live in Arkansas. My expenses are very low (&amp;gt;$500 a month.) I make about $3,500 a month and I am looking into these two ETFs for long term gains. I have about $2000 that I plan on investing Monday, and I also plan to add to these funds* consistently. Possibly a large portion of my monthly income. Which of these two would you guys recommend?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Musk says "use Signal". People buy an unrelated stock.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/01/08/elon-musk-boosts-signal-app-signal-advance-stock-jumps-1100percent.html

Do you think only stupid people bought the stock by mistake or do you think some
people bought it anticipating that others will buy it by mistake? Either way,
isn't that proof that people…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktou84/musk_says_use_signal_people_buy_an_unrelated_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktou84/musk_says_use_signal_people_buy_an_unrelated_stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 12:48:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/01/08/elon-musk-boosts-signal-app-signal-advance-stock-jumps-1100percent.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/01/08/elon-musk-boosts-signal-app-signal-advance-stock-jumps-1100percent.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think only stupid people bought the stock by mistake or do you think some people bought it anticipating that others will buy it by mistake? Either way, isn&amp;#39;t that proof that people follow Musk blindly?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathie getting the respect she deserves. Love you Aunt Cathie♥️🚀]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktcmj0/cathie_getting_the_respect_she_deserves_love_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktcmj0/cathie_getting_the_respect_she_deserves_love_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 11:52:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop with the bubble nonsense. We are not in a bubble. Your dollars are just getting more and more worthless.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The argument is really simple and has been mentioned numerous times on this
subreddit.

There is no where else for money to flow to when interest rates are so low.
There is no where else for money to flow to when interest rates are so low.
There is no where else for money to flow to when interest…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kt6h3k/stop_with_the_bubble_nonsense_we_are_not_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kt6h3k/stop_with_the_bubble_nonsense_we_are_not_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 11:52:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The argument is really simple and has been mentioned numerous times on this subreddit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no where else for money to flow to when interest rates are so low. There is no where else for money to flow to when interest rates are so low. There is no where else for money to flow to when interest rates are so low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drill that into your peanut sized brain and everything will make sense to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Signal gaining popularity in India after WhatsApp policy changes]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25696842</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25696842</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 11:52:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ruby 3, Concurrency and the Ecosystem]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25690212</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25690212</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 11:19:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Excessive “Bubble” Talk]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recently have been considering all the speculation regarding whether we are in a
bubble. I flip back and forth on whether or not we actually are in the midst.
Prices are obviously high, probably overvalued in some obvious cases, but
interest rates are low, the Fed keeps on buying, stimulus keeps…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kth7s4/excessive_bubble_talk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kth7s4/excessive_bubble_talk/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:54:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently have been considering all the speculation regarding whether we are in a bubble. I flip back and forth on whether or not we actually are in the midst. Prices are obviously high, probably overvalued in some obvious cases, but interest rates are low, the Fed keeps on buying, stimulus keeps pumping, and major companies do seem to indeed be making decent piles of money. But on a purely psychological-level, when everyone is saying we are in a bubble makes me think we aren’t actually – historically bubbles happen when everyone turns a blind-eye to excessive rises in asset prices. People aren’t turning a blind-eye yet, in fact everyone keeps making claims and saying be cautious. So I think in a contrarian sense prices will continue to rise for the short- and medium- term at least until sentiment shifts and everyone begins to think that this is all normal and BAU again. We aren’t there yet. There’s possibility of external factors coming into play: shutdown risk (I personally believe this risk is low), no future stimulus (low again), etc. Then again, I may be the one making that BAU case, only time will tell...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck in 2021 everyone and stay safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GHIV]]></title><description><![CDATA[GHIV is a SPAC I think was mentioned on here a few times, but I thought I’d give
it another shout out in lieu of some upcoming catalysts. It’s merging with UWM,
or United Wholesale Mortgage - which is an established company with revenue,
something that is not super common with the companies that…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktkuu2/ghiv/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktkuu2/ghiv/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:54:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;GHIV is a SPAC I think was mentioned on here a few times, but I thought I’d give it another shout out in lieu of some upcoming catalysts. It’s merging with UWM, or United Wholesale Mortgage - which is an established company with revenue, something that is not super common with the companies that SPACs merge with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, the company GHIV is merging with, UWM, released earnings on Jan. 6. Earnings are also expected to be released this year before the merger vote on the 20th, and are expected to show good growth from the company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of the merger, GHIV is disgustingly low for a SPAC so close to merging at only ~35% from NAV. It jumped up last month but was brought down last week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am aware that this sub does not like riskier plays like SPACs, but I really do think that UWM is a solid company with established revenue that could be a long term hold. I bought options, but I think the best decision for a long term hold if you believe in this company is shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;POS: 
12.5 c 1/15, 10c 1/15&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When Amazon Switched from Sun to Linux]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25693618</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25693618</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:54:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looking at my gains today]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kti7at/looking_at_my_gains_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kti7at/looking_at_my_gains_today/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 09:48:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You've Been Referred Here Because You're Wrong About Section 230 of the CDA]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25697823</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25697823</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 09:48:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Political twitter brings out the worst in just about everyone. Endless yelling and screaming, insults and ad-hominin attacks with zero intelligent discourse. Avoid it like the plague. Don't let them bring you down to their level.]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347661920980115463</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347661920980115463</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 09:08:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Political twitter brings out the worst in just about everyone. Endless yelling and screaming, insults and ad-hominin attacks with zero intelligent discourse. Avoid it like the plague. Don&apos;t let them bring you down to their level.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Me seeing all of Tesla gain porn, while I missed out and put life savings in GME/PLTR]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktg53h/me_seeing_all_of_tesla_gain_porn_while_i_missed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktg53h/me_seeing_all_of_tesla_gain_porn_while_i_missed/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 08:30:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VALE and TSLA]]></title><description><![CDATA[What’re the odds that the nickel mining company that Elon Musk said he would
give a ‘very big contract to for a very long time’ for mining nickel is VALE?
Are there other plausible options of company’s he could be referring to? I’m
curious which company he may have been taking about and VALE was the…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kti41l/vale_and_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kti41l/vale_and_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 08:30:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’re the odds that the nickel mining company that Elon Musk said he would give a ‘very big contract to for a very long time’ for mining nickel is VALE? Are there other plausible options of company’s he could be referring to? I’m curious which company he may have been taking about and VALE was the first to come to mind&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How do I handle jealousy and missed opportunities?]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's been an influx of successes and high returns posted in this recent
market, and whenever I look at these posts, I tend to get upset about missing
these opportunities. My heart sinks whenever I see another post about how
someone retired early due to an early TSLA stock or how they paid off…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktjf6b/how_do_i_handle_jealousy_and_missed_opportunities/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktjf6b/how_do_i_handle_jealousy_and_missed_opportunities/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 07:56:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s been an influx of successes and high returns posted in this recent market, and whenever I look at these posts, I tend to get upset about missing these opportunities. My heart sinks whenever I see another post about how someone retired early due to an early TSLA stock or how they paid off their mortgage because of BTC or AMZN or whatever. I want to desperately have an opportunity like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been mildly interested in investing for a while, but I&amp;#39;m a poor 19-year-old university student so I have pretty much no stable income and a severe lack of knowledge in investing. I want to invest now because of these posts, but I know I reasonably shouldn&amp;#39;t because I&amp;#39;d be investing with my emotions, I only have around $5,000 in my bank account and no stable income is coming in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I handle this FOMO and this jealousy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is interest rate going higher?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks, interest rates have begun to increase faster than
expected. The yield on the 10-year Treasury has risen from 0.93% at the
beginning of December to above 1%. That means that since August of last year,
when the 10-year yield hit 0.5%, interest rates have more than doubled.

I…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktbzwn/is_interest_rate_going_higher/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktbzwn/is_interest_rate_going_higher/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 07:56:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few weeks, interest rates have begun to increase faster than expected. The yield on the 10-year Treasury has risen from 0.93% at the beginning of December to above 1%. That means that since August of last year, when the 10-year yield hit 0.5%, interest rates have more than doubled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been looking at the 30y treasury bill rate and it seems like it is getting close to 2%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there are a few reasons why this is important for investors. Firstly, it means debt is more expensive. For both the U.S. government and corporate borrowers, the cost of borrowing money is rising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many analysts expect interest rates to continue to increase over the next year as a normal part of the economic cycle. When the economy is improving, it is essential to increase interest rates in order to avoid inflation spiralling out of control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Increased economic stimulus and borrowing could drive rates higher, and while this would be positive for many companies on a fundamental level, it is bound to hit equity valuations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of the risks investors need to be aware of as interest rates continue to grind higher. In past market downturns, it wasn&amp;#39;t as much of a concern, but this time around we have seen the rather unique phenomenon of a stock market bull run during a major global economic recession, which puts quite a different spin on things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The financial markets often do what we least expect as the highest probability scenarios are already priced in, and that&amp;#39;s where I believe we stand today, with a majority of investors pricing in lower for longer on the interest rate front, which is evidenced by the euphoric price action in the large-cap growth stocks, including recent heavily oversubscribed shares of initial public offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Against this backdrop, commodity prices are signaling that we are on the cusp of higher than expected future inflationary pressures. This could very well lead to the specter of a burst broader equity market bubble and a burst bond market bubble that potentially casts a pall over the broader investment landscape?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts about where is this going? I have been under the impression that the Fed will keep the interest rate low for many years but this seems contradict to what’s happening. Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roblox expects direct listing on NYSE in February]]></title><description><![CDATA[Roblox said earlier this week that it raised $520 million in private capital
ahead of a direct listing.

The company originally planned to go public in December but delayed its debut
after DoorDash and Airbnb soared more than expected out of the gates.

The company will trade on the New York Stock…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktf2ah/roblox_expects_direct_listing_on_nyse_in_february/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ktf2ah/roblox_expects_direct_listing_on_nyse_in_february/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 07:56:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roblox said earlier this week that it raised $520 million in private capital ahead of a direct listing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company originally planned to go public in December but delayed its debut after DoorDash and Airbnb soared more than expected out of the gates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company will trade on the New York Stock Exchange under ticker symbol &amp;quot;RBLX.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roblox said on Friday in an updated prospectus that it plans to go public through a direct listing next month, after the online game company delayed its debut in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, Roblox disclosed that it raised $520 million in a private financing round ahead of a direct listing. By taking this route to the public markets instead of a traditional IPO, Roblox is following Spotify, Slack, Palantir and Asana, sidestepping a share sale and instead allowing existing stakeholders and employees to sell stock to new investors right away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest funding round, at $45 a share, valued Roblox at $29.5 billion. In the updated filing, Roblox said an independent valuation report in December placed the shares at $41.52 apiece. By raising some money before going public, Roblox was able to pad its balance sheet and preserve the ability to bring in more capital through a secondary sale later this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the direct listing, the NYSE will set a reference price for the stock the night before Roblox&amp;#39;s debut, but no shares will be traded at that price. In the morning, the market makers will match buyers and sellers to determine the opening price and the stock will be available to the broader market under the ticker symbol &amp;quot;RBLX.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roblox had been considering a more traditional IPO, but tabled its plans last month after DoorDash and Airbnb popped on consecutive days, leading to concern that the company risked leaving too much money on the table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Due to market volatility and the performance of other recent underwritten initial public offerings, we have elected to file this prospectus as an amendment to the registration statement and pursue a direct listing to permit determination of the opening public price of our Class A common stock on the NYSE by buy and sell orders collected by the NYSE from broker-dealers,&amp;quot; Roblox said in the prospectus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it&amp;#39;s not doing an IPO, Roblox no longer requires underwriters. The company said Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley will stay on as financial advisers, but JPMorgan, Bank of America and RBC Capital Markets were removed from the filing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roblox, which first released its service in 2006, is hitting the public market following a year of dramatic growth as kids, who were forced to stay home during the pandemic, spent more time playing games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue in the third quarter jumped 91% from a year earlier to $242.2 million. Daily active users almost doubled in the period ended September to 36.2 million and &amp;quot;hours engaged&amp;quot; more than doubled to 8.7 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Roblox&amp;#39;s app, users create an avatar that they can move between millions of different games. They&amp;#39;re all free to play, but users buy virtual currency called Robux for advanced features or to build their character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The games are created by outside developers, who share the revenue with Roblox. The company said in the updated filing that in the first three quarters of 2020, the platform had about 3,800 developers, who earned $215 million. That&amp;#39;s up from a year earlier, when 2,400 developers made $72.2 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many game creators cash out into real world currency, &amp;quot;some choose to reinvest their Robux into developer tools, promote their experiences through our internal ad network, or spend the Robux as any other user would,&amp;quot; the company said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/08/roblox-expects-direct-listing-on-nyse-in-february.html&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TSLA went up another 0.25 Toyotas today. TSLA's daily movements can now be visualized as number of Toyota market caps.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Okay, Tesla gained another $60 billion today, but humans famously have trouble
visualizing big numbers, and $60 billion is just as arbitrary to our lizard
brains.

So, forget dollar amounts, start measuring Tesla's daily movements in number of
Toyotas (the company). $60 billion is roughly 1/4 (0.25)…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktdi5h/tsla_went_up_another_025_toyotas_today_tslas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktdi5h/tsla_went_up_another_025_toyotas_today_tslas/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 07:56:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, Tesla gained another $60 billion today, but humans famously have trouble visualizing big numbers, and $60 billion is just as arbitrary to our lizard brains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, forget dollar amounts, start measuring Tesla&amp;#39;s daily movements in number of Toyotas (the company). $60 billion is roughly 1/4 (0.25) Toyotas. Pretty soon Tesla will be going up and down by multiple Toyotas a day, so get used to it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archaeologists in Turkey unearth 2,500-year-old temple of Aphrodite]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25688066</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25688066</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 07:15:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pfizer vaccine appears effective against mutation in new coronavirus variants]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25696577</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25696577</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 07:15:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RUSH LIMBAUGH’S ACCOUNT IS GONE https://t.co/c48KWjujHR]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347742219713785859</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347742219713785859</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 06:03:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>RUSH LIMBAUGH’S ACCOUNT IS GONE https://t.co/c48KWjujHR</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Trading vultures]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktbljh/the_trading_vultures/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ktbljh/the_trading_vultures/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 06:03:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This subreddit stock picking is incredible!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I lurk on this subreddit daily and have been doing it for the past year and let
me tell you the people in this subreddit know how to pick stocks. They are so
accurate that it is borderline scary. If you been lurking here for the past year
then you know almost ALL of the most mentioned stocks here…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kti848/this_subreddit_stock_picking_is_incredible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kti848/this_subreddit_stock_picking_is_incredible/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 04:52:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I lurk on this subreddit daily and have been doing it for the past year and let me tell you the people in this subreddit know how to pick stocks. They are so accurate that it is borderline scary. If you been lurking here for the past year then you know almost ALL of the most mentioned stocks here have skyrocketed(and I am not even talking about Tesla or Nio). I know we are in a crazy bull run right now but give credit where credit is due, this subreddit stock picking is so stunning that it makes every other investing tv show/site look like amateurs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the most mentioned stocks last year included Sea limited, Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing, Draft kings, Cloudflare(NET), AMD, Nvidia, Square, Enphase, Microsoft, ICLN, Palantir, Alibaba, Apple, Sales force, Disney, ARKK, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ya I know trash like Hyliion is also mentioned a lot here but if you do just little DD you know they have no revenue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I never followed him. Anyone else?]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347738801842565120</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347738801842565120</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 04:01:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>I never followed him. Anyone else?</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I dug this out of the drawer and thought you young whippersnappers would find this interesting]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here is a Financial Holding Pyramid that I received over 20 years ago. The
bottom of the pyramid is low risk / low reward, and the top of the pyramid is
high risk / high reward. I have tried to understand each of these over the years
and dabbled in some, but I tend to stay towards the bottom, with a…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktbkn6/i_dug_this_out_of_the_drawer_and_thought_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ktbkn6/i_dug_this_out_of_the_drawer_and_thought_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 04:01:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is a Financial Holding Pyramid that I received over 20 years ago.  The bottom of the pyramid is low risk / low reward, and the top of the pyramid is high risk / high reward.  I have tried to understand each of these over the years and dabbled in some, but I tend to stay towards the bottom, with a family can&amp;#39;t be too risky.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/4N4P3DU.png&quot;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/4N4P3DU.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best of show – abuse of libc]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25690319</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25690319</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 03:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$GME now at 21 consecutive trading days on NYSE threshold securities list]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kt3azl/gme_now_at_21_consecutive_trading_days_on_nyse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kt3azl/gme_now_at_21_consecutive_trading_days_on_nyse/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 01:02:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to reduce downside risk in a stock without selling?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been holding tesla for exactly 11 months and have ridiculous gains. I want
to lock in some of my gains before Q1 earnings report. However I don't want to
sell my stock until it qualifies for long term cap gains, because I have a shit
load of profit I don't want to be counted as income.

What's…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kt4o21/how_to_reduce_downside_risk_in_a_stock_without/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kt4o21/how_to_reduce_downside_risk_in_a_stock_without/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 01:02:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been holding tesla for exactly 11 months and have ridiculous gains. I want to lock in some of my gains before Q1 earnings report.  However I don&amp;#39;t want to sell my stock until it qualifies for long term cap gains, because I have a shit load of profit I don&amp;#39;t want to be counted as income. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s the right options strategy to minimize risk here? Buy a put?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We Aren't the Only Retards Out There]]></title><description><![CDATA[So yesterday, Papa Musk tweeted "Use Signal
[https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1347165127036977153?s=20]" (227.3K likes,
28.7K retweets).

https://preview.redd.it/q9trn69923a61.png?width=604&format=png&auto=webp&s=8dba759a31f158fba12b097991e6aae44f5d03ad

This was a reference to the Signal…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kszqb5/we_arent_the_only_retards_out_there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kszqb5/we_arent_the_only_retards_out_there/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 01:02:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yesterday, Papa Musk tweeted &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1347165127036977153?s=20&quot;&gt;Use Signal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; (227.3K likes, 28.7K retweets).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/q9trn69923a61.png?width=604&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8dba759a31f158fba12b097991e6aae44f5d03ad&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/q9trn69923a61.png?width=604&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8dba759a31f158fba12b097991e6aae44f5d03ad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a reference to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://signal.org/en/&quot;&gt;Signal Messaging App&lt;/a&gt; (which by the way is not publicly traded).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An unrelated company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.otcmarkets.com/stock/SIGL/overview&quot;&gt;OTCMKTS:SIGL&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.signaladvance.com/&quot;&gt;Signal Advance&lt;/a&gt;) saw it&amp;#39;s stock rise by 526.67% over the course of the day:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/tldhx00c23a61.png?width=525&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=31ebe8d7526ba1b43a1f97c745f7beec4397fdbb&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/tldhx00c23a61.png?width=525&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=31ebe8d7526ba1b43a1f97c745f7beec4397fdbb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s amazing is that SIGL isn&amp;#39;t even available on RobinHood, so it wasn&amp;#39;t us retards that bid it up. If any of you 🌈🐻 have access to OTC markets, you probably want to short SIGL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>