<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 02:10:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Emerging Markets and Index Investing]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm passive investor with 5% of my portfolio in Emerging Markets (index). I've
been thinking lately that it's not really worth it to invest in these stocks.
Emerging market economies may indeed enjoy higher level of GDP growth than
developed economies, but their corporate governance is substandard,…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m339dm/emerging_markets_and_index_investing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m339dm/emerging_markets_and_index_investing/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m passive investor with 5% of my portfolio in Emerging Markets (index). I&amp;#39;ve been thinking lately that it&amp;#39;s not really worth it to invest in these stocks. Emerging market economies may indeed enjoy higher level of GDP growth than developed economies, but their corporate governance is substandard, corruption may be rampant, and the rule of law inconsistent. The result is that much of that growth is captured by insiders rather than by the public investors at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the market is undoubtedly aware of the problems and presumably takes them into account when setting prices, I&amp;#39;m not confident the market can accurately price in unknown information (for example, we don&amp;#39;t really know what goes on in China). Emerging Mkts is pehaps one of the few areas where active management makes sense. Indexing assumes the market is efficient, that assumption may not be true in some emerging markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel index investors are better off focusing exclusively on the US and other developed markets where we will get a fair shake. Large corporations like MCD and Coke already have exposure to emerging markets, and unlike locally traded shares, their financials are not suspect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Full Diligence Post on Nokia (NOK) Ahead of Capital Markets Day next Thursday (3/18)]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know there have been a lot of posts about NOK recently across several
different subreddits, but I recently did some due diligence on the the stock and
wanted to share my findings.

I originally had a lot of links in this, but it led to the post getting
auto-removed. Let me know if you would like…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m33vsq/full_diligence_post_on_nokia_nok_ahead_of_capital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m33vsq/full_diligence_post_on_nokia_nok_ahead_of_capital/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know there have been a lot of posts about NOK recently across several different subreddits, but I recently did some due diligence on the the stock and wanted to share my findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I originally had a lot of links in this, but it led to the post getting auto-removed. Let me know if you would like any sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;History of Nokia&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;ve seen any of the recent Nokia posts over the last few months, a common comment you will see is: &amp;quot;Nokia?!? That stock has been trading sideways for years!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While yes that is true, it is important to understand why. Let&amp;#39;s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2000-2013&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nokia dominated the mobile phone market during this time due to a quality handset. NOK traded in the $50s during the Dotcom bubble and in $30s before the housing crash. However, they never recovered after 2008 due to struggling to keep up in software as the mobile phone market started to shift to smart phones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2013-2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Nokia realized that trying to stay in the phone space was a losing battle they sold their phone division to Microsoft in 2013. For the next 3 years, Nokia was a large company in disarray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This did not get much better in 2016 when they acquired Alcatel-Lucent and decided to focus on networks. The merger did not go as smoothly as planned and over the next 5 years Nokia started &amp;quot;trading sideways&amp;quot; due to a bearish sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some investors stuck around through all of this due to a dividend being paid out, but that was suspended in 2019 so Nokia could focus on developing its 5G mobile networks. This dropped the share price down to $3.50.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2020-Present&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In March 2020, sentiment started to change somewhat bullish as they announced Pekka Lundmark would be taking over as CEO. Pekka worked for Nokia for a decade in the 90s and most notably served as Fortum&amp;#39;s, a Finnish state-owned energy company, CEO from 2015 to 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bullish sentiment was shorted lived due to the pandemic crash dropping the share price to $2.42. It started to pick back up over the summer when it was announced that Pekka would take over a month earlier than planned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was followed by rumors that there was a chance Nokia could win Verizon&amp;#39;s $6 billion 5G deal. Hype around this brought Nokia&amp;#39;s price above $5 for the first time since they suspended their dividend in October 2019. But in September, it was announced that Samsung won the Verizon deal and NOK fell down to $3.78. It fell even further to $3.37 in October when the rest of the market saw a down swing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it climbed back up to the low $4s, had a crazy January hitting $9.79 for about 10 seconds during to the meme stock frenzy, and has since returned to the high $3s low $4s after the Q4 earnings call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q4 Earnings Call&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what exactly did happen during that earnings call on 2/4/21? Why did it hurt NOK&amp;#39;s price?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people blame Pekka messing up the call with some pessimistic word choices, most notably the word &amp;quot;challenging.&amp;quot; Why would he say this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It may just be his straight forward personality. It might have been an intentional sandbag so he can control future expectations. It may because Nokia prides itself on being on ethical company. I think it was probably due to a little bit of all of the above. Pekka using this language was not surprising. He said the exact same thing during the 2020 Q3 earnings call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the rumors that Nokia may blow it out of the water during their Q4 earnings were unwarranted. Nokia did beat their expected earnings, but because of a decrease in year over year revenue, people overreacted (just like they did when Samsung won the Verizon deal) and sold their Nokia positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pekka&amp;#39;s Tenure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pekka has been in charge for 7 months during a global pandemic, but he has been able to make some progress it appears. Much of this information can be found in the Nokia 2020 Annual Report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He trimmed their employee size by 11,000.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He improved their free cash flow to $2.6 billion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even with the decrease in revenue he nearly doubled their operating profit (page 82).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He drastically reduced their net deferred tax balance (page 175).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He created four distinct business groups with plans for these groups to be shared in more detail during during Capital Markets Day on 3/18.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He replaced Nokia&amp;#39;s CFO, CTO, and CMO (CFO happened before he took over)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It appears he issued new shares to leadership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pekka has a stake in the company (page 67 of annual report) with a long term goal to &amp;quot;Focus on increase in share price and restoration of the dividend&amp;quot;.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot; In addition, Mr. Lundmark received an award of EUR 1.3 million of restricted shares on joining to buy out the awards he forfeited on leaving his previous employer. Mr. Lundmark was invited to join the co-investment based long-term incentive arrangement (eLTI) targeted to engage senior leaders with the long-term nature of our business and share price, and purchased EUR 2.6 million of Nokia shares against which he was given a matching award of EUR 5.2 million of Nokia 2020 performance shares. This investment by Mr. Lundmark aligns him with shareholders from the start and is a sign of his commitment and engagement with the company. Delivery of actual Nokia shares would take place in 2023 subject to performance conditions&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Bullish&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of 28 deals and partnerships Nokia has established since December 2020. Some of these deals are not massive, but they span across 6 continents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Largescale Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 year Multi Billion Dollar T Mobile Deal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7 year Belgium deal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Telekom in Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;France&amp;#39;s Mainland 5G Network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G Network in Austria&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Telecom Italia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cibicom ISP in Denmark&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Polkomtel Phone Provider in Poland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Telenor Group in Thailand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ooredoo in Algeria&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G Network in Philippines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tele2 in Sweden, Latvia, Lithuania, and Estonia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ecuador&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vodafone in Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Singapore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Private 5G Deals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Diego Gas &amp;amp; Electric Private Network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Port of Seattle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Japanese Companies Conexio, Hitachi Kokusai, Nippon Steel, Omron and Sharp:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WEG Motor Manufacturer in Brazil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elisa in Finland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optus Stadium in Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Partnerships&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU&amp;#39;s Hexa-X 6G Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brazil&amp;#39;s Telecommunications R&amp;amp;D Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AT&amp;amp;T tests to deploy virtualized and open RAN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patents deal with Samsung&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LG Uplus trial in South Korea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5G is the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The confusing nature of 5G could be holding back the market&amp;#39;s valuation of Nokia. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nokia is currently trading at a market cap of $22-23 billion even with a 2020 revenue of $24 billion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A letter that Pekka recently published gives a decent explanation of what 5G is.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In it, he admits &amp;quot;[5G] is exciting, but it can seem a bit abstract.&amp;quot; But then goes on to describe some real world examples that really helps explain it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Our partners saw unanticipated breakdowns and production line defects drop by 30% after installing smart video sensors in our manufacturing deployments. In the logistics sector, deploying augmented reality devices cut machine monitoring costs by half. In ports, remote-controlled cranes doubled productivity and eliminated staff injuries: an incredible 100% drop.&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This seems to suggest that there may be more uses for 5G worldwide than cellular networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nokia released a study stating that 5G could have an $8 trillion impact on global GDP by 2030.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nokia and Ericcson may have a duopoly on 5G with Huawei and ZTE being banned in many countries. This trend may continue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some analysts have predicted massive (&amp;gt;1,000%) growth in the 5G market over the next 5 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upcoming Events/Rumors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital Markets Day (3/18/21)&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is when we will get some true guidance on the future of the company. Not only will they lay out the strategic business plans for their 4 business segments as I mentioned above, but it should be when they make announcements toward potential a Dividend Reinstatement, Share Buyback, and future R&amp;amp;D decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annual General Meeting (4/8/21)&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not sure what they plan to cover during this, but I would assume it will act as a follow up to Capital Markets Day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dividend Reinstatement&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most signs point to Nokia investing in R&amp;amp;D for a while, but based on Pekka&amp;#39;s compensation package it should be back by 2023 at the latest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share Buyback&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nokia did buy back 1.25 billion shares in 2015-16 and 1 billion shares in 2016-17. So the rumors they plan to do this again could be true. They can purchase up to a total of 550 million shares both this year and next year. 550 million because it correlates to 10% of the companies total outstanding shares.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Bearish (Risks/Cons)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The meme stock frenzy has a long-lasting impact on the opinion of this stock.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The dividend is not reinstated for another 3+ years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pekka does not have what it takes. Nokia is a sinking ship and cannot be turned around.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FCF is used solely for R&amp;amp;D and no shares are bought back over the next three years. The float does turn out to be too big to move significantly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nokia may not be undervalued and their revenue streams may continue to decline due to network share loses and pricing erosion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pekka has been very serious over the last two earning calls and things are going to get much worse/challenging before they get better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With a new US administration in place, the trend of banning Huawei and ZTE that they started is lifted. These two competitors then undercut Nokia pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G is no where near as big of an industry as the experts predict. Covid continues to slow the rollout of 5G well past 2030.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5G is too confusing and never gets the buy in from today&amp;#39;s investors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Duolingo's language notes all on one page]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26427405</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26427405</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:31:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fraidycat: Follow from afar]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26422109</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26422109</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:31:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Inflation Expectations hit their highest levels in over 12 years as the federal government is set to issue another 2 trillion in debt while the federal reserve creates money out of thin air to buy it. (This is not the Onion, it's actually happening) https://t.co/swyNXiTmYJ]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370140346856902659</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370140346856902659</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:46:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goodbye MongoDB, Hello PostgreSQL (2015)]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26420665</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26420665</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:46:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Checking GME every morning]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ttbz/checking_gme_every_morning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ttbz/checking_gme_every_morning/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to get over being an idiot?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I bought 20 AMD options last week(.50 cents/share), May 2021 $95 strike, when
AMD has been at bottom. I have been watching AMD for a while, I build PCs and
think they are generally hugely undervalued, so I wanted to get in on this. But
then I sold them on Friday and bought GME options for the…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2z9w9/how_to_get_over_being_an_idiot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2z9w9/how_to_get_over_being_an_idiot/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I bought 20 AMD options last week(.50 cents/share), May 2021 $95 strike, when AMD has been at bottom. I have been watching AMD for a while, I build PCs and think they are generally hugely undervalued, so I wanted to get in on this. But then I sold them on Friday and bought GME options for the &amp;#39;squeeze&amp;#39; instead. My logic was that even if there is only a 20% chance of GME hitting 1k, I will be massively rich from that, to the point that it was worth risking the nearly &amp;quot;sure thing&amp;quot;(I saw it as maybe 90% that it would print in the next month, not this quickly though) of AMD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AMD options have gone from the 50 cents I bought them up to 2.50 per share...I basically lost out on 4k so far( a lot for me, I invest 100/week on a tight budget mostly as a hobby) and my GME options are tanking. Now, after doing more research, I think the squeeze is bullshit and I just FOMOed in, convincing myself in the moment that it was a rational decision. I am regretting this so much :(. I have a feeling like I missed out on a good opportunity I will never have again(even though of course there will be other plays, I hate this feeling so much)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Let’s real talk, retards. How fun was today??]]></title><description><![CDATA[I want to genuinely hear how fun today was for you apes that are balls deep with
me in $GME. I needed a rush like today. I had a blast. I started on a high from
pre market numbers. Hit some jazz cabbage watching the morning. LOST MY SHIT
with that midday cliff. LOST EVEN MORE OF MY SHIT with that…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2efv8/lets_real_talk_retards_how_fun_was_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2efv8/lets_real_talk_retards_how_fun_was_today/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to genuinely hear how fun today was for you apes that are balls deep with me in $GME. I needed a rush like today. I had a blast. I started on a high from pre market numbers. Hit some jazz cabbage watching the morning. LOST MY SHIT with that midday cliff. LOST EVEN MORE OF MY SHIT with that light speed bounce back that made this whole community looks like an autist brotherhood instead of a retard brotherhood for like 5 minutes. Polished off the jazz cabbage coasting through the afternoon with the absolute goldmine of content y’all were producing. I’m proud to be a member of this community and this revolution. Thank you for the journey. Diamond. Fucking. Hands. 💎🤝💎&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Never Give Up....Never Surrender]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2hdvl/never_give_upnever_surrender/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2hdvl/never_give_upnever_surrender/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepFuckingValue - Movie Teaser]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2x00k/deepfuckingvalue_movie_teaser/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2x00k/deepfuckingvalue_movie_teaser/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME YOLO UPDATE: BACK OVER $5,000,000! (20,000 Shares) ✋💎🤚 The roller coaster was fun yesterday. 🚀🚀🚀🚀 Honestly, I like the stock, Ryan Cohen, cats, games, chicken tendies and whiskey in no particular order.]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2wt8j/gme_yolo_update_back_over_5000000_20000_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2wt8j/gme_yolo_update_back_over_5000000_20000_shares/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Those Hedge funds still haven't learned]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2s7c7/those_hedge_funds_still_havent_learned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2s7c7/those_hedge_funds_still_havent_learned/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why I don't like Tailwind CSS]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26422286</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26422286</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My bank sent me 64 copies of the same debit card]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26428453</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26428453</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My broker didn't limit my cost basis]]></title><description><![CDATA[I decided to sacrifice one of my accounts to the PDT/Free Ride violation gods,
and my broker didn't limit my daily cost basis. The result was as you can see in
the picture: https://imgur.com/Uq3a19s

My question is, are there any repercussions for this insane cost basis on an
account with a $5k…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2oy8e/my_broker_didnt_limit_my_cost_basis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2oy8e/my_broker_didnt_limit_my_cost_basis/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:55:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided to sacrifice one of my accounts to the PDT/Free Ride violation gods, and my broker didn&amp;#39;t limit my daily cost basis. The result was as you can see in the picture: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/Uq3a19s&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/Uq3a19s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question is, are there any repercussions for this insane cost basis on an account with a $5k value?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ULTA Beauty ($ULTA) upside in revenue & outlook when it reports aftermarket. Used American Psycho to illustrate the revenue DD.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reported Q4 revenue number will lead to price moves of >+-10% over the next
week. I'm long & leaning towards a double digit upswing for reasons below:
Consensus revenue expectation is $2.1 billion which means yoy declines in both
total sales & same-store sales. What if the numbers are better than…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2o0p7/ulta_beauty_ulta_upside_in_revenue_outlook_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2o0p7/ulta_beauty_ulta_upside_in_revenue_outlook_when/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reported Q4 revenue number will lead to price moves of &amp;gt;+-10% over the next week. I&amp;#39;m long &amp;amp; leaning towards a double digit upswing for reasons below:
Consensus revenue expectation is $2.1 billion which means yoy declines in both total sales &amp;amp; same-store sales. What if the numbers are better than expected? Obviously there are bulls expecting a beat but what if (pardon my language here) the Q4 revenue beat beats expectations? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;REASONS for the &amp;quot;beat beat&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s start with these internal facts: 1.ULTA makes 32% of its annual revenue in Q4. 2. ULTA current ytd revenue is only half of full year revenue for the previous year? Do you see where I&amp;#39;m going with this? Ulta&amp;#39;s Q4 revenue for this year should be higher as customers haven&amp;#39;t shopped that much ytd. (Relative to historical annual spend) ULTA will beat based on restocking and holiday splurges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now consider this scenario: you are Patrick Bateman and buy your cosmetics and skincare from ULTA Beauty. There&amp;#39;s a pandemic in 2020 so you slow down on shopping because you can&amp;#39;t risk catching covid in the store. As the year goes, you start ordering a few things online but not as much as you did in store (in person) pre-pandemic. However by Q4 you have WFH fatigue and you&amp;#39;re now ready to restock all your face creams, shower gel and makeup. Gotta show Paul Allen you&amp;#39;re still the MVP. You decide to order some essentials online plus it&amp;#39;s Christmas so you add some extras. You then realize that you&amp;#39;ve only spent half of what you normally spend at ULTA so you also get Evelyn an ULTA voucher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we look at Sephora&amp;#39;s numbers to test the beat beat view. Context: Sephora is owned by LVMH and is ULTA&amp;#39;s main competitor. Sephora only sells the fancy beauty (Think Dior &amp;amp; Estee Lauder) the high-life nothing cheap. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two things to note on these numbers:
Firstly, Sephora&amp;#39;s numbers are reported in the Selective Retailing Section of LVMH results. Selective Retailing combines Sephora with LVMH&amp;#39;s travel retailers (e.g DFS - which you see at the airport).
Secondly, there&amp;#39;s a date mismatch, Sephora year end is Dec vs Jan for ULTA, so ULTA quarters are a month ahead. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LVMH reported a recovery in selective retailing from a low of -38% in Q2 to -26% in Q4 in it&amp;#39;s 2020 annual results. Now -26% sounds bad but LVMH&amp;#39;s travel retailers account for the bulk of the decline. No travel = no revenue for DFS. Travel retail accounts for 20-35% of division revenue so adjusting for the collapse in travel leads to improved metrics for Sephora. This means SEPHORA IS BACK! IT&amp;#39;S RECOVERED TO PRE PANDEMIC REVENUE. Sephora revenue is global but makes a good read-through for the US market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we&amp;#39;re on Sephora as an ULTA long I&amp;#39;m not sleeping well since Sephora announced a store arrangement with Kohl&amp;#39;s which will be a long term headache for ULTA. Kohl&amp;#39;s unlike JCPenney (RIP) has locations in US strip malls which is Ulta&amp;#39;s niche. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LVMH&amp;#39;s numbers IMO offer the best peer comparison despite their opacity. It&amp;#39;s tempting to compare ULTA with general beauty sales data but ULTA has historically had low correlation to general retail data and 2020 just made general data even less useful. When large stores like Macys and other department stores report lower sales this counts for most of the decline in market data which makes it hard to assess smaller players like ULTA. This increases the uncertainty in the Q4 revenue number. Good setup for option opportunities but I excluded trades as my DD on the &amp;quot;beat beat&amp;quot; view. Please share options strategies in the comments. &lt;a href=&quot;http://ir.ultabeauty.com/financial-reports/quarterly-reports/default.aspx&quot;&gt;ULTA Financials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lvmh.com/investors/investors-and-analysts/publications/&quot;&gt;LVMH Financials &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks Daily Discussion & Options Trading Thursday - Mar 11, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme
for today is on stock options, but if options aren't your thing then just ignore
the theme and/or post your arguments against options…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2n9tl/rstocks_daily_discussion_options_trading_thursday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2n9tl/rstocks_daily_discussion_options_trading_thursday/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme for today is on stock options, but if options aren&amp;#39;t your thing then just ignore the theme and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+semiannual+arguments+against+TA%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;post your arguments against options here&lt;/a&gt; and not in the current post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful day to day links, including news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=amd&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required info to start understanding options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/c/calloption.asp&quot;&gt;Call option Investopedia video&lt;/a&gt; basically a call option allows you to buy 100 shares of a stock at a certain price (strike price), but without the obligation to buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/putoption.asp&quot;&gt;Put option Investopedia video&lt;/a&gt; a put option allows you to sell 100 shares of a stock at a certain price (strike price), but without the obligation to sell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the following word cloud and click through for the wiki:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/wiki/options-themed-post&quot;&gt;Call option - Put option - Exercising an option - Strike price - ITM - OTM - ATM - Long options - Short options - Combo - Debit - Credit or Premium - Covered call - Naked - Debit call spread - Credit call spread - Strangle - Iron condor - Vertical debit spreads - Iron Fly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is delta,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia delta&amp;quot; and click the investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The markets are closed. 
 
✧ S&amp;P 500 △ 1.04%                  
✧ Nasdaq △ 2.52%             
✧ Russell 2K △ 2.31%                  
✧ Dow Jones △ 0.58% https://t.co/F1sOOuwwj5]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370117553360678915</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370117553360678915</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:35:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shift ($SFT) DD: A rapidly growing competitor to Carvana that seems undervalued]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is Shift?

 * Shift is an online platform where you can buy used cars and/or sell your used
   car. Their main competitors are Carvana and Vroom.

I've never heard of Shift..can they even compete with big players like Carvana?

 * Used car sales are actually consistently greater than new car…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2rh7l/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2rh7l/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:22:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is Shift?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift is an online platform where you can buy used cars and/or sell your used car. Their main competitors are Carvana and Vroom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never heard of Shift..can they even compete with big players like Carvana?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used car sales are actually consistently greater than new car sales in the US, and for over a decade, the rate of used car sales has been growing faster than the rate of new car sales. The total used car market in the US was $841b in 2019, yet less than 1% of all car sales in 2019 occurred on an ecommerce marketplace like Carvana or Shift. This is at odds with the trends, as more consumers are moving towards doing most if not all of their shopping online. This trend was accelerated with the COVID 19 pandemic. There is plenty of space for growth in this category for several major players. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What separates Shift from their competitors, such as Carvana and Vroom?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift has several unique features compared to their competitors. They are the only service in their space that offers free test drives at your home. If you see the car you like online, you can request to test drive it, and Shift will bring it to your door for you to test drive with no commitment to buy. They also focus on older cars compared to their competitors, specifically cars that are 3-5 and 6-10 years old. They also focus on cars that are less than $20k in price, with 40% of their sales being $10k-$20k and 16% being &amp;lt;$10k. Cars of this age and price range are the largest segment of the used car market. For reference, 1-3 year old car listings comprise 48% of Carvana&amp;#39;s and 68% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings, compared to just 25% of Shift&amp;#39;s. Cars priced over $20k comprise 79% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings and 27% of Carvana&amp;#39;s, compared to 20% of Shift&amp;#39;s. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where does Shift operate?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They currently operate primarily in the west coast including California, the state with the largest number of vehicles sold per year, Portland, Oregon and Seattle, Washington. In Q4 of 2020, they launched four hubs in Texas, the state with the third largest vehicle market, in Dallas, Fort Worth, Austin and San Antonio, with more plans for future expansion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Numbers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s how Shift&amp;#39;s current numbers stack up against their competitors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Feature&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Shift&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Carvana&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Vroom*&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Share price as of 3/10/2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$260.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$34.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Market Cap&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$716M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$44.8B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$4.62B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Total Enterprise Value (TEV)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$497M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$46.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$3.92B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 Revenue&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$195.7M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$5.58B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$1.36B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue (average of analysts)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$445M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$2.51B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue Growth %&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;127%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;56%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;85%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.54x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8.3x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.88x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.1x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5.36x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.56x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/EBITDA&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.41x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-563x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-16.2x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note that Vroom is down nearly 33% this month and is just now approaching levels comparable to Shift at its current price level. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the table above, we can see that by buying Shift, you are paying a lower multiple even when factoring in analyst&amp;#39;s average estimates of larger growth (over 100%) in 2021 compared to their competitors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recent Earnings (3/09/2021)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift has been growing very rapidly and shows no signs of slowing down: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Q4 of 2020, they sold 4,666 units earning $73.4m revenue, representing 147% and 168% year over year growth and ended the year at $195.7m in total revenue (18% YoY growth) with 13,135 units sold. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their margins have also drastically improved, with their adjusted gross profit per unit in 2020 being $1,350 compared to $811 the year before, a 66% change. This has been largely due to their focus in 2020 on building up their in-house recondition (repairs/maintenance) team instead of relying on 3rd party mechanic vendors, with only 14% of cars being reconditioned by 3rd parties in Jan of 2021 compared to 45% at its peak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they have grown their in-house reconditioning team&amp;#39;s ability to process cars in house, they have invested significantly in acquiring inventory, and have increased their sellable inventory by 148% from December 2020 to March 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec 31st, 2020, the company had $234m in cash and cash equivalents and $49m in inventory, with $312m in total assets and $74.9m in total liabilities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2021 Guidance:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Q1 of 2021, they are guiding revenue of $90m-$95m, representing 200-217% YoY growth. For 2021, they are expecting $450M in revenue, a 130% YoY increase and is inline with analyst&amp;#39;s expectations, with $1,600 adjusted gross profit per unit, a 19% YoY increase, which is on track for their target of $2,500 in the next few years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hold shares in Shift and continue to buy at these prices as I am bullish on the company. Thanks for reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Red Flags I Saw While Doing 60 Technical Interviews in 30 Days]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26426602</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26426602</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:45:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I threw 90k into GME this morning. Don’t let me down fellow APES. 🦍🚀💎]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rvim/i_threw_90k_into_gme_this_morning_dont_let_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rvim/i_threw_90k_into_gme_this_morning_dont_let_me/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[In honor of GME hitting 200 - I bought 100 shawarmas to give out in Bahrain.]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2u8en/in_honor_of_gme_hitting_200_i_bought_100/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2u8en/in_honor_of_gme_hitting_200_i_bought_100/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[March 10th 2021]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2jcgj/march_10th_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2jcgj/march_10th_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Market correction and yield narrative looks to be over and a new active sequence upwards is ongoing]]></title><description><![CDATA[At this point: CPI was reported and treasury auctions took place this week
(there is one more for 30 year bonds today).

It looks the market changed the narrative. The yield along with Yield Curve
Control is no more the narrative. Next week, the FED has the FOMC but likely
there will be no action or…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ve17/market_correction_and_yield_narrative_looks_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ve17/market_correction_and_yield_narrative_looks_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point: CPI was reported and treasury auctions took place this week (there is one more for 30 year bonds today).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It looks the market changed the narrative. The yield along with Yield Curve Control is no more the narrative. Next week, the FED has the FOMC but likely there will be no action or hint but may introduce some temporary volatility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the market looks to be starting a new active sequence upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Me and my paperhanded GF]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2kmjq/me_and_my_paperhanded_gf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2kmjq/me_and_my_paperhanded_gf/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Making an online multiplayer game with Godot and Nakama]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26416545</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26416545</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:55:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shift ($SFT) DD: A rapidly growing competitor to Carvana that seems undervalued]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is Shift?

 * Shift is an online platform where you can buy used cars and/or sell your used
   car. Their main competitors are Carvana and Vroom.

I've never heard of Shift..can they even compete with big players like Carvana?

 * Used car sales are actually consistently greater than new car…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2qd6k/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2qd6k/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:41:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is Shift?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift is an online platform where you can buy used cars and/or sell your used car. Their main competitors are Carvana and Vroom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never heard of Shift..can they even compete with big players like Carvana?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used car sales are actually consistently greater than new car sales in the US, and for over a decade, the rate of used car sales has been growing faster than the rate of new car sales. The total used car market in the US was $841b in 2019, yet less than 1% of all car sales in 2019 occurred on an ecommerce marketplace like Carvana or Shift. This is at odds with the trends, as more consumers are moving towards doing most if not all of their shopping online. This trend was accelerated with the COVID 19 pandemic. There is plenty of space for growth in this category for several major players. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What separates Shift from their competitors, such as Carvana and Vroom?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift has several unique features compared to their competitors. They are the only service in their space that offers free test drives at your home. If you see the car you like online, you can request to test drive it, and Shift will bring it to your door for you to test drive with no commitment to buy. They also focus on older cars compared to their competitors, specifically cars that are 3-5 and 6-10 years old. They also focus on cars that are less than $20k in price, with 40% of their sales being $10k-$20k and 16% being &amp;lt;$10k. Cars of this age and price range are the largest segment of the used car market. For reference, 1-3 year old car listings comprise 48% of Carvana&amp;#39;s and 68% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings, compared to just 25% of Shift&amp;#39;s. Cars priced over $20k comprise 79% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings and 27% of Carvana&amp;#39;s, compared to 20% of Shift&amp;#39;s. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where does Shift operate?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They currently operate primarily in the west coast including California, the state with the largest number of vehicles sold per year, Portland, Oregon and Seattle, Washington. In Q4 of 2020, they launched four hubs in Texas, the state with the third largest vehicle market, in Dallas, Fort Worth, Austin and San Antonio, with more plans for future expansion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Numbers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s how Shift&amp;#39;s current numbers stack up against their competitors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Feature&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Shift&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Carvana&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Vroom*&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Share price as of 3/10/2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$260.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$34.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Market Cap&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$716M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$44.8B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$4.62B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Total Enterprise Value (TEV)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$497M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$46.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$3.92B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 Revenue&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$195.7M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$5.58B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$1.36B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue (average of analysts)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$445M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$2.51B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue Growth %&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;127%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;56%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;85%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.54x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8.3x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.88x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.1x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5.36x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.56x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/EBITDA&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.41x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-563x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-16.2x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note that Vroom is down nearly 33% this month and is just now approaching levels comparable to Shift at its current price level. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the table above, we can see that by buying Shift, you are paying a lower multiple even when factoring in analyst&amp;#39;s average estimates of larger growth (over 100%) in 2021 compared to their competitors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recent Earnings (3/09/2021)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift has been growing very rapidly and shows no signs of slowing down: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Q4 of 2020, they sold 4,666 units earning $73.4m revenue, representing 147% and 168% year over year growth and ended the year at $195.7m in total revenue (18% YoY growth) with 13,135 units sold. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their margins have also drastically improved, with their adjusted gross profit per unit in 2020 being $1,350 compared to $811 the year before, a 66% change. This has been largely due to their focus in 2020 on building up their in-house recondition (repairs/maintenance) team instead of relying on 3rd party mechanic vendors, with only 14% of cars being reconditioned by 3rd parties in Jan of 2021 compared to 45% at its peak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they have grown their in-house reconditioning team&amp;#39;s ability to process cars in house, they have invested significantly in acquiring inventory, and have increased their sellable inventory by 148% from December 2020 to March 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec 31st, 2020, the company had $234m in cash and cash equivalents and $49m in inventory, with $312m in total assets and $74.9m in total liabilities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2021 Guidance:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Q1 of 2021, they are guiding revenue of $90m-$95m, representing 200-217% YoY growth. For 2021, they are expecting $450M in revenue, a 130% YoY increase and is inline with analyst&amp;#39;s expectations, with $1,600 adjusted gross profit per unit, a 19% YoY increase, which is on track for their target of $2,500 in the next few years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hold shares in Shift and continue to buy at these prices as I am bullish on the company. Thanks for reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon Quietly Began Building a Grocery Chain During Pandemic]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-11/amazon-quietly-began-building-a-grocery-chain-during-pandemic

Grocery analysts say Amazon Fresh stores are likely cheap to launch and even
cheaper to run—the perfect weapon to stake a long-term claim in a famously
low-margin industry.

Analysts…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ss0t/amazon_quietly_began_building_a_grocery_chain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ss0t/amazon_quietly_began_building_a_grocery_chain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-11/amazon-quietly-began-building-a-grocery-chain-during-pandemic&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-11/amazon-quietly-began-building-a-grocery-chain-during-pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grocery analysts say Amazon Fresh stores are likely cheap to launch and even cheaper to run—the perfect weapon to stake a long-term claim in a famously low-margin  industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts have long expected Amazon to bring its cashierless technology to larger stores. The company currently operates two Go Grocery locations, the largest of which is about 13,000 square feet—or roughly six times the size of the original convenience stores. Fresh stores are substantially larger, ranging from from 25,000 square feet to 45,000 square feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon is always looking for a way to defend from walmart and target, amazon fresh store is the perfect answer. Amazon keep improving the logistic warehouses and expanding the delivery network, the fresh store will be easily managed and capturing the low margin market share. Amazon is providing an unlimited growth opportunity for shareholders, for investor who bought amazon under $3k for the latest pullback, congratulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[As checking the price every minute was so nerve wracking I opted for an automated solution, which made my life so much easier! 💎💎💎🖐🖐🖐🚀🚀🚀]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ncx1/as_checking_the_price_every_minute_was_so_nerve/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ncx1/as_checking_the_price_every_minute_was_so_nerve/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deepfake: DFV sells his GME position in 2069 for $6.9 billion]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2obpb/deepfake_dfv_sells_his_gme_position_in_2069_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2obpb/deepfake_dfv_sells_his_gme_position_in_2069_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME - Chart, THE EXACT SAME THING HAPPENED DAYS BEFORE THE FIRST SQUEEZE]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ltnf/gme_chart_the_exact_same_thing_happened_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ltnf/gme_chart_the_exact_same_thing_happened_days/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME - Hey bitch do you want to make some fucking money?]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rgaj/gme_hey_bitch_do_you_want_to_make_some_fucking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rgaj/gme_hey_bitch_do_you_want_to_make_some_fucking/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME Cautionary Tale]]></title><description><![CDATA[Today’s dip was fucking delicious but it taught us a few things:

1.) Remove your fucking stop losses how the fuck does this need to be said. Why
are you letting a robot 📄 🙌🏻 for you?

2.) Half of y’all are fucking gods who bought the dip, and got a damn STEAL on
some guaranteed lottery tickets…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m28ibs/gme_cautionary_tale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m28ibs/gme_cautionary_tale/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s dip was fucking delicious but it taught us a few things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) Remove your fucking stop losses how the fuck does this need to be said. Why are you letting a robot 📄 🙌🏻 for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) Half of y’all are fucking gods who bought the dip, and got a damn STEAL on some guaranteed lottery tickets 💰💰💰&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.) The other half of y’all weren’t actually waiting on a dip (even though you guys spam it for upvotes like fucking degenerate gremlins) and pussied out when it was time our time to put our NUTS on the hedgies chin. 🌰🌰🌰&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actual important shit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) They are running out of ammo, those drops had fuck all volume behind them. That short attack topped any of the previous attacks, even going back to January. They’re running out of short volume and they know it. We are (for real this time) in the endgame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) CNBC and other shill outlets are tightly gagged, we are seeing tangibly less coverage across the board than at this far up in the share price a month ago. Only rarely to be released to revel in any tiny downtick of the share price. This is for a reason. Last time everybody was shitting themselves over GME, it was everywhere. And because of this, MANY retail investors hopped on the train and sucked up a lot of volume in a short period, hence the silence now. This is potentially a good thing because it means no influx of uneducated monkeys who know jack shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.) We need educate new members of this fuck wagon on what is going on. IN THE SIMPLEST TERMS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: NEWBIES! YOU’LL KNOW WHEN THE SQUEEZE IS HAPPENING! IT WILL FUCKING SKYROCKET *$5000+ MINIMUM. DONT SELL (unless you have to I know everyone has varying circumstances) DONT BUY UNLESS YOURE READY FOR A HIGH VOLATILITY STOCK. SHIT GOES UP DOWN BACK FORWARD, FUCKING BACKFLIPS. Stop asking stupid shit and hold on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR; Remove your stop losses. Weaponize the newly born apes. Everything has led to now. The media has sorta fucked off, paper hands are long gone. The shorts have one bullet in the gun and they’re saving it to shoot themselves in the mouth. Hang on and have fun. Love you apes &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a cat, I’m an ape.
This is not financial advice. 
🙌🏻💎🙌🏻💎🙌🏻💎🙌🏻💎🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: ok fuck 5k minimum&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: get clickbaited lul. GO SET LIMIT BUYS STOP GIVING AWARDS HAHAHA THANKS BUT FUCK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME Megathread Part 2 for March 11, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[holy moly! holy moly? ... holy moly.]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2uy4f/gme_megathread_part_2_for_march_11_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2uy4f/gme_megathread_part_2_for_march_11_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;holy moly! holy moly? ... &lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;holy&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;moly.&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME and AMC charts today during that mass drop. Identical? One could say tactical. Human emotion plays a lot into market buys and sells, and these hedges are looking to trigger you to sell with these coordinated attacks. Stay 💎🙌🏼 and remember why you bought the stock and stay retarded.]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2bjre/gme_and_amc_charts_today_during_that_mass_drop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2bjre/gme_and_amc_charts_today_during_that_mass_drop/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shoutout to anyone and everyone putting it all on the line for a stock you’ve barely researched:]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2t9a2/shoutout_to_anyone_and_everyone_putting_it_all_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2t9a2/shoutout_to_anyone_and_everyone_putting_it_all_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why I'm super happy to watch evil hedgies shave 1/3 of GME and AMC]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello WSB, this is my first official post, but I'm very proud to see how we have
all HODL together really strong.

I have been in GME since 30 Oct 2019 with an additional 1670 shares on 29 May
2020 and I wish I could take a screenshot to prove my words, but my custodian
account does not allow any…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m25szi/why_im_super_happy_to_watch_evil_hedgies_shave_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m25szi/why_im_super_happy_to_watch_evil_hedgies_shave_13/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello WSB, this is my first official post, but I&amp;#39;m very proud to see how we have all HODL together really strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been in GME since 30 Oct 2019 with an additional 1670 shares on 29 May 2020 and I wish I could take a screenshot to prove my words, but my custodian account does not allow any screenshots out of &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; reasons. I currently hold over 6 digits of value in GME and I hope to reach my 7 digits and possibly 8. After what happened today, my 7 digits is certain, 8 digits possible. With more crayons maybe I&amp;#39;ll reach 9.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said I like to share and encourage with everyone why this nosedive drop we seen today is actually the BEST affirmation we really need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s been wonderful DD that the Short interest are still extremely high and that the data in FINRA is entirely unreliable. Let&amp;#39;s be honest, before what happened today, no matter how certain we are, we weren&amp;#39;t 100% sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m an expert in Chinese history, and I&amp;#39;ll quote Sun Tzu, the famed author recognised for writing the Art of War over 2000 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles. If you know yourself but not the enemy, for every victory gained you will also suffer a defeat. If you know neither the enemy nor yourself, you will succumb in every battle.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truth is we never really knew what the hedges were up to and this week was really fishy, with the absence of obvious short ladders and peaceful markets. Other than occasional dips everyday after reaching a peak, we couldn&amp;#39;t tell much. Some people have speculated that maybe the hedges were buying calls in order to reduce their risks, but I think we can all agree now that there is a good possibility that the dips we&amp;#39;ve been seeing the last few days are just a test for hedges to see how much the price can be affected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let&amp;#39;s be honest with ourselves, that was a coordinated attack. I have no idea how long they have planned that, but looking from what we&amp;#39;ve seen, it&amp;#39;s definitely a lot of time. At that scale it&amp;#39;s not possible for 1 or 2 hedge funds to pull this off by themselves. And YET!! This is where we recovered strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what this means is this. The hedges are panicking. They are worried. And they have proven that the shorts &lt;em&gt;HAVE NOT BEEN COVERED&lt;/em&gt;. If they have been covered to the large extent they claimed to, today&amp;#39;s coordinated attack wouldn&amp;#39;t have happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just did they admit with their actions that they are fearing us, they also basically highlighted to us what stocks they are all massively shorting. AMC, KOSS, NOK, BB all are in this together with us GME Army! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know it&amp;#39;s like Harry Potter, where Voldemort basically handed the weapons to Harry by his own hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on Chinese History, there&amp;#39;s this clever strategist Sun Tzu. For him before he executes any clever maneuvers for war, he will always test them first. If the hedges we are up against are the same smooth brain people like Sun Tzu, this fall is only a test. But it&amp;#39;s costly to them and we have held strong. With the current prices, supposing they did buy some shares to cover their losses, all those buys from 180 to 250 are all gone. Now they are forced to buy shares above 260 and its only going to cost them even more. Much better for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fellow apes, they are really afraid of our gamma squeeze this week and next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now... We strike back, by doing NOTHING!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/aTaF8j6&quot;&gt;to the skeptics who need proof for everything&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I obviously have better things than to post everything on social media like a attention seeking person. I&amp;#39;m a retarded ape not a peacock. Your tongues will wag too no matter what even if my picture has shown my platform to be ancient. But that&amp;#39;s nothing to do with my investing preferences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For you skeptics who need proof for everything and choose to always doubt and flake, here it is. &amp;quot;A confident man does not live for the applause and approval of the non-worthy&amp;quot;. Your skeptical outlook has only said to me that you clearly did not see Gamestop for what it really was earlier on, and even if DFV&amp;#39;s DD was shown to you in those days, you were a late adopter. It has also shown me that you have the paper hands tendency when you don&amp;#39;t see potential and when the going gets tough. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought I have surpassed and ignored most silly comments, but thanks to the 1% of negative words, you have helped me see I still react to silly nonsense and it&amp;#39;s something I need to change in myself. You are a Hyena and this is a community of apes. Reflect on yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Receiving SpaceX Falcon 9 Telemetry with a HackRF and 1.2m Satellite Dish]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423406</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423406</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:01:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else uncomfortable in a bull market?]]></title><description><![CDATA[As someone who likes to buy the dip and has plenty of stocks in various sectors
(other than tech) they want to buy... I sense a bull market happening for at
least a month or so, and then inflation popping it's head back up in May.

But for whatever reason, I feel very dissatisfied and frustrated on…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2k8hk/anyone_else_uncomfortable_in_a_bull_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2k8hk/anyone_else_uncomfortable_in_a_bull_market/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As someone who likes to buy the dip and has plenty of stocks in various sectors (other than tech) they want to buy... I sense a bull market happening for at least a month or so, and then inflation popping it&amp;#39;s head back up in May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for whatever reason, I feel very dissatisfied and frustrated on &amp;quot;up&amp;quot; green days, and get massive FOMO when most of the stocks on my watchlist are up 3-5% and the one&amp;#39;s at worst are in the -1-+1% range. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people panic or get emotional when stocks go down, but I feel much more comfortable there with buying opportunities. It&amp;#39;s times like these where I get anxious and feel I didn&amp;#39;t do &amp;quot;enough&amp;quot; on a given day (or in prior days ESPECIALLY on down days where I bought maybe 2-3 stocks and could have in retrospect bought 5-6) especially when my portfolio only goes up maybe .25% or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is coming from someone  who looked at stocks in past months and realized had they gotten them then, they would virtually all be at higher valuations today. Also as someone who is trying to transition out of tech into other sectors, but so far is not quite there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Selling put option, want to make sure I understand the risks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tried posting this in r/Options [/r/Options] but removed as a new trader
question. Isn't the point to learn trading option from knowledgeable people I
don't get it? Anyhow, maybe someone here can reassure me.

I've gotten a bit more comfortable with basic options trading over the past 6
months. I…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s5f9/selling_put_option_want_to_make_sure_i_understand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s5f9/selling_put_option_want_to_make_sure_i_understand/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tried posting this in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/Options&quot;&gt;r/Options&lt;/a&gt; but removed as a new trader question.  Isn&amp;#39;t the point to learn trading option from knowledgeable people I don&amp;#39;t get it? Anyhow, maybe someone here can reassure me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve gotten a bit more comfortable with basic options trading over the past 6 months. I still consider selling a put option a basic task but very important to add to the repertoire for setting up more complex strategies. I want to start getting more comfortable with this type of trade as well. I want to keep the first one small just to make sure I don&amp;#39;t screw it up or lose a bunch of money. I&amp;#39;ll outline the trade below and just want to make sure there&amp;#39;s no huge potential for loss here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to own Palantir (PLTR) at $23.5, it is currently trading at $26. My assumption is that I can sell the put option (sell to open) contract for a strike price of $23.5 for whatever date I choose (looking short term just to start off - say April 1). If the price of PLTR drops to $23.5 at any point during that period and gets executed, I am assigned the shares at the strike price of $23.5 (minus the premium I receive so actually less than $23.5 overall). If it never hits the strike price of $23.5, the contract expires I get no shares but I collect the premium. Am I missing something on this that might cost me a bunch of money? I know that I need to ensure I have the capitol in my portfolio to cover the cost of the contract if it gets executed, that&amp;#39;s not an issue. But my concern is my Brokerage states my maximum loss potential is $2,239 which scares me. I&amp;#39;m assuming that the $2,239 loss is actually just the cost for purchasing the shares minus the premium received, but that to me is not a loss I still own an underlying equity worth $2350 (i.e. no loss).  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Apple's Stock Sell-Off Is A Golden Buying Opportunity $AAPL]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shanthi Rexaline [https://www.benzinga.com/users/shanthi-rexaline] , Benzinga
Staff Writer

Apple Inc. AAPL 1.65% [https://benzinga.com/stock/aapl#NASDAQ] shares may have
taken a beating in the recent tech sell-off, but an analyst at Wedbush analyst
said his conviction in the stock has only…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s8x9/why_apples_stock_selloff_is_a_golden_buying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s8x9/why_apples_stock_selloff_is_a_golden_buying/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:31:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/users/shanthi-rexaline&quot;&gt;Shanthi Rexaline&lt;/a&gt; , Benzinga Staff Writer &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://benzinga.com/stock/aapl#NASDAQ&quot;&gt;AAPL 1.65%&lt;/a&gt; shares may have taken a beating in the recent tech sell-off, but an analyst at Wedbush analyst said his conviction in the stock has only increased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Apple Analyst:&lt;/strong&gt; Daniel Ives has an Outperform rating and $175 price target for Apple shares, with the bull case price target at $225. Wedbush added the stock to its &amp;quot;Best Ideas&amp;quot; list. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Apple Thesis:&lt;/strong&gt; After a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/21/01/19370036/apple-analysts-lift-price-targets-following-jaw-dropper-q1-4-sell-side-takes&quot;&gt;stellar December quarter&lt;/a&gt;, when Apple managed to crush iPhone estimates, some cuts in the iPhone forecasts for fiscal year 2021 were discounted by the market, Ives said in a note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is reflected in the stock&amp;#39;s sell-off over the last month, the analyst said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wedbush&amp;#39;s Asia checks are markedly bullish, suggesting over 230 million units for 2021, he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initial build forecast for the iPhone 13 indicates the supercycle will continue into fiscal year 2022, Ives said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Geographically speaking, demand in China looks strong coming out of the Chinese New Year and remains a linchpin to our Apple bull thesis.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The analyst also sees continued uptick in ASPs due to a higher mix of the iPhone Pro and Pro Max, with the Mini being significantly scaled down around production/demand globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/21/02/19766821/why-apple-will-hit-a-3-trillion-market-cap-by-the-end-of-2021&quot;&gt;$3-trillion valuation in sight&lt;/a&gt; for Cupertino, the recent sell-off in share creates a golden buying opportunity, according to Wedbush. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AAPL Price Action:&lt;/strong&gt; Apple shares lost 0.91% in Wednesday&amp;#39;s session, closing at $119.98. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Sweden Solar System]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26424090</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26424090</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[One definition of inflation is "too much money chasing too few goods." We're borrowing trillions of dollars to send free money to over a hundred million people who never lost their job/income during the pandemic - for a third time. If this doesn't create inflation, nothing will. https://t.co/eFLT2fiKgo]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370025005107404815</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370025005107404815</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir announces "Double Click" demo event on April 21st]]></title><description><![CDATA[Article:
https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-announces-double-click-demo-114500595.html

Copy and Paste of Article for those of you lazy enough: Palantir Technologies
(NYSE:PLTR) today announced that it will hold the first in a series of "Double
Click" demo events on Wednesday, April 14, 2021,…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2q0v6/palantir_announces_double_click_demo_event_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2q0v6/palantir_announces_double_click_demo_event_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Article: &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-announces-double-click-demo-114500595.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-announces-double-click-demo-114500595.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copy and Paste of Article for those of you lazy enough:
Palantir Technologies (NYSE:PLTR) today announced that it will hold the first in a series of &amp;quot;Double Click&amp;quot; demo events on Wednesday, April 14, 2021, at 11:00am ET.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir software is used by customers across 40 industries worldwide. Double Click is Palantir&amp;#39;s series of software demo events that showcase how the company&amp;#39;s platforms are used across these industries and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first event will feature in-depth demonstrations of Palantir Foundry for life sciences and industrials. Palantir’s customers in these verticals include Merck, NIH, NHS, 3M, bp, PG&amp;amp;E, LANXESS, Doosan, and others. The software demos at Double Click will showcase how customers can use Archetypes, Palantir’s solution to deploy end-to-end use cases in a matter of clicks, on top of Foundry, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life Sciences: harmonized patient view, clinical and observational data curation, prognostic model management, accelerated discovery via scientific research collaboration&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Industrials: end-to-end quality assurance, production optimization, high-scale IoT analytics, supply chain optimization&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advance registration is required, and is available at &lt;a href=&quot;https://palantir.events/doubleclick&quot;&gt;https://palantir.events/doubleclick&lt;/a&gt;. Capacity is limited, and registration will close 24 hours prior to the event. For any questions regarding the event, please email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:double-click@palantir.com&quot;&gt;double-click@palantir.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn&amp;#39;t see anyone post about it yesterday, so I thought I&amp;#39;d create a thread and see what people have to say. I think these kinds of demo events will only boost PLTR, especially in the long-term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Asahi Linux Progress Report: January/February 2021]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26421963</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26421963</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Write Simply]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423090</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423090</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fda approval jumps and getting the news early]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey,

I was looking to see if there are any ways to get auto updates or live updates
for when things get FDA approved?

Theres always a jump. For 50-300% from what I've seen recently and anything that
can help get ahead of the curve and before stocktwits etc would be great!]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ls9d/fda_approval_jumps_and_getting_the_news_early/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ls9d/fda_approval_jumps_and_getting_the_news_early/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:28:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was looking to see if there are any ways to get auto updates or live updates for when things get FDA approved?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theres always a jump. For 50-300% from what I&amp;#39;ve seen recently and anything that can help get ahead of the curve and before stocktwits etc would be great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Highway sign US 9 south. 💎💎💎🖐🖐🖐🚀🚀🚀🌚]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m29uzz/highway_sign_us_9_south/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m29uzz/highway_sign_us_9_south/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:28:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Realistically, how many stocks do you actively trade in?]]></title><description><![CDATA[For you active traders, do you stick to a handful of stocks or do you try to
spread it out over everything? I'm finding it hard to concentrate when there's
so much going on in the market! I can lose sight of what I am trying to
accomplish by chasing other stocks. How do you manage your…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2gddn/realistically_how_many_stocks_do_you_actively/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2gddn/realistically_how_many_stocks_do_you_actively/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:45:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For you active traders, do you stick to a handful of stocks or do you try to spread it out over everything?  I&amp;#39;m finding it hard to concentrate when there&amp;#39;s so much going on in the market!  I can lose sight of what I am trying to accomplish by chasing other stocks.  How do you manage your stocks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thank you for your comments and insight!  I think I&amp;#39;ve just been stretching myself too thin, and it&amp;#39;s been exhausting.  I will stick to a handful of the stocks I know and we&amp;#39;ll just see what happens!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>