<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 10:59:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[What is a book that is frequently suggested here that you didn’t like? And a book you never thought you’d like, but ended up loving it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have an ongoing list of books I see suggested here a lot because I want to
read them all, and so many have been great!

But sadly, I am reading “Circe” by Madeline Miller and I just can’t get into it!
I have gotten through over half the book and I just don’t feel connected or
captivated, which…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o83ulz/what_is_a_book_that_is_frequently_suggested_here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o83ulz/what_is_a_book_that_is_frequently_suggested_here/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:52:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have an ongoing list of books I see suggested here a lot because I want to read them all, and so many have been great! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But sadly, I am reading “Circe” by Madeline Miller and I just can’t get into it! I have gotten through over half the book and I just don’t feel connected or captivated, which makes me sad because I know so many people swear by this book and it has great feminine energy which I like, I just don’t find myself really thinking about it beyond the times I am reading, and I never feel “engrossed”. I am disappointed in myself for this one, I’m sorry guys, I know it’s a great story. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has this happened to any of y’all? What is something you thought you’d love and ended up not? Also, what is a book you didn’t think you’d enjoy but you did?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just finished Of Mice and Men!]]></title><description><![CDATA[This was one of the first novels I’ve ever actually liked (the other one is Safe
as Houses).

The characters all feel so real and the writing is so incredibly descriptive.
It’s so easy to get lost in it since you can easily construct every last aspect
of every setting and person in your head. You…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7zg9h/just_finished_of_mice_and_men/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7zg9h/just_finished_of_mice_and_men/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:55:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was one of the first novels I’ve ever actually liked (the other one is Safe as Houses).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The characters all feel so real and the writing is so incredibly descriptive. It’s so easy to get lost in it since you can easily construct every last aspect of every setting and person in your head. You can understand precisely what the characters do and exactly why they do it, this is quite possibly the greatest thing I’ve ever read&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Confederacy of Dunces.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sirs, I just finished reading the book. It was a wonderful read. I thoroughly
enjoyed Ignatius’s worldview, his wanting to start a revolution, Mrs Reily’s
transformation, Santa’s don’t care attitude, Mancuso’s helplessness, Jones’s
wanting to cause a sabotage, Darlene’s innocence, Lana’s attitude,…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7kfji/a_confederacy_of_dunces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7kfji/a_confederacy_of_dunces/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:16:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sirs,
I just finished reading the book. It was a wonderful read. I thoroughly enjoyed Ignatius’s worldview, his wanting to start a revolution, Mrs Reily’s transformation, Santa’s don’t care attitude, Mancuso’s helplessness, Jones’s wanting to cause a sabotage, Darlene’s innocence, Lana’s attitude, Mr and Mrs Levy’s drama and so on.
This book has stood the test of time and has become a classic. 
How is it relevant in this generation/society?
Are there any other viewpoints from which the book should be viewed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,
Your Working Boy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just finished the murder on the orient express]]></title><description><![CDATA[I don't know what to say, I suspected that they were all in on it, pages before
the big reveal. I thought maybe M.bouc would have been in on it and organized
being the manager of the train but I didn't see anything coming.

suspecting that it was a group murder was only possible due to Poirot…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t87l/i_just_finished_the_murder_on_the_orient_express/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t87l/i_just_finished_the_murder_on_the_orient_express/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 05:19:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know what to say, I suspected that they were all in on it, pages before the big reveal. I thought maybe M.bouc would have been in on it and organized being the manager of the train but I didn&amp;#39;t see anything coming. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;suspecting that it was a group murder was only possible due to Poirot feeding us the information in the third act. I love being surprised by mystery stories and hate completely obvious ones, this is a reason that keeps me coming back to Agatha christie&amp;#39;s books. I completely ruled out Mrs. Hubbard as a suspect, but my jaw dropped when I found out, I guess you should not rule out the most unlikely suspect in an Agatha Christie novel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would keep reading a bad story for the characters but a good story without characters I find interesting or I&amp;#39;m attached to is a story I wouldn&amp;#39;t be invested in. luckily this book had the best of both worlds, great characters and a wonderful plot and mystery that I did not grow tired of. I liked other stories of christie&amp;#39;s like five little pigs and the amazing murder of roger Ackroyd but I was not attached to the characters and found the characters of the former book rather tedious. here christie balanced a large cast in a short book and kept them interesting enough in their short interviews and I have to say I appreciated the little map of the train that I went back to every once and a while to capture the setting of the train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story was amazing, I had a feeling I would love it and I&amp;#39;m glad I didn&amp;#39;t watch the movie. The fact that they all agreed to look the other way for a justified murder was also a great end. This one is one of my favorite Agatha christie books so far. next to read is and then there were none.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Has there been any HUGE hit in the past decade ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello !

Has there been any huge hit (like Harry Potter scale) in the book industry the
past decade ? I'm not talking about books that got popular afterwards such as
the GoT books, I'm talking about books that got insanely popular right from
release.

This quesion rose from watching "the mystery of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7v50n/has_there_been_any_huge_hit_in_the_past_decade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7v50n/has_there_been_any_huge_hit_in_the_past_decade/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello !  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has there been any huge hit (like Harry Potter scale) in the book industry the past decade ? I&amp;#39;m not talking about books that got popular afterwards such as the GoT books, I&amp;#39;m talking about books that got insanely popular right from release. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This quesion rose from watching &amp;quot;the mystery of Henri Pick&amp;quot; with my girlfriend and it got us thinking about the popularity of books nowadays. We do read books but we do not follow the news of the litterature world at all, we are clueless about the new releases or rising authors and such.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can&amp;#39;-t really think about any book in the past decade that got so popular that EVERYONE heard about it and got many people to read it. We thought of Twilight and 50 shades but we feel like they&amp;#39;re actually quite niche and too controversial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The inflated talents of protagonists in YA books]]></title><description><![CDATA[I don’t know if it’s just me or the books I am reading but I am finding it more
common place for protagonists (or at least main characters we are designed to
root for) to posses inflated talents.

What I mean is, almost every protagonist has an array of gifts all at once.
These talents consist of…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7o856/the_inflated_talents_of_protagonists_in_ya_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7o856/the_inflated_talents_of_protagonists_in_ya_books/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if it’s just me or the books I am reading but I am finding it more common place for protagonists (or at least main characters we are designed to root for) to posses inflated talents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean is, almost every protagonist has an array of gifts all at once. These talents consist of things such as being brilliant at music, well read, gifted at art, extremely athletic, potential world leading scientist, scholarship offers…all snowballed into one character. This is not to say these characters cannot exist or impossible to believe but I often feel that in stories in which, for example; That because the protagonist is unhappy or depressed that the reader is expected to feel more sad because of what is implied by their potential. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not to say, that books that use characters such as these are overall poorly written - but come across quite bland and copy and paste. Or perhaps it is me…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just curious to see if anyone else felt the same?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can't seem to get super engrossed in books like when I was younger and it sucks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back when I was still a kid, getting into a book - and staying there - seemed
super easy. Probably the best example of this, not just for me but for a lot of
people, was Harry Potter. If I got a new Harry Potter in my hands I just had to
finish it that same day, sleeping be damned, and the world…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7org9/cant_seem_to_get_super_engrossed_in_books_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7org9/cant_seem_to_get_super_engrossed_in_books_like/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 22:00:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back when I was still a kid, getting into a book - and staying there - seemed super easy. Probably the best example of this, not just for me but for a lot of people, was Harry Potter. If I got a new Harry Potter in my hands I just had to finish it that same day, sleeping be damned, and the world would stay with me for weeks after finishing it. It was the kind of story where you just felt compelled to go online and find communities to keep discussing it over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve tried to re-create this feeling since that time and I&amp;#39;ve never really found it. The closest was probably Game of Thrones/Song of Ice and Fire in terms of recreating this magical need for more information and discussion but otherwise, nothing much. I actually just put a bookmark at a Dresden book about ~50 pages from the ending and while I&amp;#39;ll obviously still finish the book, I have 0 urgency to do it. I&amp;#39;ve also tried reading Rowling&amp;#39;s other books as Robert Galbraith, wondering if it was her writing style that did it but the book was just nowhere near as engaging as any of her previous work. I just really want that super excitement at picking up a new book and I&amp;#39;m just not finding it, which makes me way less excited to read in general (and I hate it!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;m wondering, do you guys still regularly get deeply invested in the books you read? Do you think we feel that way less as we get older? Do some authors or genres inspire this more than others? What are your thoughts and experiences?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When I read, I pretend I am a filmmaker and as I read, I imagine what each 'scene' of 'my movie' will look like. It's silly fun but it makes literature 50% more exciting!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I assume this is a well known common thing but it only clicked with me recently
and I have been a voracious reader! Before then, I've always been one of those
"I must focus on each word and nothing else or I will get lost" kind of kid. I
could not afford anything else happening in my head other than…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t048/when_i_read_i_pretend_i_am_a_filmmaker_and_as_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t048/when_i_read_i_pretend_i_am_a_filmmaker_and_as_i/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I assume this is a well known common thing but it only clicked with me recently and I have been a voracious reader! Before then, I&amp;#39;ve always been one of those &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;I must focus on each word and nothing else or I will get lost&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; kind of kid. I could not afford anything else happening in my head other than my own voice saying the words or else I&amp;#39;d lose track of what would be happening. But now, I have aquired this...hmm... would &amp;#39;Skill&amp;#39;? be too pretentious a word? I don&amp;#39;t know but it feels like I&amp;#39;ve gone to the next level of reading! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it all started with the Grapes of Wrath which I finished a few days ago. Everytime I opened the book, the &amp;quot;movie&amp;quot; would start playing and it was so consistent and concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GOP felt like an entire film playing in my head. From page one to the last. I guess, with practice, I was able to envision how character would look, how they would sound, what the lighting of each scene would like, the location, the &amp;quot;close up shots&amp;quot; of certatain conversations and monologues and what music would be playing. All this as I read. It was..sooo...goddamn enjoyable!! I have have felt so immersed before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also just finished the Raymond Carver short story - &amp;#39;Preservation&amp;#39; only minutes ago! And duuuude lol, It took me like 15 minutes to finish but it felt like a proper short film was happening right there in my head! I envisioned what the house looked like, their accents, their facial expressions, and of course the music!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I want to go back and re-read all my favourite books! I feel so happy right now lol. I&amp;#39;ve always loved reading but now it feels like I&amp;#39;ve aquired this next level love everyone is always talking about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are books keeping you alive?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I was talking to a friend today about taking a break from exam stress to read
some interesting books, and his reply was "pfftt..what a nerd!", which is the
usual response and I don't really think about it usually. But now I started
thinking- I don't have much of a social life, nor do I have lasting…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mi9j/are_books_keeping_you_alive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mi9j/are_books_keeping_you_alive/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:52:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was talking to a friend today about taking a break from exam stress to read some interesting books, and his reply was &amp;quot;pfftt..what a nerd!&amp;quot;, which is the usual response and I don&amp;#39;t really think about it usually. But now I started thinking- I don&amp;#39;t have much of a social life, nor do I have lasting friendships. College is still underway, so I am not making strides in my career. Essentially, I don&amp;#39;t have any billionaire-ish achievements in my kitty. I could but don&amp;#39;t want to club/party and so I am content at home. But I do wake up everyday with the goal of completing all my other work till a predetermined time and finally get on with my book (s). Do you, like me, also feel this way? If you do, is it healthy to have this sort of a dependence (the friend in question told me, I think playfully, that I shouldn&amp;#39;t be dependent on anything for my happiness)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please just tell me I am not alone. This is not like a phase for me. It is really a therapeutic activity-reading. I feel the happiest when books surround me and I need to be engaged in the task to feel like I did something with my day. I mean I will get on with other things in life too, but I don&amp;#39;t know whether as an old person, I&amp;#39;ll be very different or adventurous or doing exciting things. I&amp;#39;m happy and content where I am- cozy in my reading nook :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rise of BookTok: meet the teen influencers pushing books up the charts]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mwhi/the_rise_of_booktok_meet_the_teen_influencers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mwhi/the_rise_of_booktok_meet_the_teen_influencers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:46:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So, I just discovered P.G. Wodehouse.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I came across a random post on this sub regarding humorous books and P.G.
Wodehouse's Bertie and Jeeves series came up.

I don't think I laughed so much at a book in years! (The Code of the Woosters)
had to be the funniest book about a cow-creamer out there... probably the only
one but the point…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7miic/so_i_just_discovered_pg_wodehouse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7miic/so_i_just_discovered_pg_wodehouse/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:20:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across a random post on this sub regarding humorous books and P.G. Wodehouse&amp;#39;s Bertie and Jeeves series came up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think I laughed so much at a book in years! (The Code of the Woosters) had to be the funniest book about a cow-creamer out there... probably the only one but the point stands!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Right Ho, Jeeves) has a public speaking scene that... I&amp;#39;m sorry but if you don&amp;#39;t start chuckling at the start of it then something is wrong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me this was a very pleasant surprise. I wasn&amp;#39;t expecting much out of a series published 100 years back. So tell me, what book surprised you? A book you weren&amp;#39;t expecting to like but was forced by the author to change your mind?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I want to thank this sub!]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, right off the bat I need to be honest and mention that I had not read a
novel in 15 years until March of this year. Something changed during the
lockdown and a spark ignited within me for change so I became a member of this
subreddit. I need to thank all the people who contributed and posted…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7kejq/i_want_to_thank_this_sub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7kejq/i_want_to_thank_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:33:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, right off the bat I need to be honest and mention that I had not read a novel in 15 years until March of this year. Something changed during the lockdown and a spark ignited within me for change so I became a member of this subreddit. I need to thank all the people who contributed and posted their book suggestions making me click the save button so many times. Since joining this subreddit I have purchased and completed book number nine since March. I currently have a massive list of books I need still need to purchase, read, and eventually add to my new bookshelf. Thank you all for helping me focus on reading and making me splurge on a fancy new wood bookmark!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just read The Alchemist...]]></title><description><![CDATA[and I'm livid. I can't even express in words how much I hated that
baby's-first-philosophy BS. Why does everyone love this book so much? Can
somebody please explain to me what I was supposed to get out of this experience?
Am I just too stupid to "get it?" It's so... basic. So surface level.…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7iht5/i_just_read_the_alchemist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7iht5/i_just_read_the_alchemist/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 09:27:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;and I&amp;#39;m livid. I can&amp;#39;t even express in words how much I hated that baby&amp;#39;s-first-philosophy BS. Why does everyone love this book so much? Can somebody please explain to me what I was supposed to get out of this experience? Am I just too stupid to &amp;quot;get it?&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s so... basic. So surface level. What&amp;#39;s there to get?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is 'The Girl Who Played With Fire' and 'The Girl Who Kicked The Hornet's Nest worth reading after watching 'The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo' as a movie?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I watched David Fincher's one!

Will I be able to understand both of them? Or should I read all the 3 books.]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7eapz/is_the_girl_who_played_with_fire_and_the_girl_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7eapz/is_the_girl_who_played_with_fire_and_the_girl_who/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:26:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I watched David Fincher&amp;#39;s one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I be able to understand both of them?
Or should I read all the 3 books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[classics that aren’t too difficult to read]]></title><description><![CDATA[pls i am too small brained to absorb a lot of the must read classics but i
really wanna get into reading some. any suggestions?

EDIT: thanks for the suggestions so far!! to add, some genres i really like are
fiction, historical fiction, fantasy, thriller, a good mystery, and anything
that gets this…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o74wdv/classics_that_arent_too_difficult_to_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o74wdv/classics_that_arent_too_difficult_to_read/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:26:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;pls i am too small brained to absorb a lot of the must read classics but i really wanna get into reading some. any suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: thanks for the suggestions so far!! to add, some genres i really like are fiction, historical fiction, fantasy, thriller, a good mystery, and anything that gets this small brain thinking about its life for days after finishing a book. i also do not mind books that’ll make me sob :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Read Shakespeare's work for the first time. It is an entire EXPERIENCE and now a new HOBBY!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am 21 and I have never read Shakespeare before untill the last 3-4 days. I had
spent last days just reading and studying about Shakespeare's characters and
stories.

I had 2 of his work in my shelf bought at a sale, I started off with the
thinnest one. It was As you like it, It was a quick 2-3…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7f06f/read_shakespeares_work_for_the_first_time_it_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7f06f/read_shakespeares_work_for_the_first_time_it_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 05:15:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am 21 and I have never read Shakespeare before untill the last 3-4 days. I had spent last days just reading and studying about Shakespeare&amp;#39;s characters and stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had 2 of his work in my shelf bought at a sale, I started off with the thinnest one. It was As you like it, It was a quick 2-3 hour read but then I started to analyze all these dialogues and plot. I thought it was very funny and amazingly sarcastic on the tone. Rosalind is a great character, and so is Touchstone. If I am not mistaken As you like it is a metaphor about how life simply has no greater meaning, it&amp;#39;s ephemeral at best. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next I read A Midsummer Night&amp;#39;s Dream,  another comedy this at times did remind me of As you like it, I could see a similar notion about an entire different progression of story. I think out of two that I&amp;#39;ve read I see love is a theme he uses constantly,  and also comments on what makes people fall in love generally beauty and appearance. There was more of a romantic input on this story then the other one which was more playful. I really liked the play within the play. 
- Also, I think I can see Puck being close friends with Touchstone, not going to lie. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I will spend rest of my life reading and studying more and more about his work. I have found more of his book at a local bookstore.  And I have found Othello and Macbeth which I am going to read next.  I think Shakespeare is the foundation of many stories I have seen in my life before in various Tv shows and movies. It takes time but it totally worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turning the page on the pandemic: NYC libraries set to reopen]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7ddcl/turning_the_page_on_the_pandemic_nyc_libraries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7ddcl/turning_the_page_on_the_pandemic_nyc_libraries/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 02:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just finished read A Thousand Splendid Suns by Khaled Hosseini and honestly.....WHAT WAS THATTT]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I was halfway through the book, I couldn't resist the urge to spoil it for
myself on the internet. The book's just so compelling. Its honestly one of the
best - maybe even the best - books I've ever read. I feel so ignorant about not
knowing how severe Afghanistan's situation is. And the two…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7bvpi/i_just_finished_read_a_thousand_splendid_suns_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7bvpi/i_just_finished_read_a_thousand_splendid_suns_by/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 02:12:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was halfway through the book, I couldn&amp;#39;t resist the urge to spoil it for myself on the internet. The book&amp;#39;s just so compelling. Its honestly one of the best - maybe even the best - books I&amp;#39;ve ever read. I feel so ignorant about not knowing how severe Afghanistan&amp;#39;s situation is. And the two main characters are portrayed perfectly. Everything&amp;#39;s perfect about this book. My only &amp;quot;problem&amp;quot; with it was that it was so depressing. No seriously, it was so very depressing and sad and not like the other books I&amp;#39;ve read. No it was sad on a whole other level I never even knew existed. I&amp;#39;m still trying to process everything I read and I&amp;#39;m rambling and I dont think what I&amp;#39;m saying makes any sense but whatever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So, I hated the ending of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows]]></title><description><![CDATA[(possible spoilers)

I recently finished reading (for the first time) all the Harry Potter books, and
I really hated the very end. It seemed so rushed and it didn't go into detail on
how the deaths of major characters impacted their lives afterwards. To me, the
ending seemed like 'oh we won, now…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o784bj/so_i_hated_the_ending_of_harry_potter_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o784bj/so_i_hated_the_ending_of_harry_potter_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 01:15:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(possible spoilers) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading (for the first time) all the Harry Potter books, and I really hated the very end. It seemed so rushed and it didn&amp;#39;t go into detail on how the deaths of major characters impacted their lives afterwards. 
To me, the ending seemed like &amp;#39;oh we won, now let&amp;#39;s skip to nineteen years later.&amp;#39; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please tell me other people were disappointed with the ending of the books!? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;ve still never seen The deathly hallows part two movie)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Favorite audiobooks based on both book quality and narrator?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have 8 Audible book credits to use before canceling my account, which I would
like to do before my next credit hits on 7/1. So, I need to pick 8 books ASAP.
I’ve found some great books are ruined by a bad narrator, and some mediocre ones
shine with the right talent. What are the best books you…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o71jcj/favorite_audiobooks_based_on_both_book_quality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o71jcj/favorite_audiobooks_based_on_both_book_quality/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have 8 Audible book credits to use before canceling my account, which I would like to do before my next credit hits on 7/1. So, I need to pick 8 books ASAP. I’ve found some great books are ruined by a bad narrator, and some mediocre ones shine with the right talent. What are the best books you have listened to, based on both the quality of the book AND the narrator? I’m more interested in fiction, any genre. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Octavia Butler!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I wanted to bring attention to the fact that Octavia Butler's birthday was
earlier this week. She was a literary and sci fi visionary and trailblazer. She
was the first (and I think only) science fiction author to recurve the MacArthur
Genius grant. Her work and representation in the genre helped to…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o70knn/happy_birthday_to_octavia_butler/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o70knn/happy_birthday_to_octavia_butler/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 15:51:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to bring attention to the fact that  Octavia Butler&amp;#39;s birthday was earlier this week. She was a literary and sci fi visionary and trailblazer. She was the first (and I think only) science fiction author to recurve the MacArthur Genius grant.  Her work and representation in the genre helped to create the foundation for many of the fantastic new voices we have had the opportunity to enjoy in spec fiction, especially over the last decade. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started Parable of the Sower recently. The world is captivating, main character is strong, and themes are focused. I&amp;#39;m very much enjoying my first foray into Butler and plan to check out more of her work. I&amp;#39;ve now started the second book in the series and her ability to see the future we were heading towards is eerie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I highly encourage fans of her work and novices alike to pick up one of her books or short stories to experience her work and celebrate her contributions to literature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;There&amp;#39;s nothing new under the sun, but there are new suns.&amp;quot; - Octavia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What makes Agatha Christie's books so great ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started to read Murder on the Orient Express yesterday afternoon and just felt
compelled to read through well into the night.

This morning, I was surprised. Not only had it been a long time since a book
kept me up, my latest reads had not surprised me or made me laugh like
Christie's great story.…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6z9r4/what_makes_agatha_christies_books_so_great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6z9r4/what_makes_agatha_christies_books_so_great/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 13:44:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started to read &lt;em&gt;Murder on the Orient Express&lt;/em&gt; yesterday afternoon and just felt compelled to read through well into the night. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning, I was surprised. Not only had it been a long time since a book kept me up, my latest reads had not surprised me or made me laugh like Christie&amp;#39;s great story. This is not my first Christie, but I am surprised to have almost forgotten how this lady&amp;#39;s pen can snatch you out of everyday life for a moment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering what others like about Christie&amp;#39;s books, what they feel when reading them. If you care to share your experience that would be great !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, I think it narrows down to the simplicity of it all at the end... Although at first glance Christie&amp;#39;s murder mysteries seem complicated, they are supported by many simple facts of everyday life... Like nicknames can be misleading about gender, narrators aren&amp;#39;t always reliable, truth can be found behind some strong emotional reactions...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reading Catch-22. This paragraph is indecipherable to me.. can someone help explain?]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is from the first chapter and my second attempt at the book. The last time
I tried reading, I didn’t understand this paragraph and it put me off reading
the rest of the book for some reason. Paragraph is below:

“The colonel was in Communications, and he was kept busy day and night
transmitting…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6zf61/reading_catch22_this_paragraph_is_indecipherable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6zf61/reading_catch22_this_paragraph_is_indecipherable/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is from the first chapter and my second attempt at the book. The last time I tried reading, I didn’t understand this paragraph and it put me off reading the rest of the book for some reason. Paragraph is below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The colonel was in Communications, and he was kept busy day and night transmitting glutinous messages from the interior into square pads of gauze which he sealed meticulously and delivered to a covered white pail that stood on the night table beside his bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Most of Australia's Literary Heritage is Out of Print: The fight to rescue a nations lost books]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6v4ct/most_of_australias_literary_heritage_is_out_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6v4ct/most_of_australias_literary_heritage_is_out_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 11:58:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lord of the Rings]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know it is an unpopular opinion but I just finished the first two Lord of the
Rings books and it has been one of those rare instances where I enjoyed the
movies way more than the source books.

With the novels I just never felt the true desperation and overwhelming odds
facing the characters. The…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6qgth/lord_of_the_rings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6qgth/lord_of_the_rings/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 08:41:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know it is an unpopular opinion but I just finished the first two Lord of the Rings books and it has been one of those rare instances where I enjoyed the movies way more than the source books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the novels I just never felt the true desperation and overwhelming odds facing the characters. The book just felt more of a historical text; like reading a textbook vs watching an immersive documentary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some books where I can separate the text from the movie, especially when there is great divergence between the story  (King vs Kubrick&amp;#39;s The Shining) but the LotR movies are fairly faithful adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure I would have liked to see a bit of Tom Bombadil but I think the trade-offs with the movie interpretation are well worth it. One example: when Gandalf frees Theoden from the influence of Wormtongue - in the novels was a bit underwhelming, kind of like... hey, come get a few breaths of fresh air and a Snickers, you good boss? Look at the blue sky  (and his wrinkles smoothed. The end.) VS the movie interpretation when we can see the drastic  driving out of Sarumon&amp;#39;s influence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a hot take here and I&amp;#39;m not looking to change anyone&amp;#39;s opinion or try to take away from Tolkien&amp;#39;s masterpiece, I&amp;#39;m just surprised with myself that this has been my takeaway through the first two books and wanted to know your take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are names or some persons or places in books replaced with "–:" ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I recently started reading again after many many years. I've currently read the
Count of Monte Cristo and Frankenstein in English (both from project Gutenberg)
and then I'm currently reading Pride and Prejudice in Finnish. I think in all of
these books, there has been some names of places or persons…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6m2b1/why_are_names_or_some_persons_or_places_in_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6m2b1/why_are_names_or_some_persons_or_places_in_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 05:57:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently started reading again after many many years. I&amp;#39;ve currently read the Count of Monte Cristo and Frankenstein in English (both from project Gutenberg) and then I&amp;#39;m currently reading Pride and Prejudice in Finnish. I think in all of these books, there has been some names of places or persons that are replaced with &amp;quot;–:&amp;quot;. Example could be something like &amp;quot;They went to visit the McCoys in –:&amp;quot;. Why are some names hidden like this? I tried to Google but could not find any good search terms to find info. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[anyone know any good sci-fi and/or dystopian books which make you reflect on life]]></title><description><![CDATA[i want a book that really makes u think about life/humanity that has sci-fi
themes because that stuff is cool. im also looking for a book that will leave me
feeling very empty when i finish it and be stuck on my mind long after i finish]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6p9if/anyone_know_any_good_scifi_andor_dystopian_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6p9if/anyone_know_any_good_scifi_andor_dystopian_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 04:57:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i want a book that really makes u think about life/humanity that has sci-fi themes because that stuff is cool. im also looking for a book that will leave me feeling very empty when i finish it and be stuck on my mind long after i finish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Reading Habits Of Five Generations [Infographic]]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6g4qy/the_reading_habits_of_five_generations_infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6g4qy/the_reading_habits_of_five_generations_infographic/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 21:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What did you read and LOVE because it was suggested to you on this sub?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I come here almost every day -- and I sometimes wonder if lots of us take the
suggestions we all offer one another, and how they work out for the readers --
so, tell us... what super books, what great reading experiences did you have
because someone on this sub suggested it? What was the book or…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6e7xy/what_did_you_read_and_love_because_it_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6e7xy/what_did_you_read_and_love_because_it_was/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 20:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I come here almost every day -- and I sometimes wonder if lots of us take the suggestions we all offer one another, and how they work out for the readers -- so, tell us... what super books, what great reading experiences did you have because someone on this sub suggested it? What was the book or author you are grateful this sub introduced you to? Pass it on so others can know your reading joys and share in your favorite read from a recommendation. I figure if you loved it, maybe I will, too! I&amp;#39;m always looking for something new and great!   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll start with an author I had never considered, but was suggested to me on a thread I started a while back about gritty rural fiction. Someone suggested Michael Farris Smith&amp;#39;s Blackwood -- and I absolutely loved it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘I want heroes’: KU professor Devon Mihesuah pens 2nd novel featuring Native American detective]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6ctl8/i_want_heroes_ku_professor_devon_mihesuah_pens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6ctl8/i_want_heroes_ku_professor_devon_mihesuah_pens/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 19:42:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA['To Kill a Mockingbird' is very well crafted piece of literature]]></title><description><![CDATA[Completed just yesterday, took me 15 days but at the end I can say it proudly
that it deserve all the time and attention; it's such a masterpiece.

English being my second language, I must admit that it was a hard read for me,
nevertheless I enjoyed it. The way in which the author paints the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o68eyi/to_kill_a_mockingbird_is_very_well_crafted_piece/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o68eyi/to_kill_a_mockingbird_is_very_well_crafted_piece/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 17:44:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed just yesterday, took me 15 days but at the end I can say it proudly that it deserve all the time and attention; it&amp;#39;s such a masterpiece. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;English being my second language, I must admit that it was a hard read for me, nevertheless I enjoyed it. The way in which the author paints the incidents in the mind of the reader is so profound and indelible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from the writing style I loved the characters too, especially Atticus, his way of parenting is commendable. Also, the bonding between Scout and Jem is very warming, seemed to me like they are the epitome of the saying &amp;#39;made for each other&amp;#39; .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Americans are lucky to have it in their curriculum, like I had Gulliver&amp;#39;s Travel which I barely enjoyed myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Essential fun books.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ok, I want a book that’s fun to read. I have just come to a realization that
I’ve spent most of my life reading books that have received critical acclaim,
books that are “must reads” and books that I wanted to be able to say I read. I
have since realized that I just want to enjoy reading, and I’m…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o69u95/essential_fun_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o69u95/essential_fun_books/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, I want a book that’s fun to read. I have just come to a realization that I’ve spent most of my life reading books that have received critical acclaim, books that are “must reads” and books that I wanted to be able to say I read. I have since realized that I just want to enjoy reading, and I’m really not feeling academic right now. What are the first books that come to mind that just scream a great time. Can be anything I am not really pigeon holed into a certain genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What books blew you away that they made you question how it was possible that another human was able come up with these ideas?]]></title><description><![CDATA[For example, I'm reading through Kim Stanley Robinson's Mars trilogy and I am in
awe of how much scientific knowledge he has. The physics, chemistry, and biology
knowledge to convincingly tell the story of the terraforming of Mars and make it
seem so believable without any inexplicable technobabble…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o62xvt/what_books_blew_you_away_that_they_made_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o62xvt/what_books_blew_you_away_that_they_made_you/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, I&amp;#39;m reading through Kim Stanley Robinson&amp;#39;s Mars trilogy and I am in awe of how much scientific knowledge he has. The physics, chemistry, and biology knowledge to convincingly tell the story of the terraforming of Mars and make it seem so believable without any inexplicable technobabble is beyond my mind, and he&amp;#39;s done this in several of his other books too. Even more mainstream historical fiction novels like those of Bernard Cornwell, while excellent for what they are (fun, swashbuckling, hero adventures) I still can&amp;#39;t imagine knowing all the small details that go into period specific writing, even when it&amp;#39;s just formulaic fun books. Like I don&amp;#39;t know anything about Napoleonic clothing, travel, weaponry, the common sentiments people had, horses/livestock, the age of sail... so much detail. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What books rocked your perception like that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Audiobooks have ruined me]]></title><description><![CDATA[It started during lockdown. Whether I was cleaning, exercising, or curled up in
the fetal position under my bed, I could be listening to a wonderful story,
narrated by an amazing voice actor. Since then my bedside book stack has grown,
so I finally picked up The Blade Itself and, while I’m really…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o616p2/audiobooks_have_ruined_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o616p2/audiobooks_have_ruined_me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:28:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It started during lockdown. Whether I was cleaning, exercising, or curled up in the fetal position under my bed, I could be listening to a wonderful story, narrated by an amazing voice actor. Since then my bedside book stack has grown, so I finally picked up The Blade Itself and, while I’m really enjoying it, I’m also struggling. It’s harder to become immersed in the story, and I keep wanting to hear someone read it to me whenever I’m doing something that occupies my body but not my mind. I’m sure I’ll get back into the flow of it soon enough, but it is a strange feeling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The show Good Omens is a damn fine representation of the book.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just finished the series after reading the book, everything the show left out it
made up for with tasteful additions and an amazing performance by David Tennant
and Michael Sheen. I'm usually skeptical of movie adaptations, but I feel like I
could easily pass this off to someone who hasn't read the…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6c8um/the_show_good_omens_is_a_damn_fine_representation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6c8um/the_show_good_omens_is_a_damn_fine_representation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:15:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just finished the series after reading the book, everything the show left out it made up for with tasteful additions and an amazing performance by David Tennant and Michael Sheen. I&amp;#39;m usually skeptical of movie adaptations, but I feel like I could easily pass this off to someone who hasn&amp;#39;t read the book and feel like they&amp;#39;re missing out on only small details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Irish mythology]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am looking for a book about Irish Mythology that is as accessible as "Norse
Mythology" by Neil Gaiman. Maybe something that breaks down the four cycles into
detail. Any suggestions are welcome.]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o63moe/irish_mythology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o63moe/irish_mythology/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 13:24:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am looking for a book about Irish Mythology that is as accessible as &amp;quot;Norse Mythology&amp;quot; by Neil Gaiman. Maybe something that breaks down the four cycles into detail. Any suggestions are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bogus social media outrage is making authors change lines in their books now: The silly idea that a fictional character's statements reflect an author's actual beliefs is spreading]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6b6rr/bogus_social_media_outrage_is_making_authors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6b6rr/bogus_social_media_outrage_is_making_authors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 12:59:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After Piranesi]]></title><description><![CDATA[I received Piranesi for my birthday earlier this year and knew nothing about it.
This book blew me away. I now see it recommended on this sub and it always gets
lots of love. So my question is, for those of you who loved Piranesi, what else
has been on your top three list this year?]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o60zhs/after_piranesi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o60zhs/after_piranesi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 04:52:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I received Piranesi for my birthday earlier this year and knew nothing about it. This book blew me away. I now see it recommended on this sub and it always gets lots of love. So my question is, for those of you who loved Piranesi, what else has been on your top three list this year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Suggestions for 90 year old, refuses audio and e-books, w narrow interests]]></title><description><![CDATA[Primarily looking for mystery fiction. She finds "cozies" of any stripe insipid.
On the other end, can't be too dark/brutal/sexual. No vampires, paranormal,
sci-fi, or straight-up romance. Nothing historical before 1830's. She really
liked News of the World, which led to Elmer Kelton, which she also…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5xywq/suggestions_for_90_year_old_refuses_audio_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5xywq/suggestions_for_90_year_old_refuses_audio_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 03:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primarily looking for mystery fiction. She finds &amp;quot;cozies&amp;quot; of any stripe insipid. On the other end, can&amp;#39;t be too dark/brutal/sexual. No vampires, paranormal, sci-fi, or straight-up romance. Nothing historical before 1830&amp;#39;s.
She really liked News of the World, which led to Elmer Kelton, which she also liked. She also likes Southern U.S. settings or context, but not a requirement.
She reads 3-4 hours daily, and it&amp;#39;s exhausting to keep up. Loves Grisham (but read everything) &amp;amp; courtroom settings, but knows there&amp;#39;s not all that much of that that doesn&amp;#39;t have dark or brutal 2d story). Spies/Intrigue is ok, but no torture/terrorism.
Any suggestions appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are there any good non-fiction books on the Japanese yakuza?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Something about their history, their culture, practices, etc!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5t990/are_there_any_good_nonfiction_books_on_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5t990/are_there_any_good_nonfiction_books_on_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 01:31:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something about their history, their culture, practices, etc!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do you ever finish a book and then feel kinda dumb when you have to Google wtf just happened?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I finished reading "I'm Thinking of Ending Things" which overall I thought was
an interesting book, until I got to the end. I had no fucking clue what the
ending was trying to tell me had happened and what it meant for the previous
parts of the story that happened. I had to go to Google to figure…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5vf6q/do_you_ever_finish_a_book_and_then_feel_kinda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5vf6q/do_you_ever_finish_a_book_and_then_feel_kinda/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:21:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finished reading &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m Thinking of Ending Things&amp;quot; which overall I thought was an interesting book, until I got to the end. I had no fucking clue what the ending was trying to tell me had happened and what it meant for the previous parts of the story that happened. I had to go to Google to figure out what the hell had happened and that alone made me rethink if I can even say I enjoyed the book if after all that I couldn&amp;#39;t even figure out exactly how it ended on my own. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure if I was just having a bad day and my brain decided not to work, if the ending was in fact confusing, or I&amp;#39;m just getting dumber with age. I believe the book was made into a film or movie so I am curious as to how they did it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else read this book or are there books out there where you had to look up the ending to make sure you understood it right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just finished reading Animal Farm and would like to know what symbolisms weren't the most obvious.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I loved this satirical allegory and how Orwell brilliantly demonstrated the
dynamics of oppression, tyranny, propaganda through symbolism. I feel like its
lowkey just about failed revolutions everywhere. I was, in particular, wondering
what symbolisms I might have missed or maybe weren't the most…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5hps8/just_finished_reading_animal_farm_and_would_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5hps8/just_finished_reading_animal_farm_and_would_like/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I loved this satirical allegory and how Orwell brilliantly demonstrated the dynamics of oppression, tyranny, propaganda through symbolism. I feel like its lowkey just about failed revolutions everywhere. I was, in particular, wondering what symbolisms I might have missed or maybe weren&amp;#39;t the most obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very interested in discussing and knowing the different allegorical symbolisms of certain events other than the apparent representations of political figures, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jews in Space: On the Unsung History of Jewish Writers and the Birth of Science Fiction]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5px7r/jews_in_space_on_the_unsung_history_of_jewish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5px7r/jews_in_space_on_the_unsung_history_of_jewish/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:17:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Funniest book you’ve ever read?]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is the funniest book you have read? Please provide a line of plot summary
with no spoilers. Thanks!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5jhje/funniest_book_youve_ever_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5jhje/funniest_book_youve_ever_read/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 18:56:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the funniest book you have read? Please provide a line of plot summary with no spoilers. 
Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oscar Martinez's account of the El Salvador-US migrant trail in "The Beast" is one of most compelling and horrifying books I've ever read.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oscar Martinez is an award winning journalist from El Salvador and cofounder of
elfaro.net, an online newspaper in El Salvador. One of the most intrepid
journalists I've ever encountered in nonfiction, he beautifully captures both
the horrific conditions these migrants face while simultaneously…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5q7kn/oscar_martinezs_account_of_the_el_salvadorus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5q7kn/oscar_martinezs_account_of_the_el_salvadorus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 18:31:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oscar Martinez is an award winning journalist from El Salvador and cofounder of elfaro.net, an online newspaper in El Salvador. One of the most intrepid journalists I&amp;#39;ve ever encountered in nonfiction, he beautifully captures both the horrific conditions these migrants face while simultaneously highlighting the perseverance and bravery of the migrants he encounters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pardon my language, but he didn&amp;#39;t half-ass this story. He literally jumps the train (aka &amp;quot;The Beast), riding the same rails that have maimed and killed so many before him. He heads deep into cartel territory to try and capture the fear that they&amp;#39;ve gripped the nation with. He interviews trafficked women to try and bring their story to light. One of his contacts on the journey calls him as he&amp;#39;s captured by the cartel. He encounters corrupt officials and indifferent law enforcement officers. It&amp;#39;s an absolutely harrowing journey that he somehow captures with steadfast determination and grace. Anyone who is at all interested in this subject matter, or even if you&amp;#39;re not, should absolutely read this book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only regret I don&amp;#39;t have is that I don&amp;#39;t speak Spanish and had to read a translated version. Those who do speak the language, I&amp;#39;d recommend reading the original entitled &amp;quot;Los migrantes que no importan&amp;quot; (The Migrants Who Don&amp;#39;t Matter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books about mythology and tales]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi All!

I'm looking for books about Arabian mythology. I have already read "One thousand
and one nights", so if you have any recommandations, I will be happy to take a
look :)

I am also interested in other kinds of mythologies - Chinese, Japanese or
Nordic.]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5l1gx/books_about_mythology_and_tales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5l1gx/books_about_mythology_and_tales/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:16:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi All!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for books about Arabian mythology. I have already read &amp;quot;One thousand and one nights&amp;quot;, so if you have any recommandations, I will be happy to take a look :) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also interested in other kinds of mythologies - Chinese, Japanese or Nordic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why does everyone know of Norse mythology or Beowulf, but not the Finnish Kalevala? Well, there is FINALLY a series set in the Kalevala (the primary inspiration for Tolkien’s LOTR and Silmarillion) and I am so excited!]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Kalevala can be attributed, at least partially, to a ton of the archetypes
we see in fantasy today. In large part, that’s due to the fact it inspired
Tolkien and quite a few elements, and even some characters, of the Lord of the
Rings come right out of the Kalevala. Despite that, it seems like…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5ojwt/why_does_everyone_know_of_norse_mythology_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5ojwt/why_does_everyone_know_of_norse_mythology_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kalevala can be attributed, at least partially, to a ton of the archetypes we see in fantasy today. In large part, that’s due to the fact it inspired Tolkien and quite a few elements, and even some characters, of the Lord of the Rings come right out of the Kalevala. Despite that, it seems like no one knows about it! I remember reading Beowulf in school TWICE and never even knew about the Finnish epic poems. Is that common everywhere? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well now there’s at least a series set within that mythos. I only know about it from specific forums, but the book is Mark of the Bear Clan by David Schlaefer.  I hope these books make the Kalevala more well known, because I think it’s so underrepresented right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is a must read - The Westing Game]]></title><description><![CDATA[This book is my absolute favorite book in the world. It was written by Ellen
Raskin, a pronounced children's book illustrator. She did no drafts of the book
and no written infrastructure, yet she produced a very interconnected and
exquisite story. The book won the 1979 Newbery Medal.

The book…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o582r2/this_is_a_must_read_the_westing_game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o582r2/this_is_a_must_read_the_westing_game/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 07:59:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is my absolute favorite book in the world. It was written by Ellen Raskin, a pronounced children&amp;#39;s book illustrator. She did no drafts of the book and no written infrastructure, yet she produced a very interconnected and exquisite story. The book won the 1979 Newbery Medal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book follows 16 people who have chosen to become heirs of an estate worth over $200 million belonging to a famous game-loving millionaire, Sam Westing. No one knows why Sam Westing has chosen 16 seemingly random people to inherit his vast fortune, but that won&amp;#39;t stop him from playing one last game, even if it is from beyond the grave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genre: Mystery, Action&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Published 1978 by Ellen Raskin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookshop.org has free shipping today and tomorrow in response to Prime Day]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bookshop.org sources your purchases from your local bookstores, it's a great
service that helps support local businesses that are otherwise struggling with
online competition and e-books. For today and tomorrow they're offering free
shipping to compete with Amazon Prime Day. There's a book you can…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o55mm3/bookshoporg_has_free_shipping_today_and_tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o55mm3/bookshoporg_has_free_shipping_today_and_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 22:25:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bookshop.org sources your purchases from your local bookstores, it&amp;#39;s a great service that helps support local businesses that are otherwise struggling with online competition and e-books. For today and tomorrow they&amp;#39;re offering free shipping to compete with Amazon Prime Day. There&amp;#39;s a book you can contemplating, it&amp;#39;s a good time to snatch one up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books that make you feel happy and adventurous and make you fall in love with life again, without too much sadness or tragedy]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm going through a very tough breakup after a toxic relationship. Enough tears
have been shed, now I want to find that spark back and enjoy life again.

I prefer books without romance but if it's a small subplot it's ok. Please help
me out!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o4r0dx/books_that_make_you_feel_happy_and_adventurous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o4r0dx/books_that_make_you_feel_happy_and_adventurous/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:11:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going through a very tough breakup after a toxic relationship. Enough tears have been shed, now I want to find that spark back and enjoy life again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I prefer books without romance but if it&amp;#39;s a small subplot it&amp;#39;s ok. Please help me out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>