<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 17:55:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[-14万人：就业人数自4月份以来首次下降，失业率稳定在6.7%]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国就业增长自4月以来首次在决赛中转为负值
2020年的一个月，因为在过去的一年里震撼经济的大流行处理了
这是对劳动力市场的又一次打击。

劳工部于周五上午8：30发布了12月份的就业报告。
上午et.下面是主要的…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kt2jy0/140000payrolls_drop_for_the_first_time_since/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kt2jy0/140000payrolls_drop_for_the_first_time_since/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 15:39:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. job growth turned negative for the first time since April in the final month of 2020, as the pandemic that rocked the economy over the past year dealt yet another blow to the labor market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Labor Department released its December jobs report Friday morning at 8:30 a.m. ET. Here were the main results from the report, compared to consensus estimates compiled by Bloomberg:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Change in non-farm payrolls: -140,000 vs. +50,000 expected and a revised +336,000 in November&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unemployment rate: 6.7% vs. 6.8% expected and 6.7% in November&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Average hourly earnings, month-over-month: 0.8% vs. 0.2% expected and 0.3% in November&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Average hourly earnings, year-over-year: 5.1% vs. 4.5% expected and 4.4% in November&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/december-jobs-report-payrolls-coronavirus-pandemic-2020-labor-200212779.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/december-jobs-report-payrolls-coronavirus-pandemic-2020-labor-200212779.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于铀牛市的10个最常被问到的问题的答案]]></title><description><![CDATA[老实说，我没想到这么快就换了个职位，但是我
在过去的几天里，我收到了大量的信息和评论，所以我认为
有必要(哦，对那些给我加冕的人来说也是如此，比如“铀
“弥赛亚”，“铀大师”和“那个铀家伙”，我受宠若惊，…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kt36if/answers_to_the_10_most_asked_questions_regarding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kt36if/answers_to_the_10_most_asked_questions_regarding/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 15:39:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have to be honest, I didn’t expect to make another post so soon, but I have been flooded with messages and comments in the past few days, so I deemed it necessary (oh and also for the people crowning me things like the ‘uranium messiah’, ‘uranium guru’ and ‘that one uranium guy’, I am flattered, so thank you). Since my last post I have gotten a lot of questions regarding investing in uranium, the thesis, nuclear power, geopolitical changes and what the bear case for uranium is. So, I have decided to make a post highlighting the 10 most commonly asked questions so that more people can read my general answers to those and be informed about them. Here they are:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: Isn’t nuclear power being phased out around the world?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; 
A: No it isn’t, the US now has bipartisan support for it, Canada is looking at SMR technology, the UK intends to build small modular reactors, France has pushed back the phasing out of their nuclear power fleet from 2025 to 2035, several Eastern European countries are planning new reactors, China and the Middle-East are heavily pushing the construction of new power plants and there are many other examples of nuclear power being favored once more.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: What companies should I invest in within the uranium sector:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: Check my post history and the subsequent comments, especially from my last post, to get an idea of specific stock picks. I don’t want to violate any subreddit guidelines by posting them here. What I can post however, is that everyone should check out the URNM etf and their holdings to get started.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: Uranium has been trending downwards for almost a decade, who should it change now?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A: COVID-19 has really blown this market wide open and probably made sure this bull market started earlier by a margin of at least 1 or perhaps even 2 years. This rally was built on historic seasonality, bipartisan support from the US government and their strategic reserve bill, geopolitical backing of nuclear power, the closing of Cigar Lake (one of the world’s largest uranium mines) and the covering of uranium investing by some of the more mainstream investment outlets.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: Did I miss the run already?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: No, we are nowhere close to reaching the end of this run and we probably still have years left before we see anything resembling a top. There are 6 phases to this investment and we are only just now barely starting to see the end of phase 1. Remember, the spot price of uranium needs to go to approximately $67.10 a pound to incentivize enough new production to have even a shout of fixing the supply deficit, although common consensus within the sector is that we need even more than that and that the spot price can reach inflation adjusted new all-time highs (~170 dollars a pound)  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: Won’t solar, wind and hydro remove the need for nuclear power and thus uranium?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: No it won’t, see the first question, it is the best and safest form of baseload green power generation we have. But for the sake of argument, let’s say we only finish the reactors currently under construction and shut all further planning of new reactors. What will happens? Guess what, the supply deficit is still significant and the thesis will still play out. There is roughly a 57 million pound supply deficit and the spot market is getting thin with both Cameco and Kazatomprom (the world’s 2 largest producers) buying on the spot market. This can’t hold out for much longer, regardless of whether or not nuclear power plants keep being constructed.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: If the price shoots up, can’t people just find alternatives to uranium?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: No, for two key reasons. Firstly, as discussed above, we need nuclear power and we are starting to favor it more and more, which means we need a lot of uranium to meet demand. It is also impossible to change the fuel source in these nuclear reactors, you can’t just fill a plant up with natural gas or oil and hope it will do something. Secondly, unlike gas plants and coal plants, uranium is only a small portion of the total operational cost of these reactors. While with gas and coal it can be up to 80-85% of total costs, with uranium it is closer to 5-10%. This means that price can double and double again from here, without having an enormous impact on the total cost structure. Demand is relatively inelastic.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: When prices go up, can’t Kazakhstan or some other state owned entity not just flood the market with uranium and bring the price back down?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: They can’t and they won’t (Kazatomprom has tended to favor quality over quantity since 2017). First of all, it can take up to 2 years for uranium to go from the ground all the way through the enrichment process and be ready to be used as fuel. This means that even if it was possible and these companies start pumping out massive amounts of uranium, it would take up to 2 years for it to even be used as fuel. This is why security of supply needs to be met years in advance, so that a reactor does not sit there without a fuel source. In terms of the fuel cycle, we are already well into 2023. In terms of the development of new uranium sources to reach the market, we might be in 2030 already. A decade is tomorrow in uranium.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: But isn’t there hundreds of millions of pounds of uranium on earth?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: Yes there is, but no one is going to mine that at these prices. It takes many years to fully permit and construct a uranium mine in most countries. There might be plenty of supply out there, but there certainly isn’t a way to reach it easily without significant price incentive. Figures of 130 dollars or more per pound of uranium have been quoted as being needed to get to all these different sources of uranium.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: What are some catalysts to look out for in 2021?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: There are several. Biden’s implementation of the ‘green new deal’, reactors finishing construction and being activated (needing around 3x as much uranium to start with to build a fuel core), the closure of two uranium mines (Ranger and Cominak, a combined ~7 million pounds a year, gone), long term contract negotiations, spot price increasing to meet the  increase in enrichment prices of the past few years, institutional money getting into the sector and last but not least more news on the development and possible implementation of small modular reactor technology. All these catalyst make 2021 a year to look forward to for uranium.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: When should I sell my shares?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  
A: I can’t tell you that, tops are nearly impossible to call in any sector. However, to get an idea of how a uranium bull market can unfold, here is an article covering the entirety of the previous bull market which ended in 2007. Read it, take some notes, read it again and craft an exit strategy for yourself. This is not a lifetime hold, don’t fall in love with these stocks, there will be a time to sell.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thetideoffortune.com/would-you-have-made-a-fortune-in-uranium-part-1/%C2%A0&quot;&gt;https://thetideoffortune.com/would-you-have-made-a-fortune-in-uranium-part-1/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh and an extra point regarding whether or not you should buy into the sector after the recent price run up:
If you have not yet established a position in the market, I would advise to do so and scale in over time and extra on weakness. It is a volatile market and a pullback will come, the question is if that it today or next week after another 20% run up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there we have it, 10 questions about the sector and the thesis. I have tried my best to provide short and easy to understand answers and I hope it helps all of you. Make sure to always do your own due diligence and asses your own risk tolerances, so that you are not shaken out by the volatility of this sector. Best of luck with your investments. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[未来5-10年持有的最佳ETF和/或股票？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果这是一个问得太频繁的问题，我很抱歉。我最近开始
投资，我想知道下一步最好的ETF和股票
5-10年实现大规模增长/保证金。到目前为止我已经做到了。：方舟，ICLN，
OGIG、TAN、DIS、APPL、AMZN、PYPL、BABA、NIO。

(顺便说一句，这不是为了…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kst7vi/best_etfs_andor_stocks_to_hold_for_next_510_years/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kst7vi/best_etfs_andor_stocks_to_hold_for_next_510_years/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 15:39:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry if it’s a question that is asked too frequently. I recently started investing and I would like to know the best ETFs and Stocks to hold for next 5-10 years for massive growth/ guaranteed money. So far I have. : ARKK, ICLN, OGIG, TAN, DIS, APPL, AMZN, PYPL, BABA, NIO. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Btw, this is not for a Retirement account, it’s a taxable account)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PLTR登上月球，宝贝]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kszf9g/pltr_to_the_moon_baby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kszf9g/pltr_to_the_moon_baby/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 15:39:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币4.1万美元。这张桌子的空间快用完了。https://t.co/TVsx5ahhad TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347525554208206850</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347525554208206850</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 13:57:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin $41,000. Running out of room in this table. $BTC https://t.co/TVsx5ahhad</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在购买了一些自闭症患者将🚀🚀放在旁边的期权后，我的投资组合]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksptrl/my_portfolio_after_buying_options_that_some/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksptrl/my_portfolio_after_buying_options_that_some/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 13:57:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shopify撤下唐纳德·特朗普商店，投资者如何看待这一举措？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，Shopify今天将唐纳德·特朗普的商店从Shopify平台上撤下。作为
为我的业务使用Shopify的人，同时也是Shopify的投资者
我不太喜欢这一举动。

这也是公司立场的改变，就像之前Shopify首席执行官说的那样
这不是他的职责让道德…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksnskv/shopify_removes_donald_trumps_stores_what_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksnskv/shopify_removes_donald_trumps_stores_what_do/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 12:53:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So Shopify today removed Donald Trump&amp;#39;s stores from the Shopify platform. As someone who uses Shopify for my business as well as an investor in Shopify I&amp;#39;m not a huge fan of this move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is also a change in the companies stance as previously the Shopify CEO said it&amp;#39;s not his place to make moral judgements about who can and can&amp;#39;t have a store. It&amp;#39;s also important to point out Trump love him or hate him didn&amp;#39;t violate Shopify TOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big discussion in the world of eCommerce ie Shopify users and customers is owning your platform ie building your own website vs leasing ie something like Shopify or BigCommerce. While the movement is to a leased model hence Shopify&amp;#39;s success, there is something to be said for not being reliant on a third parties rules or decisions which is exactly what happenned here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone running a business which is in the very least controversial will find this troubling that Shopify if they disagree with your politics, your niche, your products, your actions could take you down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally speaking I think this will go over pretty smoothly as everyone hates Trump and the media isn&amp;#39;t gonna take up on this issue but as a Shopify user and investor I find this troubling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉泡沫太疯狂了]]></title><description><![CDATA[祝贺那些坚持了这么久的人，但不要试图证明
TSLA通过论证基本面来定价。这只股票与现实脱节了很长一段时间。
很久以前，最疯狂的是那些仍然持有它的人相信
不然的话。

只有在空头挤压…的情况下，该股才会走高]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksxrno/tesla_bubble_is_insane/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksxrno/tesla_bubble_is_insane/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 10:52:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to those who have held for this long, but don’t try to justify TSLAs price by arguing fundamentals. This stock disconnected from reality a long time ago, and the craziest part is the people still holding it believe otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock will only go higher if the short squeeze continues, but all short squeezes eventually end violently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volkswagen went from $85 to $635 in 18 months. It took 6 months to collapse to $159 and then another year to get back to $65.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who don’t know history are doomed to repeat it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众在挪威市场电动车销量超越特斯拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威电动汽车市场受到密切关注，因为它们作为一个国家
采用电动汽车和充电可用性的先驱和爱好者。

2019年，特斯拉在挪威电动车销量排名第一。2020年，大众将夺得第一名
斑点。特斯拉仍然位居第二。

德语…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksr1ht/volkswagen_overtakes_tesla_in_the_norwegian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksr1ht/volkswagen_overtakes_tesla_in_the_norwegian/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 10:52:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Norwegian electric car market is closely observed since they as a nation are pioneers and enthusiasts for adopting electric cars and charging availability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2019, Tesla was the #1 in the norwegian e-car sales. In 2020, VW takes the #1 spot. Tesla remains second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;German Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.deraktionaer.de/artikel/mobilitaet-oel-energie/e-autos-hier-hat-volkswagen-tesla-schon-ueberholt--20223261.html&quot;&gt;https://www.deraktionaer.de/artikel/mobilitaet-oel-energie/e-autos-hier-hat-volkswagen-tesla-schon-ueberholt--20223261.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还记得人们嘲笑@CathieDWood和@ARKInvest在2018年说美国电话服务水平协议有朝一日会达到4,000美元吗？

那天就是今天。

https://t.co/QeWutjhpoJ]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347455335641001989</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347455335641001989</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 08:59:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>RT @DriveTeslaca: Remember when people laughed at @CathieDWood and @ARKInvest for saying in 2018 $TSLA would one day reach $4,000? 

That d…</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一个真正的自闭症患者。美国电话服务级别协议]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksv6fe/a_true_autist_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksv6fe/a_true_autist_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 08:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所以你的意思是.美国电话服务级别协议1000C？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kslu8i/so_what_youre_saying_is_tsla_1000c/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kslu8i/so_what_youre_saying_is_tsla_1000c/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 08:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果特斯拉是一个每天盈利1美元的香蕉摊位呢？分析]]></title><description><![CDATA[假设斯奈德拥有一个香蕉摊位，每天盈利1美元。

查克想买下斯奈德香蕉摊50%的股份。查克问自己，什么？
买这个香蕉摊的一半价格合理吗？

如果查克花500美元买下一半的香蕉摊位：

*香蕉摊总市值：…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kshqwi/what_if_tesla_was_a_banana_stand_that_made_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kshqwi/what_if_tesla_was_a_banana_stand_that_made_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 08:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lets say Sneed owns a Banana Stand that makes a profit of $1 per day.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck wants to buy a 50% share in Sneeds Banana Stand. Chuck asks himself, what is a reasonable price to pay for half of this banana stand?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Chuck paid $500 for half of the Banana Stand:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Banana Stand market value: $1000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Banana Stand earnings for last fiscal year: $365&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price to profit ratio (P/E ratio): 2.73&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time to recoup his $500 investment: 2.73 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck is willing to take on a little more risk than this. Hell, this Banana Stand really shows a lot of promise! And Sneed, well, Sneed is like a genius! He had a great Banana Stand over on the other side of town that sold tons of bananas. What if Chuck paid ... $25,000 ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Banana Stand market value: $50,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Banana Stand earnings for last fiscal year: $365&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio: 137&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time to recoup his $25,000 investment: 137 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck doesn&amp;#39;t expect to hold his investment for 137 years. He believes that what&amp;#39;s really important is not the money coming into the Banana Stand, but rather how other people like Chuck &lt;em&gt;feel&lt;/em&gt; about the Banana Stand. See chuck is a growth investor - not a value investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chuck feels really good about the future of this Banana Stand. It&amp;#39;s only making $1 a day right now, but man Sneed is going to take this Stand places. Chuck decides to go all in and pay $289,080 for a 50% share in the Banana Stand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Banana Stand market value: $578,160&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Banana stand earnings for last fiscal year: $365&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio: 1584&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time to recoup his $289,080 investment: 1584 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5vjt2r26zx961.png?width=632&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=69814500b8efd7f7a233e8fa7f0c6cd63a60c382&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/5vjt2r26zx961.png?width=632&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=69814500b8efd7f7a233e8fa7f0c6cd63a60c382&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: Nice awards fuckin soyboys stop giving your money to Reddit you dumbasses &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的2021年投资组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[虽然晚了一周，但我想分享我的2021年投资组合，以供记录之用
对任何感兴趣的人。我的目标是平衡这个投资组合中的风险
一些成长型名字和传统剧目。归根结底，我要把我的钱
在不同的…中(在我看来)最高质量的公司]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kspxe3/my_2021_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kspxe3/my_2021_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 06:00:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Albeit a week late, I want to share my 2021 portfolio for documentation purposes and for whoever is interested. I aimed to balance risk in this portfolio with some growth names and legacy plays. Down to brass tacks, I am putting my money in the highest quality companies (in my view) across a diverse set of industries I find attractive. Some of these names are overvalued in the short term. However, I have realized I am not in the business of beating Wall Street’s pricing, but would rather hold high-quality companies that I believe will grow faster that the market in the long term. In other words, I am totally fine paying a short-term premium for growth and quality. Below is a summary of the portfolio and big picture reasoning behind each investment. I&amp;#39;m definitely open to any feedback. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Company&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Ticker&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Entry Price&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Exposure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;ARK Genomic Revolution ETF&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;ARKG&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$93.26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;6.60%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;CrowdStrike&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;CRWD&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$211.82&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;11.78%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Disney&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;DIS&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$181.18&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;10.53%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Enphase Energy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;ENPH&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$175.47&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;7.98%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Evolution Gaming Group&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;EVVTY&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$101.02&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;12.77%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;FB&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$273.16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;11.05%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Redfin&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;RDFN&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$68.63&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;10.41%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Teladoc&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;TDOC&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$199.96&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;9.60%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Sea Ltd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;SE&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$199.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;14.09%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Waste Connections&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;WCN&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$102.57&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5.19%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARK Genomic Revolution ETF (BATS: ARKG) -&lt;/strong&gt; Invests in companies advancing genomics. The companies held in ARKG may develop, produce or enable: CRISPR, Targeted Therapeutics, Bioinformatics, Molecular Diagnostics, Stem Cells, Agricultural Biology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovative industry. Since 2003 the cost to sequence a human genome has dropped from nearly $3bn to less than $1,000. ARK believes that as costs continue to drop, genomic sequencing will become a standard of care in oncology. It will introduce more science into  healthcare decision making, enable personalized medicine, and accelerate drug discovery. ARK estimates that genomic sequencing revenues will grow 43% at an annual rate, from $3.5bn last year to $21bn in 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cathie Wood. She’s a beast stock picker. Out of all the  ETFs she runs, her closest competitor trailed by 60%. Her worst ETF still  doubled investors&amp;#39; money. Her strategy is to make investments into companies that she considers incredibly transformational and she has seen success doing it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CrowdStrike (NASDAQ: CRWD) -&lt;/strong&gt; Cybersecurity technology company that provides endpoint security, threat intelligence, and cyber attack response services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Best in class technology. Remember about a week ago a bunch of Russian hackers breached SolarWinds? The same hackers also tried to hack CrowdSrike at the same time but were unsuccessful. I’ve wandered on to a bunch of cybersecurity forums, and the general consensus is CrowdStrike has developed the best cybersecurity solution by miles. CRWD is the undisputed leader in cybersecurity. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Pick-and-shovel” investment into the world’s increasing digitization. Even in the absence of COVID, cybersecurity remains a key component of the world’s increasing digitization as cyberthreats have been an ongoing issue from the onset of the internet. In the last decade we have seen a bunch of hacks where companies have exposed sensitive customer information. It seems companies are just starting to realize the importance of cybersecurity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disney (NYSE: DIS) -&lt;/strong&gt; Worldwide entertainment company that you all are probably familiar with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reopening trade. In 2019, parks generated 45% of total operating income for DIS. Full reopening and attendance in parks will be slow, but certainly benefit DIS when it happens. The company has been executing on several other segments in the meantime (i.e. streaming). It has proved competitive, increasing the margin of safety if parks take longer to reopen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast-growing streaming division. DIS has proved agile as it successfully launched a streaming service, Disney+, that has already gained 86mn+ subscribers which was the company’s original 5 year target. This is promising as it shows management can adapt to rapidly changing technology trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enphase Energy (NASDAQ: ENPH) -&lt;/strong&gt; Designs and manufactures software-driven home energy solutions that span solar generation, home energy storage and web-based monitoring and control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift to clean energy; ENPH emerging as market leader. Going into 2021, sentiments towards solar have been at an all time high. This trend is expected to continue, especially after the Georgia run-off results. Solar firms are expected to benefit from extended tax incentives on both the consumer and producer ends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technological advantage. ENPH has developed the industry leading solution and is rapidly taking market share from its primary competitor, SolarEdge. Pricing reflects this, but it&amp;#39;s expected to continue. Among key competitors, Enphase has been one of the lowest cost producers. Its low-cost structure is a major contributing factor to its improving margins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evolution Gaming Group (OTC: EVVTY) -&lt;/strong&gt; Swedish company that develops, produces, markets and licenses integrated B2B live casino solutions for gaming operators. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early mover advantage. Evolution’s lack of competition enables it to rapidly grow in new markets and create a loyal customer base, with high switching costs. The company has effectively grown EBITA margins from 41.6% in 1Q18 to 64.8% in 3Q20. Margin expansion is expected to continue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Massive untapped markets. Europe is estimated to be around $2.5bn (EVVTY has 50% market share), Asian market is ~15x the size of Europe (150% YoY growth for EVVTY in Asia). North America’s market is ~$210mn, a 42% increase YoY, with NJ and PA the only states currently operating (NY looks promising). Management thinks the US will be the largest in the long-term. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undetected from Wall Street. Evolution has almost no analyst coverage in the US and very minimal coverage in Europe, presenting opportunity for additional growth as institutional money managers recognize this opportunity and draw attention to the stock. Additionally, Evolution has a founder-led management team that is highly aligned with shareholders (mgmt owns over 30% of the stock).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook (NASDAQ: FB) -&lt;/strong&gt; Enables people to connect through devices. It’s products include Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, WhatsApp and Oculus. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zuck. It’s not a question of who is the next Jobs/Bezos/Gates/Zuck, because Zuck is super young. He has a history of being able to execute: IG acquisition / transition from desktop to mobile /  denying multiple acquisition opportunities in his twenties. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undervalued. FB is the cheapest among the FAANG stocks, yet has some of the highest growth rates. This is mainly because of its continuous political scandals. With Trump out of office, I think FB has a chance to stay out of trouble and start to realize higher multiples.  The antitrust lawsuit is not a threat imo, it is actually an opportunity. If the govt forces FB to break up, we would get shares in the spin-offs, which would be valued at a higher multiple than FB. For example, if Instagram spun off from FB and traded at the same multiple as SNAP, Instagram’s market cap would be larger than FB’s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redfin Corporation (NASDAQ: RDFN) -&lt;/strong&gt; Provides residential real estate brokerage services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digitization of Real Estate (i.e. “iBuying”). Technology in RE is moving from being informational to transactional. Redfin’s iBuying service is dubbed “RedfinNow.” The service basically buys homes from sellers looking for a quick and convenient sale (close deals within 10-30 days). This segment isn’t profitable yet as it is just getting started, but promising as the management adapts to technology trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inter-US Migration and housing outlook. People are moving out of the cities because of COVID / trying to avoid taxes / etc. which increases demand for Redfin’s services. With interest rates extremely low (and no expectation for them to increase), homebuying demand should continue to grow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RDFN most attractively valued compared to Z and OPEN, with the most upside potential given its market cap ~$7bn. Some are predicting RDFN might start offering rental services as well. RDFN has the best LT margin potential. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teladoc Health (NYSE: TDOC) -&lt;/strong&gt; Provides virtual healthcare services on a B2B basis to its clients and provides services to consumers directly and through channel partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive positioning in industry ripe for disruption. Healthcare is a huge market yet to be significantly disrupted. COVID has accelerated this disruption. Providers who were once opposed to telemedicine now realize its benefits and several regulatory changes are promising for telemedicines growth potential. Medicare and other government-sponsored coverage is expected to include telemedicine benefits, increasing TDOC’s TAM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Livongo acquisition. From the consumer POV, this will increase access to healthcare at a lower cost. Teladoc will have access to a larger amount of data it can interpret to refine its services and monetization strategies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sea Ltd (NYSE: SE) -&lt;/strong&gt; Digital entertainment, electronic commerce, and digital financial services. The Company operates three business segments: Garena, Shopee, and SeaMonkey. The Company’s digital entertainment business, Garena, is a global game developer and publisher with a presence in Southeast Asia, Taiwan, and Latin America. Garena provides access to mobile and personal computer online games. Shopee provides users with a shopping environment that is supported by integrated payment, logistics, fulfillment, and other value-added services. SeaMonkey business is a digital financial services provider. SeaMonkey offers e-wallet services, payment processing, credit related digital financial offerings, and other financial products. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diversified consumer internet company with market-leading position. Sea caters to Southeast Asia and Taiwan, providing its online gaming, e-commerce, and payment platforms. Shopee has overtaken competitors, it is widening its market share lead. ESports is a rapidly growing market (15.7% YoY to $1.1bn in 2020) and Sea is outpacing market growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pay for quality. The best companies keep going up for years in a row, and I think Sea is in the early stages of being classified as such a company. It’s worth $100bn but has effectively proved its ability to identify opportunities and expand business lines. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Still early stages of developing its consumer banking business, so we get the security of a bigger, established company with upside for an additional, lucrative business line such as fintech.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waste Connections Inc. (NYSE: WCN) -&lt;/strong&gt; Waste services company that provides non-hazardous waste collection, transfer, disposal and recycling services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recession resilient; re-opening trade. The waste management industry is recession resilient, it will always be around. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-hazardous waste collection. With a progressive government likely to push climate initiatives, recycling and non-hazardous waste collection are likely to benefit on the back end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WCN has a large moat; there isn’t much of a competitive threat the way the industry operates. Management’s strategy is to generally only spend what FCF is available. This enables the company to make acquisitions while handling its debt load. Great for stable growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. I have two other accounts - one with about 40 growth stocks and another with about 10 big names / ETFs. However, this portfolio has the largest allocation for 2021. My first time trying a more concentrated approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有谁今天过得很开心？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我只想知道今天有没有其他人度过了令人惊叹的绿色一天。因为我起床了
今天6%(这是我得到的最高利率)，这要归功于电动汽车和可再生能源股票
这是我的。令我有点震惊的是，今天是所有主要股票事业的绿色日
昨天在华盛顿发生的事。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksqmy2/anyone_else_had_a_really_great_day_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksqmy2/anyone_else_had_a_really_great_day_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 04:50:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just wanna know if anyone else had an amazing green day today. Cause I am up 6% today(which is the highest I ever gotten)thanks to EV&amp;#39;s and renewable stocks I own. I am bit shocked that today was a green day across all major stocks cause of what happened yesterday in D.C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不用担心TSLA估值：DD Inside]]></title><description><![CDATA[一只股票/资产只有在我不可避免地买入信息时才会下跌。

到目前为止，我没有购买特斯拉股票的打算。

因此，您的投资是百分之百安全的。

不要担心一辆1510.75千瓦的KGV]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksqwu8/dont_worry_about_tsla_valuation_dd_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksqwu8/dont_worry_about_tsla_valuation_dd_inside/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 03:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stock/asset only drops in value when I inevitably FOMO into it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus far I have zero intention of buying Tesla shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your investment is therefore 100% safe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do not worry about a KGV of 1510.75&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我做到了。我在9月份设定了一个目标，就是要从这个洞里爬出来。这就是，两年后我在股票市场赚了187.29美元。谢谢WSB。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksntls/i_did_it_i_set_a_goal_in_september_to_claw_my_way/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksntls/i_did_it_i_set_a_goal_in_september_to_claw_my_way/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 03:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国在紧要关头降临了！插头🚀]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kseh18/south_korea_came_in_clutch_plug/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kseh18/south_korea_came_in_clutch_plug/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 03:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉从租借中获得的收益yolo谢谢你爸爸]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksheq5/tesla_gainz_from_a_loan_yolo_thank_u_papa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksheq5/tesla_gainz_from_a_loan_yolo_thank_u_papa/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 03:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[没有炒作的比特币涨势让我紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[当时，它显然是一种泡沫。就连你的出租车司机都知道密码的事。
现在我觉得几乎没有人谈论比特币，更不用说意识到这件疯狂的事了。
集合。我的印象对吗？

这让我相信，一定是机构在抬高价格。
这一次不同于零售…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksl9fh/bitcoin_rally_without_hype_is_making_me_nervous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksl9fh/bitcoin_rally_without_hype_is_making_me_nervous/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 02:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back then it was clearly a bubble. Even your taxi driver knew all about crypto. Now I feel barely anyone talks about bitcoin let alone is aware of this insane rally. Is my impression right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That makes me believe that it must be institutions that are pumping the price this time unlike retail investors last time. Why would they do that? Are they worried / know something about traditional currencies going down the drain?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add to that the insane valuations of some companies on the stock market (TSLA, DASH, SNOW... I&amp;#39;m looking at you) it makes me really nervous something is about to go down. Anyone else feels uneasy with bitcoin around $40k?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪个杰夫？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kslndd/jeff_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kslndd/jeff_who/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 02:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币年复一年的回报。

https://t.co/n0xF6Iku9P TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347247618917883906</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347247618917883906</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 01:01:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>RT @charliebilello: Bitcoin returns by year...

$BTC https://t.co/n0xF6Iku9P</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉市值超过Facebook，成为全球第五大上市公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据雅虎财经报道，截至撰写本文时，特斯拉的市值为765.5美元
而脸书的是765.0美元。现在只有苹果、微软、亚马逊和Alphabet
市值比特斯拉大。这可能会持续很长时间，也可能不会持续很长时间，但在
我的观点是，无论哪种方式，这都是重要的。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kski6n/tesla_passes_facebook_in_market_cap_becoming_5th/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kski6n/tesla_passes_facebook_in_market_cap_becoming_5th/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 01:01:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of writing this, per Yahoo Finance, Tesla’s Market cap stands at $765.5 bil and Facebook’s is $765.0 bil. Now only Apple, Microsoft, Amazon, and Alphabet are larger than Tesla by market cap. This may or may not hold for long, but in my opinion it’s significant either way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[截至周四上午，埃隆·马斯克以1,885亿美元成为全球首富。

“太奇怪了，”他在推特上写道。https://t.co/MIDlBEpTyI]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347307251271393283</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347307251271393283</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 23:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>As of Thursday morning, Elon Musk was the wealthiest person in the world with $188.5 billion. 

&quot;How strange,&quot; he tweeted. https://t.co/MIDlBEpTyI</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普500指数有史以来首次收在3800点上方。

斯普林特px]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347287466487787522</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347287466487787522</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 23:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The S&amp;amp;P 500 closed above 3800 for the first time ever. 
 
$SPX</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年-2022年的股票：)挑选3只你认为会在新的一年里成为大玩家的股票。到今年年底，我们就会知道什么是陈年好的了！我将从下面的精选开始，如果你愿意，可以打分。“通过致富来解决你的问题”]]></title><description><![CDATA[美价DQ/大全新能源ICLN/ETF网络版Cibr/ETF
安全性

奖金：净额

请让我知道你们2020年的库存计划是什么。如果你有什么想法
成长型股票！

奖金奖励NVIDIA]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksl51y/stocks_for_20212022_pick_3_stocks_you_believe_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksl51y/stocks_for_20212022_pick_3_stocks_you_believe_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 23:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DQ / Daqo New Energy
ICLN / Etf at a beautiful price
CIBR / Etf for cyber security&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus: NET&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please let me know what your Stock plans are for 2020. And if you have any ideas for growth stocks! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BONUS BONUS
NVIDIA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[抱歉，我出去了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在看到TSLA今天登陆火星时，它突破了800美元大关，我得到了一个
有点担心。我的内心有一种奇怪的感觉。我知道下一站会是
朱庇特，我只是.情不自禁地觉得“我们到了”。

因此，在经过长时间和艰苦的考虑，来回考虑之后，我决定…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksod8l/sorry_im_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksod8l/sorry_im_out/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 23:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing TSLA land on Mars today when it crossed the $800 mark, I got a little worried. I had a weird feeling in my gut. I knew the next stop would be Jupiter, I just... couldn’t help but feel like ”we had arrived”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after thinking about it long and hard, going back and forth, I decided to cash out and get off this reusable masterpiece of a rocketship. It had taken me and my SO safely from Earth to Mars and it was time to get off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money we made from TSLA helped us make a down payment on our first apartment, so it went to good use. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Selling TSLA felt bitter sweet as I love this company, I have a man crush on Papa Musk and I was planning initially to hold my dear TSLA shares “forever”. However, I’m forever grateful to this company as it made buying an apartment possible for me. Believing in it paid off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you Elon. Thank you TSLA. ❤️&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thank you guys for all the comments! It is crazy how emotionally attached you can get to a stock. I’ve just spent countless hours studying this company and Elon. I believed in it when so many said I was crazy (or thought it). Elon is a true visionary and I truly believe TSLA is going to continue on its path to greatness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I wasn’t trying to time the top at all. It’s near impossible to do anyway. I just saw an opportunity, went with my gut feeling and seized it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1.股票：创历史新高
2.房价：创历史新高
3、公司债收益率：创历史新低
4.按揭利率：创历史新低
5.美联储：我们需要更多年的零利率和债券购买来提振资产价格和通胀。
6.比特币：创历史新高]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347307160305360896</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347307160305360896</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>1. Stocks: all-time highs
2. Home prices: all-time highs
3. Corporate bond yields: all-time lows
4. Mortgage rates: all-time lows
5. Fed: we need many more years of 0% rates and bond buying to boost asset prices &amp;amp; increase inflation.
6. Bitcoin: all-time highs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[公牛赚钱，猪赚钱，熊被宰杀。

(我知道这不会很陈旧)]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347291646048804871</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347291646048804871</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bulls make money, pigs make money, bears get slaughtered.

(I know this won&apos;t age well)</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉刚刚超过Facebook，成为美国第五大公司。7650亿美元的市值，高于一年前的850亿美元。美国电话服务级别协议脸书

图表通过@ycharts https://t.co/lJo1xvbyO6]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347260302900011012</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347260302900011012</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tesla just passed Facebook to become the 5th largest company in the US. $765 billion market cap, up from $85 billion 1 year ago. $TSLA $FB

Chart via @ycharts https://t.co/lJo1xvbyO6</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#Long Live The Meme🚀]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksldfd/long_live_the_meme/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksldfd/long_live_the_meme/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部对波音公司罚款超过25亿美元，指控其在737 MAX坠机事件中共谋欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/07/doj-fines-boeing-over-2point5-billion-charges-it-with-fraud-conspiracy-over-737-max-crashes.html

>司法部周四表示，波音同意支付超过2.5美元
>10亿美元解决因其最畅销产品崩溃而引发的刑事指控
>737Max…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksmze6/doj_fines_boeing_over_25_billion_charges_it_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksmze6/doj_fines_boeing_over_25_billion_charges_it_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/07/doj-fines-boeing-over-2point5-billion-charges-it-with-fraud-conspiracy-over-737-max-crashes.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/07/doj-fines-boeing-over-2point5-billion-charges-it-with-fraud-conspiracy-over-737-max-crashes.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Department of Justice on Thursday said Boeing agreed to pay more than $2.5 billion to resolve criminal charges stemming from crashes of its best-selling 737 Max airplanes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每个人都别再提TSLA了，把收益塞进去]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksiu44/everyone_shut_up_about_tsla_and_plug_gains/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksiu44/everyone_shut_up_about_tsla_and_plug_gains/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[技术分析系列1：烛台，它们是什么，我如何使用它们？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，互联网，

这篇文章是我将要做的一系列文章的第一部分，我将概述一些
我用来对图表进行技术分析的基本工具、技巧和技巧。

我认为最好的起点是开头，所以书名是
今天的帖子是：“烛台，它们和…是什么？]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksew9c/technical_analysis_series_1_candlesticks_what_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksew9c/technical_analysis_series_1_candlesticks_what_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Internet,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post is the first part in a series I will be doing outlining some of the basic tools, tips, and techniques I use to conduct technical analysis on charts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I figured that the best place to start is at the beginning, so the title of today&amp;#39;s post is: &amp;quot;Candlesticks, what are they and how do I use them?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this post I will present some of the basic elements of candle sticks, a few noteworthy candle stick formations, and introduce some other relevant terminology. In addition, this post will be helpful in generally explaining how to read a chart at a very basic level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A candlestick tells the story of the price action for the asset during the relevant timeframe you have selected for your chart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While they may not look like much to the untrained eye, markets are run off of human emotion, primarily fear and greed. Candlesticks can give valuable insight into what the mood of the market was during a given timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Candlesticks vs other types of Charts?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are plenty of valid ways to look at historical price data for assets:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bar charts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;line charts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;heikin-ashi charts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The reasons I prefer candlesticks are:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;can easily visually see where the candle opened&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;can easily visually see where the candle closed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;can easily visually see where the candle &amp;quot;wicked&amp;quot; up or down to and was rejected from

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being able to easily identify these data points allows for a technical trader to more quickly assess the relevant info required for assessing risk and putting on trades.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here is a 1 week (&amp;quot;1W&amp;quot;) timeframe (&amp;quot;TF&amp;quot;) chart of Starbucks:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/gmzRPrY&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/gmzRPrY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As explained in the graphic:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The asset is generally listed in the top left of the chart followed by the TF of the candles on the chart.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since this is a 1W TF chart of Starbucks that means that each red or green candle on the chart represents 1 week of price action.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candle periods are broken into what is considered high TF, medium TF, and low TF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The general rule of thumb is that looking at a high TF candle chart reduces the risks of getting &amp;quot;faked out&amp;quot; by bull traps, bear traps, or otherwise sideways choppy action (future posts will touch on what these are if you&amp;#39;d like to know more).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essentially, it would take much more sustained application of capital to lay such a trap for a 1 week period vs. a 1 hour period. Therefore, high TF charts are much more reliable for longer term analysis. The downside to high TF candles though is that they are obviously less responsive to explosive and sudden price action brought on by a catalyst or other outside event.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On equities the TF breakdown is generally:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High TF: 12 month candles, 6 month candles, 3 month candles, 1 month candles, 2 week candles, and 1 week candles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medium TF: 3 day candles, 2 day candles, and 1 day candles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low TF: 4 hour candles, 2 hour/90 minute candles, 1 hour candles, 30 minute candles, 15 minute candles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical traders will run all types of TF&amp;#39;s on candles and these are just some of the most common examples. Furthermore , the most relevant or &amp;quot;favorite&amp;quot; TF&amp;#39;s of technical traders will change as algorithms are adjusted across the market, thereby requiring the trader to adjust as relevant market data is analyzed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here is another shot of the 1W TF chart of Starbucks with some additional info to cover candle stick bodies and wicks:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/IUNET9x&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/IUNET9x&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As explained in the graphic:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The body of the candle is the solid portion of each candle.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The body contains the price range between the Open and Close of the asset.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A red candle has the Open at the top of the body and the close at the bottom of the body.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A green candle has the Open at the bottom of the body and the close at the top of the body.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The lines sticking out of the top and bottom of the candle body are the wicks for the candle and represent the High and Low for the TF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The importance of Open and Close for a candle will be further expanded upon in later posts, but the short version is that open and closing prices for an asset are extremely important for &amp;quot;confirmation trading.&amp;quot; This is a style of technical trading where one waits for a candle to confirm (open, or even open and close) over (or under) a critical resistance level before entering a position. This is a more conservative technical trading style, but it can also increase one&amp;#39;s chance of success by preventing them from buying or selling into wicking price action that is not truly indicative of the trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Candle Stick Formations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of materials have been written on various candlestick formations and in my experience the new trader will put far too much weight in these formations, Treating these formations as if they are some secret sauce to conquering the markets. In my experience candle stick formations and patterns are quite important, but what is less important is memorizing every catchy name for the formations and being able to recite them off the top of your head. Once one understands the principles and market forces these formations are conveying they will be much better served in comparison to just memorizing their names.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most important concepts of analyzing candlestick formations relate to the size of the bodies and wicks on the candles being analyzed. In addition, volume should also be a main consideration when looking at candlesticks in order to gauge the level of market participation over the relevant period (a little write up on volume will be coming shortly).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Concepts on formations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wicks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A long wick coming out the bottom of a candle on a downtrend may reflect that a local floor has been reached for the asset. The long wick reflects this because it shows that the market has readily bought up the price of the asset at lower prices.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, here is what is known as a &amp;quot;bullish hammer&amp;quot;, or dragonfly doji, on the 3d tf for the S&amp;amp;P 500 in the march lows of 2020: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/xjjC3dB&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/xjjC3dB&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you will notice that there was a massive wick coming out the bottom of the candle body (reflecting the strong buy pressure at those lower levels) and then subsequently no candle body closed below the body of this bullish hammer/dragonfly doji.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Similarly, a long wick coming out the top of a candle on an uptrend may reflect that a local top has been reached for the asset. The long wick reflect this because it shows that the market has readily sold down the price of the asset at higher prices.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, here is a local top reached in September 2020 for the S&amp;amp;P 500 (the second arrow pointing out a long wick to the bottom and resumption of trend): &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/HFM85ni&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/HFM85ni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Body:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The size of the candle body and its relation to prior candle bodies is also of critical importance. As previously discussed, the candle body represents the open and closing prices of that asset for the given TF. This range can be considered the &amp;quot;accepted price range&amp;quot; for the asset while the wicks are outliers on the relevant price action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Therefore, a candle body that closes above the prior candle body can be indicative of bullish trend resuming.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, here is a shot of 3d S&amp;amp;P 500 showing the relevance of candle bodies: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/NP3AT6d&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/NP3AT6d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here is another example except for a bearish continuation of candle bodies: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/JeZPCUB&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/JeZPCUB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doji:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A doji is a name for a session in which the candlestick for a security has an open and close that are virtually equal and are often components in patterns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doji candlesticks look like a cross, inverted cross or plus sign.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here are some types of dojis: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/GNWdwyG&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/GNWdwyG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dojis by themselves are not inherently bearish or bullish patterns, they must be analyzed in context of the greater trend and accompanying volume.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;However, Dojis are a sign of indecision in the market place. The fact that there was very little range between the open and close (thereby causing the candle to have a very small body) reflects that bulls and bears are undecided on which direction the asset should continue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In practice, I often view Dojis as a sign to watch out, because it suggests the asset may soon be making a sizable move one way or the other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, here is a recent 3d gravestone doji on AAPL incorporating several of the concepts related to candles touched on in this article: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/NYYwn1x&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/NYYwn1x&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that some general concepts have been outlined regarding the relevancy of candle bodies and candle wicks, take a look at the below traditional candlestick formations and try to determine why they are considered &amp;quot;bullish&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;bearish&amp;quot; candlestick formations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bullish candlestick formations: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/LgIUUtg&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/LgIUUtg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bearish candlestick formations: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/cmuRhWP&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/cmuRhWP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope the above was helpful in providing some useful info for new technical analysts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗宾汉上市时，投资者每天交易罗宾汉的股票：https://t.co/do786cn1rk]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347290630188367873</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347290630188367873</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 21:55:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Robinhood investors day trading Robinhood’s stock when it goes public: https://t.co/do786cn1rk</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[金黄色制药公司(行情代码：AUPH)主要催化剂1月22日]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，在最近所有的医学狂热发生的情况下，我对公司做了一些DD
随着即将到来的催化剂的出现，股票可能会飙升，并跌入金星
制药公司。我会贴出主要文章的链接，详细解释
它，但简而言之：

-金色制药拥有最多的…之一]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksgt1k/aurinia_pharmaceuticals_ticker_auph_major/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksgt1k/aurinia_pharmaceuticals_ticker_auph_major/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 21:30:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So with all the medical mania happening recently, I did some DD on companies with upcoming catalysts that could skyrocket the stock, and fell into Aurinia pharmaceuticals. I will post link to the main article explaining in detail about it, but in short:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Aurinia Pharmaceuticals has one of the most important milestones in its history in a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Next January 22, 2021 is the PDUFA where the FDA will decide the approval of the candidate drug Voclosporin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Voclosporin approval by the FDA is almost assured (estimated at 95% chance of approval) thanks to the very good phase III trial data presented last December 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Estimates of the potential revenues that Voclosporin could generate worldwide once approved range from $1.5B to $3B per year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also have around $400+ mill in cash on hand with great leadership. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only other completion they have in this field is Glaxosmithkline that currently produces an inferior product (just approved dec 17) and is currently trading at $38/share&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now AUPH is only $13 a share, and with the high probability of being approved in a couple weeks, I have a feeling this thing will 🚀 straight to the moon, and evidence of that is how it jumped to $21 last December when it released its phase 3 trial results. Currently all analysts have a buy rating at a PT average of $23.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do your own DD, but I’m in with $5k waiting for this home run&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/seekingalpha.com/amp/article/4395615-aurinia-pharmaceuticals-offers-good-entry-opportunity-next-pdufa-for-voclosporin&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/seekingalpha.com/amp/article/4395615-aurinia-pharmaceuticals-offers-good-entry-opportunity-next-pdufa-for-voclosporin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir实时冠状病毒事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[Palantir首席执行官亚历山大·卡普谈帮助各国政府应对冠状病毒
[https://www.washingtonpost.com/washington-post-live/2021/01/07/path-forward-combating-covid-19-with-palantir-ceo-alexander-karp/].
PLTR被包括美国政府在内的世界各国政府利用，以
使用其…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksitm2/palantir_live_covid19_event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksitm2/palantir_live_covid19_event/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 20:50:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/washington-post-live/2021/01/07/path-forward-combating-covid-19-with-palantir-ceo-alexander-karp/&quot;&gt;Palantir CEO Alexander Karp on helping governments with coronavirus response&lt;/a&gt;. PLTR was tapped by governments around the world including the U.S. government to use its software to manage the data on the spread of COVID-19, to analyze trends and anticipate various needs across the supply chain. Palantir products such as Foundry is able to monitor the manufacture of coronavirus vaccines and determine where they should go. Foundry allows users to understand what is happening on the ground and to determine which hospitals do not have enough supplies, are over utilized, and have capacity through a dashboard unifying data sets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[三月份关于我父亲的真实故事]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kse0q0/true_story_about_my_dad_in_march/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kse0q0/true_story_about_my_dad_in_march/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 20:50:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB和SEC]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kshph5/wsb_and_sec/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kshph5/wsb_and_sec/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 20:50:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[氢气和可再生股票在夜间发生大规模爆炸。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我只想祝贺每一位在过去几天/一周的低价买入的人
几位氢气特别是Plug和ICLN股东赚取了丰厚的利润
现在。但最后我在问自己，这是怎么在几个小时后发生的
将近20%来自Plug？]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ks87i2/massive_explosion_from_hydrogen_and_renewable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ks87i2/massive_explosion_from_hydrogen_and_renewable/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 19:30:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to congrats everyone who bought at the dips last days/week of several hydrogen especially plug and icln shareholders for some nice profits now.
But in the end I&amp;#39;m asking myself how did this happen after hour with like nearly 20% from plug?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币突破40K

比特币TC.X#比特币 https://t.co/rUcn6aPRBr]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347244478495657984</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347244478495657984</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:57:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin broke 40K 
 
$BTC.X #Bitcoin https://t.co/rUcn6aPRBr</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币在触及2万美元3周后，首次触及4万美元。https://t.co/fO0uPt2gUT TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347245287790796800</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347245287790796800</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:57:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin hits $40,000 for the first time, 3 weeks after hitting $20,000. $BTC https://t.co/fO0uPt2gUT</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币年复一年的回报。

https://t.co/n0xF6Iku9P TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347239579397586945</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347239579397586945</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:57:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin returns by year...

$BTC https://t.co/n0xF6Iku9P</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在19世纪30年代的英国投资铁路，你就会赔钱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你在19世纪30年代的英国投资铁路，你就会赔钱。如果
如果你投资东印度公司，你会赔钱的。如果
你在1999年投资了科技，最多花了十多年的时间
你要赚钱，如果有的话。不能因为某样东西是…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksic77/if_you_had_invested_in_railroads_in_1830s_britain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ksic77/if_you_had_invested_in_railroads_in_1830s_britain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:57:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you had invested in railroads in 1830&amp;#39;s Britain you would have lost money. If you would have invested in the East India Company you would have lost money. If you had invested in tech in 1999 it would have at best taken over a decade for you to make money, if ever. Just because something is the future doesn&amp;#39;t mean it&amp;#39;s a good investment. Just keep this in mind if you plan on investing in EV&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉被低估了]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前，特斯拉的股价只在未来200年内有价值，但研究
已经表明，在太阳消亡之前，地球还将存活10亿年
出去。因此，即使你不是天才，也能看出特斯拉的价值被严重低估
而且它只在很短的时间内成为当前的价值因素。I…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksfr15/tesla_is_undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksfr15/tesla_is_undervalued/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:57:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently Tesla share price is only valued for the next 200 years but studies have shown that Earth will survive another 1 billions years before the Sun dies out. Thus You don’t have to be genius to figure out Tesla is heavily undervalued and it’s current value factors in only the very short time. I am kinda retarded to be able to do the math but trust me it’s heavy money. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Factor in the when Zuckenberg  calls in his species and that planet will be another market for Tesla that’s more clients for Tesla and it will sky rocket. Get in before it’s late&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币3.9万美元。https://t.co/6dNI3E3xUP TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347217296046088193</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347217296046088193</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:17:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin $39,000. $BTC https://t.co/6dNI3E3xUP</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[赚大钱的日子会让其他人紧张吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我有一天的收益比一天多的时候，我会变得更紧张，这是不是很奇怪
当东西是微红的时候？让我害怕泡沫，我有一种更强烈的冲动
在我的投资组合上涨5-6%的时候“恐慌性抛售”，而不是在下跌一天的时候“恐慌性抛售”。
我有多奇怪？]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksg4kn/do_biggain_days_make_anyone_else_nervous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksg4kn/do_biggain_days_make_anyone_else_nervous/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:17:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it weird that I get more nervous when I have a day of big gains than a day when things are slightly red? Makes me fear a bubble and I have more of an urge to “panic sell” when my portfolio is up 5-6% than I do when it’s down for a day. How weird am I?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克现在是世界上最富有的人，超过了杰夫·贝佐斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksff4q/elon_musk_is_now_the_richest_person_in_the_world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ksff4q/elon_musk_is_now_the_richest_person_in_the_world/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:17:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[突破：根据扎克伯格的说法，Facebook无限期阻止特朗普访问他的账户。“我们认为，允许总统在此期间继续使用我们的服务的风险实在太大了。”https://t.co/8iXbkgDV9O https://t.co/IGmHkieG8L]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347212507010760711</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1347212507010760711</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 17:07:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>RT @Kantrowitz: BREAKING: Facebook blocks Trump from accessing his accounts indefinitely, per Zuckerberg. &quot;We believe the risks of allowing…</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆·马斯克即将超越杰夫·贝佐斯成为世界首富]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/07/investing/elon-musk-jeff-bezos-richest-person/index.html

彭博社(Bloomberg)实时亿万富翁追踪机构现在有这两位亿万富翁
相互之间的差距在30亿美元以内，贝佐斯的价格为1840亿美元，马斯克的价格为181美元
十亿美元。比尔·盖茨现在以132万美元的…远远排在第三位]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksfco1/elon_musk_is_close_to_overtaking_jeff_bezos_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ksfco1/elon_musk_is_close_to_overtaking_jeff_bezos_as/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 17:07:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/07/investing/elon-musk-jeff-bezos-richest-person/index.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/07/investing/elon-musk-jeff-bezos-richest-person/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bloomberg real-time billionaire tracker now has the two multi-billionaires within $3 billion of each other, with Bezos at $184 billion and Musk at $181 billion. Bill Gates is now a distant third at $132 billion, according to Bloomberg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: As of now, Elon is officially the richest person on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>