<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 10:59:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[在这里经常被推荐的、你不喜欢的书是什么？还有一本你从未想过自己会喜欢的书，但最后却喜欢上了它？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有一个正在进行的书单，我在这里经常看到有人推荐，因为我想把它们都读完。
因为我想把它们都读完，而且很多书都很好！但遗憾的是，我正在读玛德琳-米勒的《Circe》，但我就是读不进去

但不幸的是，我正在读玛德琳-米勒的《Circe》，我就是无法进入这本书！我已经读了一半多，但我就是没有感觉到联系，也不知道该怎么办。
我已经读完了一半以上的书，但我就是感觉不到有什么联系，也不知道该怎么办。
被吸引了，这...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o83ulz/what_is_a_book_that_is_frequently_suggested_here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o83ulz/what_is_a_book_that_is_frequently_suggested_here/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:52:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have an ongoing list of books I see suggested here a lot because I want to read them all, and so many have been great! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But sadly, I am reading “Circe” by Madeline Miller and I just can’t get into it! I have gotten through over half the book and I just don’t feel connected or captivated, which makes me sad because I know so many people swear by this book and it has great feminine energy which I like, I just don’t find myself really thinking about it beyond the times I am reading, and I never feel “engrossed”. I am disappointed in myself for this one, I’m sorry guys, I know it’s a great story. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has this happened to any of y’all? What is something you thought you’d love and ended up not? Also, what is a book you didn’t think you’d enjoy but you did?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚刚读完《人鼠之间》!]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是第一本我真正喜欢的小说之一（另一本是《像房子一样安全》）。
as Houses）。)

书中的人物给人以真实的感觉，文字的描述也令人难以置信。
你很容易迷失在其中，因为你可以很容易地在脑海中构建每个环境和人物的每一个方面。
每一个环境和人物都在你的脑海里。你...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7zg9h/just_finished_of_mice_and_men/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7zg9h/just_finished_of_mice_and_men/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:55:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was one of the first novels I’ve ever actually liked (the other one is Safe as Houses).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The characters all feel so real and the writing is so incredibly descriptive. It’s so easy to get lost in it since you can easily construct every last aspect of every setting and person in your head. You can understand precisely what the characters do and exactly why they do it, this is quite possibly the greatest thing I’ve ever read&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傻瓜的联盟》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[先生们，我刚刚读完这本书。这是一本精彩的读物。我完全
我非常喜欢伊格内修斯的世界观，他想发动一场革命，瑞丽夫人的转变，圣诞老人不在乎的态度，曼库索的无助，琼斯的无助。
变化，圣诞老人不在乎的态度，曼库索的无助，琼斯的
琼斯想造成破坏，达琳的天真无邪，拉娜的态度......。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7kfji/a_confederacy_of_dunces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7kfji/a_confederacy_of_dunces/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:16:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sirs,
I just finished reading the book. It was a wonderful read. I thoroughly enjoyed Ignatius’s worldview, his wanting to start a revolution, Mrs Reily’s transformation, Santa’s don’t care attitude, Mancuso’s helplessness, Jones’s wanting to cause a sabotage, Darlene’s innocence, Lana’s attitude, Mr and Mrs Levy’s drama and so on.
This book has stood the test of time and has become a classic. 
How is it relevant in this generation/society?
Are there any other viewpoints from which the book should be viewed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,
Your Working Boy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚读完《东方快车谋杀案》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道该说什么，我怀疑他们都是一伙的，在大揭秘之前的几页就已经有了。
我怀疑他们都参与其中，在大揭秘之前的几页。我想也许M.Bouc也会参与其中，并组织了
作为火车的经理，我没有看到任何事情发生。

怀疑这是一起集体谋杀案，只是因为波洛才有可能......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t87l/i_just_finished_the_murder_on_the_orient_express/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t87l/i_just_finished_the_murder_on_the_orient_express/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 05:19:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know what to say, I suspected that they were all in on it, pages before the big reveal. I thought maybe M.bouc would have been in on it and organized being the manager of the train but I didn&amp;#39;t see anything coming. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;suspecting that it was a group murder was only possible due to Poirot feeding us the information in the third act. I love being surprised by mystery stories and hate completely obvious ones, this is a reason that keeps me coming back to Agatha christie&amp;#39;s books. I completely ruled out Mrs. Hubbard as a suspect, but my jaw dropped when I found out, I guess you should not rule out the most unlikely suspect in an Agatha Christie novel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would keep reading a bad story for the characters but a good story without characters I find interesting or I&amp;#39;m attached to is a story I wouldn&amp;#39;t be invested in. luckily this book had the best of both worlds, great characters and a wonderful plot and mystery that I did not grow tired of. I liked other stories of christie&amp;#39;s like five little pigs and the amazing murder of roger Ackroyd but I was not attached to the characters and found the characters of the former book rather tedious. here christie balanced a large cast in a short book and kept them interesting enough in their short interviews and I have to say I appreciated the little map of the train that I went back to every once and a while to capture the setting of the train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story was amazing, I had a feeling I would love it and I&amp;#39;m glad I didn&amp;#39;t watch the movie. The fact that they all agreed to look the other way for a justified murder was also a great end. This one is one of my favorite Agatha christie books so far. next to read is and then there were none.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在过去的十年中，是否有任何巨大的打击？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好!

在过去的十年里，图书行业是否有任何巨大的冲击（如哈利波特的规模）？
过去的十年里，有什么巨大的成功吗？我说的不是后来流行起来的书，例如
我说的是那些一经发行就大受欢迎的书。
发布。

这个问题来自于观看《神秘的世界》（The Mystery of...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7v50n/has_there_been_any_huge_hit_in_the_past_decade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7v50n/has_there_been_any_huge_hit_in_the_past_decade/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello !  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has there been any huge hit (like Harry Potter scale) in the book industry the past decade ? I&amp;#39;m not talking about books that got popular afterwards such as the GoT books, I&amp;#39;m talking about books that got insanely popular right from release. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This quesion rose from watching &amp;quot;the mystery of Henri Pick&amp;quot; with my girlfriend and it got us thinking about the popularity of books nowadays. We do read books but we do not follow the news of the litterature world at all, we are clueless about the new releases or rising authors and such.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can&amp;#39;-t really think about any book in the past decade that got so popular that EVERYONE heard about it and got many people to read it. We thought of Twilight and 50 shades but we feel like they&amp;#39;re actually quite niche and too controversial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[青春期书籍中主角的夸大才能]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道是我的原因还是我读的书的原因，但我发现越来越多的
我发现主角（或至少是我们被设计为支持的主要人物）越来越常见。
我发现主角（或至少是我们要支持的主角）拥有夸张的才能。

我的意思是，几乎每个主人公都同时拥有一系列的天赋。
这些天赋包括...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7o856/the_inflated_talents_of_protagonists_in_ya_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7o856/the_inflated_talents_of_protagonists_in_ya_books/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if it’s just me or the books I am reading but I am finding it more common place for protagonists (or at least main characters we are designed to root for) to posses inflated talents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean is, almost every protagonist has an array of gifts all at once. These talents consist of things such as being brilliant at music, well read, gifted at art, extremely athletic, potential world leading scientist, scholarship offers…all snowballed into one character. This is not to say these characters cannot exist or impossible to believe but I often feel that in stories in which, for example; That because the protagonist is unhappy or depressed that the reader is expected to feel more sad because of what is implied by their potential. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not to say, that books that use characters such as these are overall poorly written - but come across quite bland and copy and paste. Or perhaps it is me…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just curious to see if anyone else felt the same?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[似乎不能像我年轻时那样超级沉迷于书籍，这很糟糕。]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我还是个孩子的时候，进入书中--并停留在那里--似乎很容易。
超级容易。这方面最好的例子，不仅仅是对我，对很多人来说都是如此。
人来说，最好的例子是《哈利-波特》。如果我手里有一本新的《哈利-波特》，我就必须要看完。
就必须在当天读完它，睡觉也不例外，而世界......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7org9/cant_seem_to_get_super_engrossed_in_books_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7org9/cant_seem_to_get_super_engrossed_in_books_like/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 22:00:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back when I was still a kid, getting into a book - and staying there - seemed super easy. Probably the best example of this, not just for me but for a lot of people, was Harry Potter. If I got a new Harry Potter in my hands I just had to finish it that same day, sleeping be damned, and the world would stay with me for weeks after finishing it. It was the kind of story where you just felt compelled to go online and find communities to keep discussing it over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve tried to re-create this feeling since that time and I&amp;#39;ve never really found it. The closest was probably Game of Thrones/Song of Ice and Fire in terms of recreating this magical need for more information and discussion but otherwise, nothing much. I actually just put a bookmark at a Dresden book about ~50 pages from the ending and while I&amp;#39;ll obviously still finish the book, I have 0 urgency to do it. I&amp;#39;ve also tried reading Rowling&amp;#39;s other books as Robert Galbraith, wondering if it was her writing style that did it but the book was just nowhere near as engaging as any of her previous work. I just really want that super excitement at picking up a new book and I&amp;#39;m just not finding it, which makes me way less excited to read in general (and I hate it!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;m wondering, do you guys still regularly get deeply invested in the books you read? Do you think we feel that way less as we get older? Do some authors or genres inspire this more than others? What are your thoughts and experiences?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[当我阅读时，我假装自己是一个电影制片人，当我阅读时，我想象 "我的电影 "的每个 "场景 "会是什么样子。这很傻很有趣，但它使文学作品变得更令人兴奋]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想这是一个众所周知的普遍现象，但我最近才意识到这一点
而我一直是个贪婪的读者! 在此之前，我一直都是那种
"我必须专注于每一个字，而不是其他，否则我就会迷路 "的那种孩子。I
我的脑子里不能有其他事情发生，除了......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t048/when_i_read_i_pretend_i_am_a_filmmaker_and_as_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t048/when_i_read_i_pretend_i_am_a_filmmaker_and_as_i/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I assume this is a well known common thing but it only clicked with me recently and I have been a voracious reader! Before then, I&amp;#39;ve always been one of those &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;I must focus on each word and nothing else or I will get lost&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; kind of kid. I could not afford anything else happening in my head other than my own voice saying the words or else I&amp;#39;d lose track of what would be happening. But now, I have aquired this...hmm... would &amp;#39;Skill&amp;#39;? be too pretentious a word? I don&amp;#39;t know but it feels like I&amp;#39;ve gone to the next level of reading! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it all started with the Grapes of Wrath which I finished a few days ago. Everytime I opened the book, the &amp;quot;movie&amp;quot; would start playing and it was so consistent and concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GOP felt like an entire film playing in my head. From page one to the last. I guess, with practice, I was able to envision how character would look, how they would sound, what the lighting of each scene would like, the location, the &amp;quot;close up shots&amp;quot; of certatain conversations and monologues and what music would be playing. All this as I read. It was..sooo...goddamn enjoyable!! I have have felt so immersed before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also just finished the Raymond Carver short story - &amp;#39;Preservation&amp;#39; only minutes ago! And duuuude lol, It took me like 15 minutes to finish but it felt like a proper short film was happening right there in my head! I envisioned what the house looked like, their accents, their facial expressions, and of course the music!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I want to go back and re-read all my favourite books! I feel so happy right now lol. I&amp;#39;ve always loved reading but now it feels like I&amp;#39;ve aquired this next level love everyone is always talking about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[书籍是否让你活着？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我今天和一个朋友谈起从考试压力中抽身出来阅读一些有趣的书。
他的回答是 "噗......真是个书呆子！"。
这是通常的反应，我通常不会真的去想它。但现在我开始
思考--我没有什么社交生活，也没有持久的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mi9j/are_books_keeping_you_alive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mi9j/are_books_keeping_you_alive/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:52:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was talking to a friend today about taking a break from exam stress to read some interesting books, and his reply was &amp;quot;pfftt..what a nerd!&amp;quot;, which is the usual response and I don&amp;#39;t really think about it usually. But now I started thinking- I don&amp;#39;t have much of a social life, nor do I have lasting friendships. College is still underway, so I am not making strides in my career. Essentially, I don&amp;#39;t have any billionaire-ish achievements in my kitty. I could but don&amp;#39;t want to club/party and so I am content at home. But I do wake up everyday with the goal of completing all my other work till a predetermined time and finally get on with my book (s). Do you, like me, also feel this way? If you do, is it healthy to have this sort of a dependence (the friend in question told me, I think playfully, that I shouldn&amp;#39;t be dependent on anything for my happiness)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please just tell me I am not alone. This is not like a phase for me. It is really a therapeutic activity-reading. I feel the happiest when books surround me and I need to be engaged in the task to feel like I did something with my day. I mean I will get on with other things in life too, but I don&amp;#39;t know whether as an old person, I&amp;#39;ll be very different or adventurous or doing exciting things. I&amp;#39;m happy and content where I am- cozy in my reading nook :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BookTok的崛起：认识那些将书籍推上排行榜的青少年影响者]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mwhi/the_rise_of_booktok_meet_the_teen_influencers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mwhi/the_rise_of_booktok_meet_the_teen_influencers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:46:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所以，我刚刚发现了P.G. Wodehouse。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在这个网站上随机看到一个关于幽默书的帖子，其中提到了P.G.
Wodehouse的Bertie and Jeeves系列出现了。

我想我已经很多年没有在一本书上笑得这么开心了！（《伍斯特的密码》）。(The Code of the Woosters)
(The Code of the Woosters)必须是最有趣的关于奶牛挤奶器的书......可能是唯一的一本。
可能是唯一的一本，但重点是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7miic/so_i_just_discovered_pg_wodehouse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7miic/so_i_just_discovered_pg_wodehouse/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:20:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across a random post on this sub regarding humorous books and P.G. Wodehouse&amp;#39;s Bertie and Jeeves series came up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think I laughed so much at a book in years! (The Code of the Woosters) had to be the funniest book about a cow-creamer out there... probably the only one but the point stands!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Right Ho, Jeeves) has a public speaking scene that... I&amp;#39;m sorry but if you don&amp;#39;t start chuckling at the start of it then something is wrong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me this was a very pleasant surprise. I wasn&amp;#39;t expecting much out of a series published 100 years back. So tell me, what book surprised you? A book you weren&amp;#39;t expecting to like but was forced by the author to change your mind?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想感谢这个子!]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，一开始我就需要诚实地提到，直到今年3月，我已经15年没有读过小说了。
直到今年3月，我已经有15年没有读过小说了。在禁闭期间，有些事情发生了变化，我内心燃起了改变的火花。
锁定期间发生了一些变化，我内心燃起了改变的火花，所以我成为了这个
分论坛。我需要感谢所有贡献和发布的人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7kejq/i_want_to_thank_this_sub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7kejq/i_want_to_thank_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:33:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, right off the bat I need to be honest and mention that I had not read a novel in 15 years until March of this year. Something changed during the lockdown and a spark ignited within me for change so I became a member of this subreddit. I need to thank all the people who contributed and posted their book suggestions making me click the save button so many times. Since joining this subreddit I have purchased and completed book number nine since March. I currently have a massive list of books I need still need to purchase, read, and eventually add to my new bookshelf. Thank you all for helping me focus on reading and making me splurge on a fancy new wood bookmark!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚读了《炼金术士》...]]></title><description><![CDATA[而且我很生气。我甚至无法用语言来表达我有多讨厌那种
婴儿第一哲学的废话。为什么每个人都这么喜欢这本书？谁能给我解释一下
谁能给我解释一下，我应该从这个经历中得到什么？
我是不是太傻了，不能 "理解"？它是如此......基本。如此的表面水平....]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7iht5/i_just_read_the_alchemist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7iht5/i_just_read_the_alchemist/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 09:27:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;and I&amp;#39;m livid. I can&amp;#39;t even express in words how much I hated that baby&amp;#39;s-first-philosophy BS. Why does everyone love this book so much? Can somebody please explain to me what I was supposed to get out of this experience? Am I just too stupid to &amp;quot;get it?&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s so... basic. So surface level. What&amp;#39;s there to get?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[玩火的女孩》和《踢马蜂窝的女孩》值得在观看《龙纹身的女孩》这部电影后阅读吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看了大卫-芬奇的那部!

我能够理解这两部作品吗？或者我应该把这3本书都读完。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7eapz/is_the_girl_who_played_with_fire_and_the_girl_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7eapz/is_the_girl_who_played_with_fire_and_the_girl_who/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:26:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I watched David Fincher&amp;#39;s one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I be able to understand both of them?
Or should I read all the 3 books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不难读的经典之作]]></title><description><![CDATA[我脑子太小，无法吸收很多必读的经典，但我真的想读一些。
但我真的想读一些。有什么建议吗？

编辑：谢谢你到目前为止的建议！！补充一下，我非常喜欢的一些类型是
小说、历史小说、幻想、惊悚片、好的悬疑片，以及任何能得到这些东西的东西。
引起这个问题......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o74wdv/classics_that_arent_too_difficult_to_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o74wdv/classics_that_arent_too_difficult_to_read/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:26:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;pls i am too small brained to absorb a lot of the must read classics but i really wanna get into reading some. any suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: thanks for the suggestions so far!! to add, some genres i really like are fiction, historical fiction, fantasy, thriller, a good mystery, and anything that gets this small brain thinking about its life for days after finishing a book. i also do not mind books that’ll make me sob :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次阅读莎士比亚的作品。这是一个完整的体验，现在是一个新的爱好!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我今年21岁，以前从未读过莎士比亚，直到最近三四天。我
在过去的几天里，我一直在阅读和研究莎士比亚的人物和故事。
故事。

我的书架上有两本他的作品，是在一次拍卖会上买的，我从最薄的那本开始读起。
最薄的一本。它是《如你所愿》，是一本快速的2-3页的书。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7f06f/read_shakespeares_work_for_the_first_time_it_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7f06f/read_shakespeares_work_for_the_first_time_it_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 05:15:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am 21 and I have never read Shakespeare before untill the last 3-4 days. I had spent last days just reading and studying about Shakespeare&amp;#39;s characters and stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had 2 of his work in my shelf bought at a sale, I started off with the thinnest one. It was As you like it, It was a quick 2-3 hour read but then I started to analyze all these dialogues and plot. I thought it was very funny and amazingly sarcastic on the tone. Rosalind is a great character, and so is Touchstone. If I am not mistaken As you like it is a metaphor about how life simply has no greater meaning, it&amp;#39;s ephemeral at best. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next I read A Midsummer Night&amp;#39;s Dream,  another comedy this at times did remind me of As you like it, I could see a similar notion about an entire different progression of story. I think out of two that I&amp;#39;ve read I see love is a theme he uses constantly,  and also comments on what makes people fall in love generally beauty and appearance. There was more of a romantic input on this story then the other one which was more playful. I really liked the play within the play. 
- Also, I think I can see Puck being close friends with Touchstone, not going to lie. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I will spend rest of my life reading and studying more and more about his work. I have found more of his book at a local bookstore.  And I have found Othello and Macbeth which I am going to read next.  I think Shakespeare is the foundation of many stories I have seen in my life before in various Tv shows and movies. It takes time but it totally worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[翻开大流行病的一页。纽约市图书馆将重新开放]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7ddcl/turning_the_page_on_the_pandemic_nyc_libraries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7ddcl/turning_the_page_on_the_pandemic_nyc_libraries/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 02:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚读完卡勒德-侯赛尼的《千秋万代》，说实话.....，那是什么东西？]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我看完这本书的一半时，我忍不住想在互联网上为自己扫扫兴
在互联网上为自己剧透。这本书实在是太引人注目了。老实说，它是我读过的最好的--甚至是最好的--书之一。
它是我读过的最好的--甚至是最好的--书之一。我觉得自己很无知，不知道
知道阿富汗的情况有多严重。而这两个...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7bvpi/i_just_finished_read_a_thousand_splendid_suns_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7bvpi/i_just_finished_read_a_thousand_splendid_suns_by/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 02:12:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was halfway through the book, I couldn&amp;#39;t resist the urge to spoil it for myself on the internet. The book&amp;#39;s just so compelling. Its honestly one of the best - maybe even the best - books I&amp;#39;ve ever read. I feel so ignorant about not knowing how severe Afghanistan&amp;#39;s situation is. And the two main characters are portrayed perfectly. Everything&amp;#39;s perfect about this book. My only &amp;quot;problem&amp;quot; with it was that it was so depressing. No seriously, it was so very depressing and sad and not like the other books I&amp;#39;ve read. No it was sad on a whole other level I never even knew existed. I&amp;#39;m still trying to process everything I read and I&amp;#39;m rambling and I dont think what I&amp;#39;m saying makes any sense but whatever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所以，我讨厌《哈利波特与死亡圣器》的结局]]></title><description><![CDATA[(可能的破坏者)

我最近读完了（第一次）所有的《哈利-波特》书籍，并且
我真的很讨厌最后的结局。它看起来如此仓促，而且没有详细说明
主要人物的死亡对他们之后的生活有何影响。对我来说，结尾似乎是 "哦，我们赢了，我们赢了"。
结局似乎是 "哦，我们赢了，现在......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o784bj/so_i_hated_the_ending_of_harry_potter_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o784bj/so_i_hated_the_ending_of_harry_potter_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 01:15:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(possible spoilers) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading (for the first time) all the Harry Potter books, and I really hated the very end. It seemed so rushed and it didn&amp;#39;t go into detail on how the deaths of major characters impacted their lives afterwards. 
To me, the ending seemed like &amp;#39;oh we won, now let&amp;#39;s skip to nineteen years later.&amp;#39; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please tell me other people were disappointed with the ending of the books!? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;ve still never seen The deathly hallows part two movie)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[根据书的质量和叙述者，最喜欢的有声书？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在取消我的账户之前，我有8个Audible图书积分可以使用。
我想在7月1日我的下一个信用额度出现之前使用。因此，我需要尽快挑选8本书。
我发现一些好书被糟糕的解说员毁掉了，而一些平庸的书
有了合适的人才，就会大放异彩。你认为什么是最好的书？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o71jcj/favorite_audiobooks_based_on_both_book_quality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o71jcj/favorite_audiobooks_based_on_both_book_quality/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have 8 Audible book credits to use before canceling my account, which I would like to do before my next credit hits on 7/1. So, I need to pick 8 books ASAP. I’ve found some great books are ruined by a bad narrator, and some mediocre ones shine with the right talent. What are the best books you have listened to, based on both the quality of the book AND the narrator? I’m more interested in fiction, any genre. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[祝屋大维娅-巴特勒生日快乐!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想提请大家注意，屋大维娅-巴特勒的生日是
本周早些时候。她是一位文学和科幻界的远见卓识者和开拓者。她
她是第一个（我想也是唯一一个）获得麦克阿瑟天才奖的科幻小说作家。
天才奖。她的作品和在该流派中的代表作帮助她的作品在世界范围内得到了认可。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o70knn/happy_birthday_to_octavia_butler/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o70knn/happy_birthday_to_octavia_butler/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 15:51:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to bring attention to the fact that  Octavia Butler&amp;#39;s birthday was earlier this week. She was a literary and sci fi visionary and trailblazer. She was the first (and I think only) science fiction author to recurve the MacArthur Genius grant.  Her work and representation in the genre helped to create the foundation for many of the fantastic new voices we have had the opportunity to enjoy in spec fiction, especially over the last decade. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started Parable of the Sower recently. The world is captivating, main character is strong, and themes are focused. I&amp;#39;m very much enjoying my first foray into Butler and plan to check out more of her work. I&amp;#39;ve now started the second book in the series and her ability to see the future we were heading towards is eerie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I highly encourage fans of her work and novices alike to pick up one of her books or short stories to experience her work and celebrate her contributions to literature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;There&amp;#39;s nothing new under the sun, but there are new suns.&amp;quot; - Octavia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是什么让阿加莎-克里斯蒂的书如此伟大？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我昨天下午开始读《东方快车谋杀案》，只是感觉到
被迫读到了晚上。

今天早上，我很惊讶。不仅很久没有一本书让我睡不着觉了
我最近读的书也没有像克里斯蒂的《东方快车谋杀案》那样让我吃惊或发笑。
克里斯蒂的伟大故事....]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6z9r4/what_makes_agatha_christies_books_so_great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6z9r4/what_makes_agatha_christies_books_so_great/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 13:44:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started to read &lt;em&gt;Murder on the Orient Express&lt;/em&gt; yesterday afternoon and just felt compelled to read through well into the night. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning, I was surprised. Not only had it been a long time since a book kept me up, my latest reads had not surprised me or made me laugh like Christie&amp;#39;s great story. This is not my first Christie, but I am surprised to have almost forgotten how this lady&amp;#39;s pen can snatch you out of everyday life for a moment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering what others like about Christie&amp;#39;s books, what they feel when reading them. If you care to share your experience that would be great !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, I think it narrows down to the simplicity of it all at the end... Although at first glance Christie&amp;#39;s murder mysteries seem complicated, they are supported by many simple facts of everyday life... Like nicknames can be misleading about gender, narrators aren&amp;#39;t always reliable, truth can be found behind some strong emotional reactions...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在读Catch-22。这一段我看不懂......谁能帮忙解释一下？]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是第一章的内容，也是我对这本书的第二次尝试。上一次
我试图阅读，我不明白这一段，它使我放弃了阅读
这让我对这本书的其他部分产生了怀疑。段落在下面。

"上校在通信部门，他日夜忙碌着
发送......"。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6zf61/reading_catch22_this_paragraph_is_indecipherable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6zf61/reading_catch22_this_paragraph_is_indecipherable/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is from the first chapter and my second attempt at the book. The last time I tried reading, I didn’t understand this paragraph and it put me off reading the rest of the book for some reason. Paragraph is below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The colonel was in Communications, and he was kept busy day and night transmitting glutinous messages from the interior into square pads of gauze which he sealed meticulously and delivered to a covered white pail that stood on the night table beside his bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚的大部分文学遗产都已绝版。拯救国家失落书籍的斗争]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6v4ct/most_of_australias_literary_heritage_is_out_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6v4ct/most_of_australias_literary_heritage_is_out_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 11:58:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[指环王》杂志]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道这是一个不受欢迎的观点，但我刚刚读完《指环王》的前两部。
指环王》的前两部书，这是一个罕见的情况，我喜欢电影，而不是原著。
电影比原著更受欢迎。

在小说中，我只是从未感受到人物所面临的真正的绝望和压倒性的困难
角色所面临的真正的绝望和压倒性的困难。这部电影是我最喜欢的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6qgth/lord_of_the_rings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6qgth/lord_of_the_rings/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 08:41:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know it is an unpopular opinion but I just finished the first two Lord of the Rings books and it has been one of those rare instances where I enjoyed the movies way more than the source books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the novels I just never felt the true desperation and overwhelming odds facing the characters. The book just felt more of a historical text; like reading a textbook vs watching an immersive documentary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some books where I can separate the text from the movie, especially when there is great divergence between the story  (King vs Kubrick&amp;#39;s The Shining) but the LotR movies are fairly faithful adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure I would have liked to see a bit of Tom Bombadil but I think the trade-offs with the movie interpretation are well worth it. One example: when Gandalf frees Theoden from the influence of Wormtongue - in the novels was a bit underwhelming, kind of like... hey, come get a few breaths of fresh air and a Snickers, you good boss? Look at the blue sky  (and his wrinkles smoothed. The end.) VS the movie interpretation when we can see the drastic  driving out of Sarumon&amp;#39;s influence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a hot take here and I&amp;#39;m not looking to change anyone&amp;#39;s opinion or try to take away from Tolkien&amp;#39;s masterpiece, I&amp;#39;m just surprised with myself that this has been my takeaway through the first two books and wanted to know your take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么书中的人名或地名用"-: "代替？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近在很多很多年后再次开始阅读。目前我已经读了
基督山伯爵》和《弗兰肯斯坦》（均来自古腾堡项目）。
然后我目前正在读芬兰语的《傲慢与偏见》。我认为在所有这些
这些书中，都有一些地名或人名......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6m2b1/why_are_names_or_some_persons_or_places_in_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6m2b1/why_are_names_or_some_persons_or_places_in_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 05:57:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently started reading again after many many years. I&amp;#39;ve currently read the Count of Monte Cristo and Frankenstein in English (both from project Gutenberg) and then I&amp;#39;m currently reading Pride and Prejudice in Finnish. I think in all of these books, there has been some names of places or persons that are replaced with &amp;quot;–:&amp;quot;. Example could be something like &amp;quot;They went to visit the McCoys in –:&amp;quot;. Why are some names hidden like this? I tried to Google but could not find any good search terms to find info. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有谁知道有什么好的科幻和/或歇斯底里的书能让你反思人生？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想要一本真正让你思考生命/人类的书，有科幻的
因为这些东西很酷。
感到非常空虚的书，并且在我看完之后还能在我脑海中停留很久。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6p9if/anyone_know_any_good_scifi_andor_dystopian_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6p9if/anyone_know_any_good_scifi_andor_dystopian_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 04:57:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i want a book that really makes u think about life/humanity that has sci-fi themes because that stuff is cool. im also looking for a book that will leave me feeling very empty when i finish it and be stuck on my mind long after i finish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[五代人的阅读习惯[信息图] 。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6g4qy/the_reading_habits_of_five_generations_infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6g4qy/the_reading_habits_of_five_generations_infographic/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 21:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你读了什么并喜欢上了它，因为它是在这个子上推荐给你的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我几乎每天都来这里 -- 我有时会想，如果我们很多人都接受了我们彼此提供的建议
建议，以及这些建议对读者的作用如何。
所以，告诉我们......你有哪些超级书籍，有哪些伟大的阅读体验？
因为本子上有人推荐？是什么书或...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6e7xy/what_did_you_read_and_love_because_it_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6e7xy/what_did_you_read_and_love_because_it_was/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 20:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I come here almost every day -- and I sometimes wonder if lots of us take the suggestions we all offer one another, and how they work out for the readers -- so, tell us... what super books, what great reading experiences did you have because someone on this sub suggested it? What was the book or author you are grateful this sub introduced you to? Pass it on so others can know your reading joys and share in your favorite read from a recommendation. I figure if you loved it, maybe I will, too! I&amp;#39;m always looking for something new and great!   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll start with an author I had never considered, but was suggested to me on a thread I started a while back about gritty rural fiction. Someone suggested Michael Farris Smith&amp;#39;s Blackwood -- and I absolutely loved it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想要英雄"。科大教授Devon Mihesuah撰写了第二本以美国本土侦探为主角的小说]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6ctl8/i_want_heroes_ku_professor_devon_mihesuah_pens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6ctl8/i_want_heroes_ku_professor_devon_mihesuah_pens/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 19:42:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[杀死一只知更鸟》是一部非常精巧的文学作品]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天刚刚完成，我花了15天时间，但最后我可以骄傲地说
它值得所有的时间和关注；它是这样一个杰作。

英语是我的第二语言，我必须承认，对我来说，这是一本难读的书。
然而，我很喜欢它。作者在书中描绘了 "我 "与 "我 "之间的关系。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o68eyi/to_kill_a_mockingbird_is_very_well_crafted_piece/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o68eyi/to_kill_a_mockingbird_is_very_well_crafted_piece/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 17:44:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed just yesterday, took me 15 days but at the end I can say it proudly that it deserve all the time and attention; it&amp;#39;s such a masterpiece. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;English being my second language, I must admit that it was a hard read for me, nevertheless I enjoyed it. The way in which the author paints the incidents in the mind of the reader is so profound and indelible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from the writing style I loved the characters too, especially Atticus, his way of parenting is commendable. Also, the bonding between Scout and Jem is very warming, seemed to me like they are the epitome of the saying &amp;#39;made for each other&amp;#39; .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Americans are lucky to have it in their curriculum, like I had Gulliver&amp;#39;s Travel which I barely enjoyed myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[必要的有趣的书。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我想要一本读起来很有趣的书。我刚刚悟出一个道理
我一生中大部分时间都在读那些获得好评的书。
那些 "必读 "的书，以及那些我想说我读过的书。I
从那时起，我意识到，我只想享受阅读，而我...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o69u95/essential_fun_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o69u95/essential_fun_books/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, I want a book that’s fun to read. I have just come to a realization that I’ve spent most of my life reading books that have received critical acclaim, books that are “must reads” and books that I wanted to be able to say I read. I have since realized that I just want to enjoy reading, and I’m really not feeling academic right now. What are the first books that come to mind that just scream a great time. Can be anything I am not really pigeon holed into a certain genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪些书让你大吃一惊，让你质疑另一个人怎么可能想出这些想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[例如，我正在阅读金-斯坦利-罗宾逊的火星三部曲，我对他所掌握的科学知识感到敬畏。
我对他所拥有的大量科学知识感到敬畏。物理学、化学和生物学知识
知识，以令人信服的方式讲述火星地球化的故事，并使其
显得如此可信，没有任何莫名其妙的技术废话......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o62xvt/what_books_blew_you_away_that_they_made_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o62xvt/what_books_blew_you_away_that_they_made_you/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, I&amp;#39;m reading through Kim Stanley Robinson&amp;#39;s Mars trilogy and I am in awe of how much scientific knowledge he has. The physics, chemistry, and biology knowledge to convincingly tell the story of the terraforming of Mars and make it seem so believable without any inexplicable technobabble is beyond my mind, and he&amp;#39;s done this in several of his other books too. Even more mainstream historical fiction novels like those of Bernard Cornwell, while excellent for what they are (fun, swashbuckling, hero adventures) I still can&amp;#39;t imagine knowing all the small details that go into period specific writing, even when it&amp;#39;s just formulaic fun books. Like I don&amp;#39;t know anything about Napoleonic clothing, travel, weaponry, the common sentiments people had, horses/livestock, the age of sail... so much detail. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What books rocked your perception like that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有声读物毁了我]]></title><description><![CDATA[它开始于禁闭期间。无论我是在打扫卫生、锻炼身体，还是蜷缩在床下的
我都可能在听一个精彩的故事。
由一个了不起的配音演员讲述的精彩故事。从那时起，我的床头书堆就越来越多。
因此，我终于拿起了《刀锋战士》，虽然我真的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o616p2/audiobooks_have_ruined_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o616p2/audiobooks_have_ruined_me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:28:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It started during lockdown. Whether I was cleaning, exercising, or curled up in the fetal position under my bed, I could be listening to a wonderful story, narrated by an amazing voice actor. Since then my bedside book stack has grown, so I finally picked up The Blade Itself and, while I’m really enjoying it, I’m also struggling. It’s harder to become immersed in the story, and I keep wanting to hear someone read it to me whenever I’m doing something that occupies my body but not my mind. I’m sure I’ll get back into the flow of it soon enough, but it is a strange feeling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[节目《好预兆》是对该书的一个该死的良好表现。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看完书后，刚看完这个系列，剧中遗漏的一切都被弥补了。
弥补了这些缺憾，大卫-坦南特和迈克尔-希恩的表演也很精彩。
和迈克尔-辛的精彩表演。我通常对改编的电影持怀疑态度，但我觉得
但我觉得我可以很容易地把它传给没有读过这本书的人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6c8um/the_show_good_omens_is_a_damn_fine_representation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6c8um/the_show_good_omens_is_a_damn_fine_representation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:15:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just finished the series after reading the book, everything the show left out it made up for with tasteful additions and an amazing performance by David Tennant and Michael Sheen. I&amp;#39;m usually skeptical of movie adaptations, but I feel like I could easily pass this off to someone who hasn&amp;#39;t read the book and feel like they&amp;#39;re missing out on only small details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰神话]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在寻找一本关于爱尔兰神话的书，它能像尼尔-盖曼的《北欧神话》一样容易理解。
神话》一样容易理解。也许能把四个周期的内容细分为
详细的书。欢迎任何建议。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o63moe/irish_mythology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o63moe/irish_mythology/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 13:24:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am looking for a book about Irish Mythology that is as accessible as &amp;quot;Norse Mythology&amp;quot; by Neil Gaiman. Maybe something that breaks down the four cycles into detail. Any suggestions are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[虚假的社交媒体的愤怒正在使作者改变他们书中的台词。认为一个虚构人物的言论反映了作者的实际信仰的愚蠢想法正在蔓延。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6b6rr/bogus_social_media_outrage_is_making_authors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6b6rr/bogus_social_media_outrage_is_making_authors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 12:59:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[皮拉内西之后]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年年初，我收到了皮拉内西的生日礼物，对它一无所知。
这本书让我大吃一惊。我现在看到它在这个子上被推荐，它总是得到
很多人的喜爱。所以我的问题是，对于那些喜欢皮拉内西的人来说，还有什么是你今年排名前三的？
在你今年的前三名名单上？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o60zhs/after_piranesi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o60zhs/after_piranesi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 04:52:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I received Piranesi for my birthday earlier this year and knew nothing about it. This book blew me away. I now see it recommended on this sub and it always gets lots of love. So my question is, for those of you who loved Piranesi, what else has been on your top three list this year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对90岁老人的建议，拒绝音频和电子书，兴趣狭窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要是寻找神秘小说。她认为任何类型的 "巧合 "小说都很平淡。
在另一端，不能太黑暗/残酷/性。没有吸血鬼、超自然现象。
科幻小说，或直接的浪漫主义。1830年以前的历史题材都不行。她真的
她很喜欢《世界新闻报》，这导致了《埃尔默-凯尔顿》，她也很喜欢这本书。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5xywq/suggestions_for_90_year_old_refuses_audio_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5xywq/suggestions_for_90_year_old_refuses_audio_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 03:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primarily looking for mystery fiction. She finds &amp;quot;cozies&amp;quot; of any stripe insipid. On the other end, can&amp;#39;t be too dark/brutal/sexual. No vampires, paranormal, sci-fi, or straight-up romance. Nothing historical before 1830&amp;#39;s.
She really liked News of the World, which led to Elmer Kelton, which she also liked. She also likes Southern U.S. settings or context, but not a requirement.
She reads 3-4 hours daily, and it&amp;#39;s exhausting to keep up. Loves Grisham (but read everything) &amp;amp; courtroom settings, but knows there&amp;#39;s not all that much of that that doesn&amp;#39;t have dark or brutal 2d story). Spies/Intrigue is ok, but no torture/terrorism.
Any suggestions appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么好的关于日本黑社会的非虚构书籍吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[关于他们的历史、文化、习俗等方面的内容!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5t990/are_there_any_good_nonfiction_books_on_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5t990/are_there_any_good_nonfiction_books_on_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 01:31:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something about their history, their culture, practices, etc!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否曾经读完一本书，然后当你不得不用谷歌搜索刚才发生的事情时，感觉有点愚蠢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我读完了《我想结束一切》，总的来说我认为这是一本有趣的书。
一本有趣的书，直到我读到最后。我他妈的根本不知道
结局是想告诉我发生了什么，以及它对之前发生的故事意味着什么。
故事中发生的部分意味着什么。我不得不去谷歌上查找...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5vf6q/do_you_ever_finish_a_book_and_then_feel_kinda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5vf6q/do_you_ever_finish_a_book_and_then_feel_kinda/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:21:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finished reading &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m Thinking of Ending Things&amp;quot; which overall I thought was an interesting book, until I got to the end. I had no fucking clue what the ending was trying to tell me had happened and what it meant for the previous parts of the story that happened. I had to go to Google to figure out what the hell had happened and that alone made me rethink if I can even say I enjoyed the book if after all that I couldn&amp;#39;t even figure out exactly how it ended on my own. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure if I was just having a bad day and my brain decided not to work, if the ending was in fact confusing, or I&amp;#39;m just getting dumber with age. I believe the book was made into a film or movie so I am curious as to how they did it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else read this book or are there books out there where you had to look up the ending to make sure you understood it right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚读完《动物农场》，想知道哪些象征意义不是最明显的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜欢这个讽刺性的寓言故事，喜欢奥威尔通过象征性手法出色地展示了
奥威尔通过象征性的手法，出色地展示了压迫、暴政和宣传的动态。我觉得它
低调地讲述了各地失败的革命。我特别想知道
我可能错过了哪些象征意义，或者也许不是最...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5hps8/just_finished_reading_animal_farm_and_would_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5hps8/just_finished_reading_animal_farm_and_would_like/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I loved this satirical allegory and how Orwell brilliantly demonstrated the dynamics of oppression, tyranny, propaganda through symbolism. I feel like its lowkey just about failed revolutions everywhere. I was, in particular, wondering what symbolisms I might have missed or maybe weren&amp;#39;t the most obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very interested in discussing and knowing the different allegorical symbolisms of certain events other than the apparent representations of political figures, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[太空中的犹太人。关于犹太作家的无名历史和科幻小说的诞生]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5px7r/jews_in_space_on_the_unsung_history_of_jewish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5px7r/jews_in_space_on_the_unsung_history_of_jewish/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:17:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你读过的最有趣的书？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你读过的最有趣的书是什么？请提供一行情节摘要
不带破坏性的。谢谢!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5jhje/funniest_book_youve_ever_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5jhje/funniest_book_youve_ever_read/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 18:56:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the funniest book you have read? Please provide a line of plot summary with no spoilers. 
Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥斯卡-马丁内斯（Oscar Martinez）在《野兽》中对萨尔瓦多-美国移民之路的描述，是我读过的最令人信服和恐怖的书之一。]]></title><description><![CDATA[奥斯卡-马丁内斯是一位来自萨尔瓦多的获奖记者，也是 "ELFARO.N "的创始人之一。
elfaro.net的共同创始人，这是萨尔瓦多的一份在线报纸。他是我遇到过的最无畏的非小说记者之一。
我在非虚构作品中遇到过的最无畏的记者之一，他漂亮地捕捉到了以下两点
这些移民所面临的可怕条件，同时又...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5q7kn/oscar_martinezs_account_of_the_el_salvadorus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5q7kn/oscar_martinezs_account_of_the_el_salvadorus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 18:31:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oscar Martinez is an award winning journalist from El Salvador and cofounder of elfaro.net, an online newspaper in El Salvador. One of the most intrepid journalists I&amp;#39;ve ever encountered in nonfiction, he beautifully captures both the horrific conditions these migrants face while simultaneously highlighting the perseverance and bravery of the migrants he encounters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pardon my language, but he didn&amp;#39;t half-ass this story. He literally jumps the train (aka &amp;quot;The Beast), riding the same rails that have maimed and killed so many before him. He heads deep into cartel territory to try and capture the fear that they&amp;#39;ve gripped the nation with. He interviews trafficked women to try and bring their story to light. One of his contacts on the journey calls him as he&amp;#39;s captured by the cartel. He encounters corrupt officials and indifferent law enforcement officers. It&amp;#39;s an absolutely harrowing journey that he somehow captures with steadfast determination and grace. Anyone who is at all interested in this subject matter, or even if you&amp;#39;re not, should absolutely read this book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only regret I don&amp;#39;t have is that I don&amp;#39;t speak Spanish and had to read a translated version. Those who do speak the language, I&amp;#39;d recommend reading the original entitled &amp;quot;Los migrantes que no importan&amp;quot; (The Migrants Who Don&amp;#39;t Matter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于神话和故事的书籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好!

我正在寻找有关阿拉伯神话的书籍。我已经读过 "一千零一夜"，所以如果你们有任何推荐，我将很高兴参加。
和一个晚上"，所以如果你有任何推荐，我很乐意看一下。
看一看 :)

我对其他类型的神话也很感兴趣--中国、日本或北欧神话。
北欧的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5l1gx/books_about_mythology_and_tales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5l1gx/books_about_mythology_and_tales/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:16:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi All!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for books about Arabian mythology. I have already read &amp;quot;One thousand and one nights&amp;quot;, so if you have any recommandations, I will be happy to take a look :) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also interested in other kinds of mythologies - Chinese, Japanese or Nordic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么每个人都知道北欧神话或贝奥武夫，却不知道芬兰的卡勒瓦拉？好吧，终于有一个以卡勒瓦拉（Tolkien's LOTR和Silmarillion的主要灵感来源）为背景的系列作品了，我太兴奋了！"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这本书叫《熊族的标记》，作者是大卫-施莱弗。这是一本不知名的
我已经在论坛上关注了很久，但我非常兴奋
现在它终于发行了。卡勒瓦拉（Kalevala）可以归功于，至少是
部分归功于我们今天在幻想中看到的大量原型。在《卡勒瓦拉》中，我们可以看到很多的原型。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5ojwt/why_does_everyone_know_of_norse_mythology_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5ojwt/why_does_everyone_know_of_norse_mythology_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kalevala can be attributed, at least partially, to a ton of the archetypes we see in fantasy today. In large part, that’s due to the fact it inspired Tolkien and quite a few elements, and even some characters, of the Lord of the Rings come right out of the Kalevala. Despite that, it seems like no one knows about it! I remember reading Beowulf in school TWICE and never even knew about the Finnish epic poems. Is that common everywhere? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well now there’s at least a series set within that mythos. I only know about it from specific forums, but the book is Mark of the Bear Clan by David Schlaefer.  I hope these books make the Kalevala more well known, because I think it’s so underrepresented right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这是一本必读的书--《西游记》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这本书是世界上我绝对喜欢的书。它的作者是埃伦
拉斯金写的，她是一位著名的儿童读物插画师。她没有为这本书打草稿
也没有书面的基础设施，但她却写出了一个非常相互联系和
精致的故事。该书获得了1979年纽伯瑞奖。

这本书...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o582r2/this_is_a_must_read_the_westing_game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o582r2/this_is_a_must_read_the_westing_game/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 07:59:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is my absolute favorite book in the world. It was written by Ellen Raskin, a pronounced children&amp;#39;s book illustrator. She did no drafts of the book and no written infrastructure, yet she produced a very interconnected and exquisite story. The book won the 1979 Newbery Medal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book follows 16 people who have chosen to become heirs of an estate worth over $200 million belonging to a famous game-loving millionaire, Sam Westing. No one knows why Sam Westing has chosen 16 seemingly random people to inherit his vast fortune, but that won&amp;#39;t stop him from playing one last game, even if it is from beyond the grave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genre: Mystery, Action&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Published 1978 by Ellen Raskin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookshop.org为响应Prime Day，今明两天免运费]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bookshop.org为您从当地书店购买的商品提供货源，这是一项伟大的服务。
它是一项伟大的服务，有助于支持当地企业，否则这些企业将在网络竞争和电子书中挣扎。
在线竞争和电子书。在今天和明天，他们提供免费
来与亚马逊总理日竞争。有一本书你可以...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o55mm3/bookshoporg_has_free_shipping_today_and_tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o55mm3/bookshoporg_has_free_shipping_today_and_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 22:25:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bookshop.org sources your purchases from your local bookstores, it&amp;#39;s a great service that helps support local businesses that are otherwise struggling with online competition and e-books. For today and tomorrow they&amp;#39;re offering free shipping to compete with Amazon Prime Day. There&amp;#39;s a book you can contemplating, it&amp;#39;s a good time to snatch one up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[让你感到快乐和冒险的书籍，让你再次爱上生活，没有太多的悲伤或悲剧的书籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一段有毒的关系之后，我正在经历一个非常艰难的分手。泪水已经够多了
现在我想找回那种火花，再次享受生活。

我更喜欢没有爱情的书，但如果是一个小的次要情节也可以。请帮助
我吧!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o4r0dx/books_that_make_you_feel_happy_and_adventurous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o4r0dx/books_that_make_you_feel_happy_and_adventurous/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:11:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going through a very tough breakup after a toxic relationship. Enough tears have been shed, now I want to find that spark back and enjoy life again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I prefer books without romance but if it&amp;#39;s a small subplot it&amp;#39;s ok. Please help me out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>