<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 20:23:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[如果你提供收银机，我会提供技术分析]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。短短两个交易周的背靠背，我发现自己做得太多了。
我手上的时间都在等周一，所以如果你有股票行情的话，你会想要一个
然后对长期和短期趋势进行快速、有记录的技术分析
请随时给我发收件箱。总是想尽我所能帮你。这是…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kpidxf/ill_provide_technical_analysis_if_you_provide_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kpidxf/ill_provide_technical_analysis_if_you_provide_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 19:05:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all. With 2 short trading weeks back-to-back, I find myself with too much time on my hands waiting for monday so if you have a ticker you would like a quick and recorded technical analysis of long-term and short-term trend then feel free to inbox me. Always trying to help however I can. This is the year of the Retail Trader!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I plan to do the Analysis in sets of 2 starting with the most commonly asked for tickers first. Will have all analysis and videos done within the next few hours but feel free to provide more tickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: video uploads and requests a can be found and done in  &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investingandtrading&quot;&gt;r/investingandtrading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年将是铀投资者难忘的一年(15个强大的催化剂已经到位)]]></title><description><![CDATA[过去几个月对铀投资者来说是相当多事，股票
整个行业的公司都在大幅升值。那里
造成这种情况的原因有很多，感觉就是不同于
季节性很强。下面是15件“第一次”看起来像…的东西]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kpjvhs/2021_will_be_an_unforgettable_year_for_uranium/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kpjvhs/2021_will_be_an_unforgettable_year_for_uranium/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 17:41:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last few months have been quite eventful for uranium investors, with shares of companies all across the sector appreciating in value substantially. There have been many reasons why this is the case and it feels different to just being strong seasonality. Below are 15 ‘first time’ things to look out for in this sector to start the year with, with full credit going to John Quakes (@quakes99 on Twitter), a retired earth sciences researcher, professor, analyst, writer and one of the best public sources for news about the uranium sector. I share his view that 2021 will prove to be an incredible year for the uranium sector and subsequently for anyone invested in it. Now, onto the aforementioned ‘first times’: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time entering a new year with uranium already in a record supply deficit, which is set to deepen further with 2 major mines permanently closing this year in Australia and Niger (~7 million pounds, gone). At the same time, demand for nuclear energy has remained strong throughout the COVID-19 pandemic and continues to grow in a global shift to decarbonize industry dependent on fossil fuels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that Cameco, the world’s 2nd largest producer, has begun a new year with every one of its uranium mines in Canada shut down. Both of the world’s 2 largest uranium mines are under care and maintenance, resulting in zero lbs being produced in Canada as we enter 2021. The US is also producing zero lbs while Kazakhstan’s production is at a multi-year low that is likely to continue thru 2022 under the nation’s current flex-down program and pandemic related mining disruptions. All uranium mines in the Ukraine have also been shut down due to the inability of the mine operator to pay the wages of 5000 mine workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fist time that at least 3 of the world’s largest uranium producers are forced into buying uranium on the spot market. Cameco is now the largest spot market buyer in the world. World’s largest producer Kazatomprom is now also a spot buyer, as is French Orano given that heir Canadian mills are suspended and their Cominak mine in Africa is heading for closure in March. Inventory held by the world’s largest uranium producers is at rock bottom levels for the first time ever and in need of replenishment this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time the US has taken steps to support its domestic uranium mining industry by establishing a strategic uranium reserve, a 10 year buying program (1.5 billion dollars total) whereby the US government will purchase, convert and potentially enrich US mined uranium to create an emergency supply for US reactors. Goal is to ensure at least 2 US uranium mining companies remain active and viable during this time when the commodity price of U3O8 is half the cost of production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time in several decades that there is strong bipartisan support in the US to rebuild the existing nuclear energy industry and manufacture a new generation of advanced reactors on a global scale, which is seen as a high priority in order to catch up with Russia and China who have become the new world leaders in nuclear energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that uranium equities have entered a bull market when there is an actual supply deficit. The last bull market saw the price of uranium skyrocket on mine floods and other events that created the ‘fear’ of a supply deficit on the horizon, at a time when the US-Russia Megatons to Megawatts program was still continuing to supply 20m lbs per year to US nuclear utilities, a program that continued until 2021 as the world’s largest virtual uranium mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that a new year begins with spot market supplies significantly depleted. Supply accessible to carry traders has been severely reduced. Kazatomprom no longer sells any lbs into the spot market and Orano’s supply from Canada and Niger is at a record low level, pushing nuclear utilities to secure new long term contracts with producers rather than entering into shorter term contracts with carry traders. Security of supply is a top priority of utilities (whose inventories are estimated to be around 2,5 years’ worth of supply, when the guideline is to never let it drop below 2-3 years given the long time it takes to enrich and deliver the fuel to the reactors).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that US and European nuclear utilities have begun a new year with inventories drawn down below usual safety margins at the same time that mines supply is in a record deficit and global uranium production is at its lowest level in 12 years. The new 2020 IAEA/NEA uranium Red Book projects that secondary supplies will fall in the future as an overdue utility inventory restocking cycle begins, due to higher levels of contracting, conversion and enrichment that will reduce underfeeding as facilities see their utilization rates rise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time in several years that there are no geopolitical overhangs holding back the uranium contracting plans of US and European nuclear utilities. There are no potential section 232 actions targeting uranium imports and no sanctions likely against UUN participants (Russia, China, UK, Germany, France) in the JCPOA Iran Nuclear deal. Russia and the US have successfully negotiated a 20-year extension to the Russian Suspension Agreement that will see the US imports from Russia decline over the coming 2 decades. The incoming US administration supports keeping nuclear power plants running and plans to immediately rejoin the Paris Climate Accord, pushing for global net zero emissions by 2050, a process in which nuclear energy will play a major role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that nations around the world will be recovering from a global pandemic with massive infrastructure spending programs that include boosting nuclear capacity to achieve net zero carbon emissions goals. A new ‘nuclear renaissance’ is beginning to take shape on pandemic recovery spending to boost clean energy. The perception of nuclear energy is also changing to that of a safe, reliable, necessary baseload power source that fits with an emerging ESG investing model. Decarbonization has become a new buzz word in the global vocabulary. The ‘electrification of everything’ from cars, buses, trucks and trains to major industry is the new global target. Sustainability of so-called renewables solar and wind is now being called into question after failures by Germany and California to successfully transition to an economy powered by intermittent energy sources. Higher electricity prices, no net carbon emissions reductions and rolling blackouts have demonstrated how ‘renewables’ are not able to fulfill their early promise. This might change with new battery technology and better implementation, but we are nowhere near that point yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that uranium stocks are entering a new year on the heels of one of their best performance years since the last bull market. The U3O8 spot price is still one-half the global average cost of production that will incentivize new mines to be built this decade. This signals to investors that we are still at the opening pitch of the first inning of a long game yet to play out. A necessary doubling of the U3O8 commodity price is yet to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that Canada has begun a new year embarking on a small modular reactors build-out program with several provinces pledging to deploy SMR’s to power remote communities, mines and industrial heat applications in the energy industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time that nuclear is being viewed as the ideal carbon free high-temperature power source to produce clear hydrogen fuel. US, Russia, Japan and others are looking to leverage their existing nuclear power capacity to produce hydrogen and build high-temperature SMR’s to optimize the use of emissions free nuclear to produce zero emissions hydrogen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time in decades that there is an emerging surge in acceptance of nuclear  of nuclear energy as necessary to achieve zero carbon emissions goals, with countries like the Netherlands looking to add more capacity after conducting studies showing nuclear is safer and cheaper than variable renewable energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time I can recall one of the leading nuclear fuel consultants UxC reporting to their subscribers that uranium is in a 57M lbs mined supply deficit, that utility and supplier inventories are “declining at a rapid rate” just as global fuel demand growth is accelerating, a clear signal that a bull market is getting underway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: with all the catalysts that are in place, I am of the firm believe that uranium related equities, namely the developers and explorers, will offer returns that will outperform any other broad investment asset class/sector in the market. This is a bold claim to make, but I can’t see any other opportunity that offers even close to the same risk vs reward the uranium sector offers. Read my other posts on the subject to get an idea of what companies you might want to look at and to get an answer to any question you might have. Good luck and here is to a great new year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国科技亿万富翁马云被从自己的真人秀节目中除名，在因反监管言论本身与习主席发生冲突后，他已经两个月没有公开露面了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9108421/Chinese-tech-billionaire-Jack-Ma-not-seen-public-TWO-MONTHS.html

读这封信有点乱七八糟的。感觉中国并不关心巴巴是否会被烧死
倒在地上。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kpn41c/chinese_tech_billionaire_jack_ma_was_removed_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kpn41c/chinese_tech_billionaire_jack_ma_was_removed_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 17:41:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9108421/Chinese-tech-billionaire-Jack-Ma-not-seen-public-TWO-MONTHS.html&quot;&gt;https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9108421/Chinese-tech-billionaire-Jack-Ma-not-seen-public-TWO-MONTHS.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reading this is kind of messed up. Feels like China doesn&amp;#39;t care if BABA burns to the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有谁是贪婪的狗屎？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpk6l2/anyone_else_a_greedy_piece_of_shit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpk6l2/anyone_else_a_greedy_piece_of_shit/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 16:53:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我已经准备好2021年的网球了]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpdx8n/im_ready_for_some_2021_tendies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpdx8n/im_ready_for_some_2021_tendies/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 16:53:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[那么，在我们进入2021年之际，你们现在倾向于哪些投机性投资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的大部分投资都是先锋指数基金(VTSAX值得称赞)，但
我在考虑尝试一些风险更高的投资项目，比如股票，
ETF，密码，或者其他任何东西！不会受伤的，对吧？我年轻，没有债务，没有
孩子们，不用花大价钱。不如试着做点药，…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kp50lm/so_what_speculative_investments_are_you_guys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kp50lm/so_what_speculative_investments_are_you_guys/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 16:53:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of my investments are in Vanguard index funds (praise be to the VTSAX), but I&amp;#39;m thinking about dipping my toes into some riskier ventures, be they stocks, ETFs, crypto, or whatever!  Couldn&amp;#39;t hurt, right?  I&amp;#39;m young with no debt, no kids, no major expenses.  Might as well try to make some dosh, yeah?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what do you guys have planned?  Any big moves you plan on making in 2021 compared to last year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉上海制造的Model Y受到热烈欢迎，因为中国买家争先恐后地订购价格有竞争力的SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.scmp.com/business/companies/article/3116253/teslas-shanghai-made-model-y-gets-rousing-reception-chinese

特斯拉大幅降价其中国制造的Model Y汽车，以吸引中国的司机
全球最大的电动汽车市场，加大了其全球市场的压力
和…的中国竞争对手]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kplo25/teslas_shanghaimade_model_y_gets_rousing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kplo25/teslas_shanghaimade_model_y_gets_rousing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 16:53:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.scmp.com/business/companies/article/3116253/teslas-shanghai-made-model-y-gets-rousing-reception-chinese&quot;&gt;https://www.scmp.com/business/companies/article/3116253/teslas-shanghai-made-model-y-gets-rousing-reception-chinese&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla has slashed prices of its made-in-China Model Y cars to woo drivers in the world’s largest electric vehicle market, ratcheting up pressure on its global and Chinese rivals that focus on the premium segment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Long Range version of Model Y starts from 339,000 yuan (US$52,074), excluding a government subsidy, 30 per cent cheaper than the price quoted six months ago when presale orders could first be placed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local media reported that some drivers who previously ordered cars by Tesla challengers – NIO, Xpeng and Li Auto – have reneged on their contracts and were looking to buy Model Y.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[当所有比特币都兑换成美元时，将会出现恶性通货膨胀。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345716425772695552</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345716425772695552</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 16:00:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>There’s going to be hyperinflation when all the Bitcoin gets converted into dollars.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在他们1.78美元的时候卖出了NIO，错过了他们的快速上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[我要为这件事自杀了。我是在两年多前了解到NIO的，当时他们
是“60分钟”的特色节目，是r/nio上的首批活跃用户之一。
[/r/nio]。当时，股票是10美元，我买了500股。但是在他们的
在首次公开募股(IPO)期间，他们经历了艰难的一年，销售额不断下降。尽管如此，I…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kpjmim/i_sold_nio_when_they_were_178_and_missed_out_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kpjmim/i_sold_nio_when_they_were_178_and_missed_out_on/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 15:30:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m killing myself over this. I learned about NIO over two years ago when they were featured on 60 Minutes and was one of the first active users on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/Nio&quot;&gt;r/Nio&lt;/a&gt;. Back then, the stock was 10$, and I bought 500 shares. But after their IPO, they had a rough year with declining sales. Despite that, I kept buying in to eventually accumulate 3,200 shares at an average price of 3.12$.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then came more bad news and worse sales. People were talking about the company running out of cash and the stock going to 0$, and they did eventually hit 1.00$. I sold at 1.78$ before that happened and took my 57% loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve only been investing for two years, but it&amp;#39;s my biggest regret so far. I should have never listened to some asshole at Bloomberg getting paid to write negative articles and trusted my gut. NIO is a solid company and is going to be one the leaders in the Chinese and global EV market. They completely restructured after those losses (Nio Places vs. Nio Houses, fired staff, etc.), and those 3,200 shares are worth over 150,000$ today. They&amp;#39;ll be worth even more in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I can do now is take this as a learning experience, but I feel like I&amp;#39;ll never find another stock like them. Sigh ...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone here contacted the Reddit Care Team. Thank you for the laugh ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我整个人生的故事]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpj5t3/the_story_of_my_life/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpj5t3/the_story_of_my_life/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 15:30:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你只能逃避现实这么久]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kphiiz/you_can_only_run_from_reality_for_so_long/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kphiiz/you_can_only_run_from_reality_for_so_long/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 15:30:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在过去的24小时里，还有其他人在关注比特币的涨势吗？见鬼，这是怎么回事？]]></title><description><![CDATA[从昨天早上开始，比特币在大约2小时内从29K涨到33K，然后
一下子跌到了30K，从那以后就一直在不停地撕裂。直达
牛市上涨，疯狂的资金获取。它现在的位置略低于34750
截至本帖子[https://i.imgur.com/49fT6Bu.png].不管…是什么]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kpgi2r/has_anyone_else_been_following_the_bitcoin_run/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kpgi2r/has_anyone_else_been_following_the_bitcoin_run/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:32:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting yesterday morning bitcoin went from 29k to 33k in like 2 hrs, it then instantly crashed to 30k and has gone on an absolute tear ever since.  Non stop bull rally with insane amounts of money acquiring.  It now sits just under 34750 &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/49fT6Bu.png&quot;&gt;as of this post&lt;/a&gt;.       Whatever is driving this run, it seems institutionally funded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never been a big crypto market player but making +18% on a closed market is too juicy to pass up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我看到你年轻的凯西和我带给你一个更年轻的(与NeuRA有关的)埃隆。TSLA 1800 eoy]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpdt60/i_see_your_young_cathie_and_i_raise_you_a_younger/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpdt60/i_see_your_young_cathie_and_i_raise_you_a_younger/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 11:36:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[合法并不比赌博好]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpg83k/legit_no_better_than_gambling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kpg83k/legit_no_better_than_gambling/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 10:43:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nio Inc.提供2020年12月、第四季度和全年交付更新]]></title><description><![CDATA[*NIO在2020年12月交付了7,007辆汽车，增长了121.0
与去年同期相比
*NIO在截至2020年12月的三个月中交付了17,353辆汽车，
同比增长111.0%
*NIO在2020年总共交付了43,728辆汽车，增长了112.6
与去年同期相比

NiO…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kph4ut/nio_inc_provides_december_fourth_quarter_and_full/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kph4ut/nio_inc_provides_december_fourth_quarter_and_full/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 10:43:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NIO delivered 7,007 vehicles in December 2020, increasing by 121.0% year-over-year&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NIO delivered 17,353 vehicles in the three months ended December 2020, increasing by 111.0% year-over-year&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NIO delivered 43,728 vehicles in 2020 in total, increasing by 112.6% year-over-year&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NIO delivered 7,007 vehicles in December 2020, setting a new monthly record representing a strong 121.0% year-over-year growth. The deliveries consisted of 2,009 ES8s, the Company’s 6-seater and 7-seater flagship premium smart electric SUV, 2,493 ES6s, the Company’s 5-seater high-performance premium smart electric SUV, and 2,505 EC6s, the Company’s 5-seater premium electric coupe SUV. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NIO delivered 17,353 vehicles in the fourth quarter of 2020, representing an increase of 111.0% year-over-year and exceeding the higher end of the Company’s quarterly guidance. As of December 31, 2020, cumulative deliveries of the ES8, ES6 and EC6 reached 75,641 vehicles, of which 43,728 were delivered in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[说服我不要买PLTR]]></title><description><![CDATA[除了估值很高之外，你还会给出什么理由不买呢？
购买PLTR？他们已经与政府机构签订了合同，并且
通过进入他们的潜在市场，有很大的增长空间。该公司
是由公认的赢家创立的。看看贝宝(PayPal)和Facebook吧。那是…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kp85rw/convince_me_not_to_buy_pltr/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kp85rw/convince_me_not_to_buy_pltr/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 08:42:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides it having a high valuation, what other reasons would you give for not buying PLTR? They have contracts with government agencies already and have plenty of room for growth by tapping into their addressable market. The company is founded by proven winners. Look at PayPal and Facebook. That’s who’s behind this company. Who would their main competition be? Is there any reason they might not become profitable in the future?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我只知道🚀的意思是买。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp8z2e/all_i_know_is_means_buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp8z2e/all_i_know_is_means_buy/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 06:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们的方舟女王在古代努力工作🚀]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp9wwc/our_ark_queen_hard_at_work_in_the_ancient_times/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp9wwc/our_ark_queen_hard_at_work_in_the_ancient_times/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 06:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们可能不会进入泡沫的原因]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到很多帖子把它与2000年的网络泡沫相提并论。这是一个
为什么我们不可能达到接近2000的疯狂水平。

第一：在互联网时代，纳斯达克综合指数的市盈率
估值高达200英镑。相比之下，该指数今天的市盈率为…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kpeffw/reasons_we_may_not_be_in_a_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kpeffw/reasons_we_may_not_be_in_a_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 06:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m seeing a lot of posts comparing this to the 2000 dot-com bubble. Here&amp;#39;s a breakdown of why we&amp;#39;re likely not anywhere close to 2000 levels of craziness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First:&lt;/strong&gt;  During the dot-com era, the Nasdaq Composite&amp;#39;s price-to-earnings valuation ran up as high as 200. By comparison, the index&amp;#39;s P/E today is a relatively tame 28, only modestly higher from 23 at the end of 2019. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second:&lt;/strong&gt; Interest rates were a very attractive 6% which provided a strong alternative to stocks. No such outlet exists today unless you trust bitcoin, or want to invest in paper gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third:&lt;/strong&gt; Much of the value gains we&amp;#39;re seeing in the market can be tied directly to the fact that people who invest are making similar or better money this year, and spending significantly less causing them to save more and invest more:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/01/upshot/why-markets-boomed-2020.html&quot;&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/01/upshot/why-markets-boomed-2020.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fourth:&lt;/strong&gt; The rest of the growth can largely be attributed to increased liquidity from all of the money printing. Stocks tend to mirror an increase in the money supply with their value making them a great hedge against inflation. The valuations of the 2000s weren&amp;#39;t backstopped by QE or increased savings, making them much shakier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fifth:&lt;/strong&gt; The money printing will likely go on for a while. People mistakenly assume we&amp;#39;re printing against our 22T dollar economy when we&amp;#39;re really printing against the 80-100T global economy for which are the reserve currency. A weak dollar benefits the global economy, and benefits us because we are the trading floor for the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a long but very illuminating read on why QE is necessary and actually helpful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lynalden.com/fraying-petrodollar-system/&quot;&gt;https://www.lynalden.com/fraying-petrodollar-system/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Take:&lt;/strong&gt; There are a few stocks that are out of control with their valuations (Hi TSLA!), and a few sectors that are overvalued, but overall the market looks to be on sturdy ground with the increased savings, and the increased liquidity. There will be peaks and valleys, but I think there&amp;#39;s a lot of room to grow, especially once the vaccine is widespread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗斯的十大股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你刚从大学毕业，你在罗斯个人退休帐户(Roth IRA)中排名前10的股票是什么？
今天，在你的领域找到一份工作(假设你大约22-24岁，
最高可达每年6,000元的供款限额)。我的理由是选择
在他们的技术客户经理中处于市场领先地位，并且颠覆了…的规范]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kp0jjc/top_10_stocks_for_roth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kp0jjc/top_10_stocks_for_roth/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 06:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What would be your top 10 stocks in a Roth IRA if you were fresh outta college today and have a job in your field (let&amp;#39;s say you are about 22-24 years old and can max out the contribution limit of $6,000/year). My rationale is to pick market leaders in their TAM and are disruptive to the norm of conventional business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This would be my top 10:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mecardo Libre&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shopify&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Trade Desk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CRISPR (or ARKG)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Square&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alibaba (or Teladoc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not see a point in dividend stocks like PG, Coke, Caterpillar, etc. when you are young and have 30+ years for these stocks to grow and go through their ups and downs. My plan is to let these positions grow and then cash out when I retire and invest in safe dividend stocks for income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If my rationale is twisted or wrong in any way please let me know. I am open to criticism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你们难道不担心你们是鞋匠吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我经常想起约瑟夫·肯尼迪著名的鞋帮系列，当然它是
可能他只是在掩盖内幕交易，这种情绪仍然存在。这个
我经常担心的是：我是鞋匠吗？我是不是卷入了这件事
市场预示着什么不好的东西吗？我26岁，没有受过这方面的教育，…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kp1nc3/arent_you_guys_ever_worried_that_youre_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kp1nc3/arent_you_guys_ever_worried_that_youre_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 01:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think about Joseph Kennedys famous Shoe shiner line a lot, granted it was probably him just covering for insider trading, the sentiment still remains. The thing I worry about often is: am I the shoe shiner? Is my involvement in this market indicative of something bad? Im 26, no schooling on this, I just google and research stuff independently. Maybe its a bad sign that Im involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess the major discussion points I intended for this thread are this: How do you not become the Shoeshiner?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you separate yourself from an average trader and gain that edge?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir刚刚更新了他们的网站，准备发行“哥谭泰坦”(Gotham Titan)。他们有他们的软件的gif在运行！]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kousvv/palantir_just_updated_their_website_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kousvv/palantir_just_updated_their_website_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 01:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你在频谱中处于什么位置？？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp2jgc/where_are_you_on_the_spectrum/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp2jgc/where_are_you_on_the_spectrum/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 01:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是过去30年来标准普尔500指数中排名前30位的股票……

通过@ycharts https://t.co/QDO7kTQyiZ提供的数据]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345491526265274368</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345491526265274368</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 23:46:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>These are the top 30 stocks in the S&amp;amp;P 500 over the past 30 years...

Data via @ycharts https://t.co/QDO7kTQyiZ</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有这里。我们。去。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/koyq6k/and_here_we_go/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/koyq6k/and_here_we_go/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 23:46:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是如何在赔钱的情况下赚钱的]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一种非常简单的方法。每当我要花钱的时候，我都会问自己
“我宁愿用这笔钱买OTM电话吗？”95%的时间里，
答案是肯定的。

我在过去的6个月里没有买过任何非必需品。没有新消息
衣服，游戏机，电子游戏。只购买基本…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp3gpl/how_im_making_money_while_i_lose_money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp3gpl/how_im_making_money_while_i_lose_money/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 23:46:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a very simple method. Whenever I&amp;#39;m about to spend money, I ask myself &amp;quot;would I rather buy OTM calls with this money instead?&amp;quot;. 95% of the time, the answer is yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t bought any non essential items in the last 6 months now. No new clothes, game consoles, video games. Only buy basic groceries and don&amp;#39;t order out. I also began cutting my own hair. I still spend money when I want to invest in myself though. Probably saved $3000 these past months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now hypothetically, even if I lose 90% of my money in yolo calls, I&amp;#39;m still up $300. It&amp;#39;s impossible to lose money with this method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[它真的不能翘起来]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp66wf/it_literally_cant_go_tits_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp66wf/it_literally_cant_go_tits_up/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 23:46:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为我的新公寓做一些装饰]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp3lna/some_decoration_for_my_new_apartment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp3lna/some_decoration_for_my_new_apartment/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 23:46:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[警方突击搜查加拿大一户人家非法集会6人
https://t.co/FNdDWfTSKL]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345453159305588737</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345453159305588737</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 22:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>POLICE RAID CANADIAN HOME FOR HAVING ILLEGAL GATHERING OF 6 PEOPLE
https://t.co/FNdDWfTSKL</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[技术泡沫的经验教训-(@corry_Wang提供)]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在推特上看到了这个帖子，我觉得这是一个很棒的观点
90年代的网络泡沫上有很多东西。有关参考资料，请参阅
推特帖子在这里[https://twitter.com/corry_wang/status/1345192541545766915]
它有一些很棒的注释和图表，我没有粘贴…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kp42c1/lessons_from_the_tech_bubble_courtesy_of_corry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kp42c1/lessons_from_the_tech_bubble_courtesy_of_corry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 22:43:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across this thread on twitter and thought it was a fantastic view on a lot of things from the 90&amp;#39;s dotcom bubble. For reference, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/corry_wang/status/1345192541545766915&quot;&gt;please refer to the Twitter thread here&lt;/a&gt; which has some fantastic notes and charts that I did not paste into the transcript below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since there have been so many comparisons recently discussing tech froth, I think this is a wonderful share, especially for the majority of people here who were not investors during that time period. Definitely sheds a lot of light on some popular market cliches that misconstrue that period (IE, &amp;quot;you can only recognize a bubble in hindsight&amp;quot;).  I do not know or follow this person, but still thought this was worth sharing as I came across it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lessons:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lessons From The Tech Bubble:  Last year, I spent my winter holiday reading hundreds of pages of equity research from the 1999/2000 era, to try to understand what it was like investing during the bubble  A few people recently asked me for my takeaways. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here they are - Every document hereon comes from my former employer Bernstein Research&amp;#39;s internal research archive, which extend back to 1994  Unfortunately, they&amp;#39;re not available to the public (even Bernstein&amp;#39;s client website cuts off at 2003), but happy to give more details if necessary (see twitter thread for graphic documents).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON #1&lt;/strong&gt;: Everybody knew it was a bubble  Unfortunately, the quip &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s not a bubble if everyone says it is&amp;quot; just isn&amp;#39;t true  Investors were comparing the internet sector to tulip mania as early as mid-98. Bernstein held an entire conference on it in June 99! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON #2:&lt;/strong&gt; Calling bubbles is easy, making money is hard  In truth, the hard part about the tech bubble wasn&amp;#39;t noticing it. The hard part was timing it  Our equity strategist tried in January 99... he was off by 14 months (and another 30 point gap in value vs growth) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON #3:&lt;/strong&gt; Nobody knew the bubble popped until months after it did  Nobody noticed in March 2000 when it finally popped. Our equity strategist (who bet his career on it!) didn&amp;#39;t catch on until June &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON #4:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;Tech&amp;quot; bubble was a misnomer... it was really a large cap growth bubble  See the valuation table below, 1 year before the top  Yes, Microsoft traded at 70x earnings. But Coca Cola was 43x. Pfizer was 92x. Every stock here was a disaster over the next 10 years... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON #5:&lt;/strong&gt; Most large cap tech stocks in the bubble had real businesses with strong fundamentals  The internet stocks were a sideshow. In 2000, the software sector had a $1 trillion market cap, 20% net margins, 20% annual growth  The problem? It was trading at 16x sales &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LESSON #6:&lt;/strong&gt; Fundamentals follow price, not vice versa  The bubble popped in Q1 2000. Fundamentals didn&amp;#39;t decelerate until Q4 2000.   It was reflexivity at work. Lower stock prices = less capex spend = less revenue growth = lower stock prices. A vicious cycle &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s the takeaway here?   Be humble.  For bears, it&amp;#39;s easy to call a bubble. Anybody can do that. Timing is the hard part  For bulls, it&amp;#39;s easy to point to the fundamentals. Historical investors weren&amp;#39;t dumb. The hard part is matching fundamentals with price...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉是去年标准普尔500指数中表现最好的股票，遥遥领先(注：特斯拉直到12/21才加入标准普尔500指数)。https://t.co/5d49MTA3lk美国电话服务级别协议]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345415909591154689</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345415909591154689</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 21:54:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tesla was the best performing stock in the S&amp;amp;P 500 last year by a wide margin (note: Tesla did not join the S&amp;amp;P 500 until 12/21). $TSLA https://t.co/5d49MTA3lk</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉2020年交付499,550辆汽车，略低于目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-01-02/tesla-delivers-499-550-electric-cars-in-2020-just-shy-of-target?srnd=premium

正如标题和文章所说-特斯拉在第四季度交付了约18万辆汽车，并
2020年交付的汽车略低于50万辆。

恕我直言，我想知道你是如何…的]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kp0o5j/tesla_delivers_499550_vehicles_in_2020_just_shy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kp0o5j/tesla_delivers_499550_vehicles_in_2020_just_shy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 21:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-01-02/tesla-delivers-499-550-electric-cars-in-2020-just-shy-of-target?srnd=premium&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-01-02/tesla-delivers-499-550-electric-cars-in-2020-just-shy-of-target?srnd=premium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the title and the article says - Tesla delivered ~180k cars in q4 and were just shy of 500k delivered cars for 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without exerting my bias, I&amp;#39;m wondering how you guys are interpreting this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[他们会为你的股票给你商店积分。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/konr0f/theyll_give_you_store_credit_for_your_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/konr0f/theyll_give_you_store_credit_for_your_shares/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 21:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你们都知道范型📈📈]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp0tcw/you_all_know_the_paradigm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kp0tcw/you_all_know_the_paradigm/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 21:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[过去10年的资产类别回报.

发信人：https://t.co/ctsmWg0Luc

通过@ycharts https://t.co/Vf8a2WMrNf提供的数据]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345399729056849921</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345399729056849921</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 20:53:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Asset Class Returns over the last 10 Years...

Post: https://t.co/ctsmWg0Luc

Data via @ycharts https://t.co/Vf8a2WMrNf</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[84岁以上的美国人约有550万(占总人口的1.8%)。这一年龄段占所有冠状病毒死亡人数的32%。

今天就让军队参与进来，让每个人都接种84+疫苗。可以在一周内完成，并将减少近三分之一的死亡人数。https://t.co/Tc9eIGSKAy]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345458941187268615</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345458941187268615</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 20:53:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>There are around 5.5 million Americans over the age of 84 (1.8% of population). This age group has accounted for 32% of all Covid-19 deaths.

Get the military involved today to get everyone 84+ vaccinated. Could be done in a week and would cut deaths down by almost a third. https://t.co/Tc9eIGSKAy</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易所交易的自闭症患者]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kowzuy/exchangetraded_autists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kowzuy/exchangetraded_autists/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 20:31:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去年罗素1000指数中表现最佳的股票.

1)特斯拉美国电话服务级别协议：+743%.
2)相能量$ENPH：+572%
3)Peloton品钛on：+434%.
4)现代$mRNA：+434%
5)缩放缩放https://t.co/t6xeWpKL8Z：+396%Zoom视频]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345420895347744774</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345420895347744774</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Best Performing Stocks in the Russell 1000 last year...

1) Tesla $TSLA: +743%
2) Enphase Energy $ENPH: +572%
3) Peloton $PTON: +434%
4) Moderna $MRNA: +434%
5) Zoom $ZM: +396% https://t.co/t6xeWpKL8Z</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币3.2万美元。https://t.co/55MOkOyAKs TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345404190231818243</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345404190231818243</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin $32,000. $BTC https://t.co/55MOkOyAKs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们应该让亚马逊和沃尔玛负责分发疫苗的物流。

贝佐斯会在24小时内解决这个问题]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345438280129646592</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345438280129646592</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We should just have Amazon and Walmart run the logistics for distributing the vaccine

Bezos would have this solved in 24 hrs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“除了我，你不能相信任何人。”]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/koy5ij/you_cant_trust_anyone_except_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/koy5ij/you_cant_trust_anyone_except_me/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1901年，我们有了第一个10亿美元的市值。到最近为止，我们已经达到了第一个万亿美元的市值。第一家市值达到万亿美元的公司将是什么？为什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[什么行业(或多个行业)会实事求是地、可行地运作？
在……里面?

在这个过程中，哪些行业最终会被颠覆？

有问题的企业将如何管理它，以使他们能够
维持上述市值水平，而不是泡沫或…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kokzef/in_1901_we_had_the_first_billion_dollar_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kokzef/in_1901_we_had_the_first_billion_dollar_market/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what industry (or industries) would it realistically and feasibly operate in?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What industries would end up being disrupted in the process?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And how would the business in question manage it in such a way that they&amp;#39;re able to sustain said level of market cap, as opposed to it being a bubble or one-time occurrence?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir发布关于哥谭泰坦项目的信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.palantir.com/palantir-gotham/titan/

我不太明白它的作用，但我猜它与
蝙蝠侠和对泰坦的攻击。

不管怎样，更多的确认天网正在部署。他们将展示
1月26日他们的技术，我怀疑这将是一辆黑色的…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kozriu/palantir_releases_information_on_project_gotham/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kozriu/palantir_releases_information_on_project_gotham/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.palantir.com/palantir-gotham/titan/&quot;&gt;https://www.palantir.com/palantir-gotham/titan/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t really understand what it does but I&amp;#39;m assuming it has something to do with batman and attack on titan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, more confirmation that skynet is being deployed. They will showcase their technology on Jan 26th, I suspect this will be a black turtle neck level event. Bullish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[等待周末股市开市。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/koy5bm/waiting_for_stock_market_to_open_during_looooong/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/koy5bm/waiting_for_stock_market_to_open_during_looooong/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币3.3万美元。https://t.co/jrQRNUQNh6 TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345410064748851207</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345410064748851207</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 17:45:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin $33,000. $BTC https://t.co/jrQRNUQNh6</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币3.1万美元。https://t.co/uYGCT9Kzha TC巴恩斯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345395866371317763</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345395866371317763</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 16:55:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bitcoin $31,000. $BTC https://t.co/uYGCT9Kzha</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我从没想过我会讨厌周末！]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kowb1h/i_never_thought_i_would_hate_the_weekend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kowb1h/i_never_thought_i_would_hate_the_weekend/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 16:55:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为所有产品定价，就像它们是下一个AMZN一样(TSLA故事)]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前在这个市场上让我感到惊讶的一件事是，它感觉像是
我们试图证明每一家新出现的热门技术/成长型公司都是合理的，就好像他们是
他们领域里的下一个AMZN。我认为人们产生的一种错觉
最近他们关注的是人们对AMZN5…的预测]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/koyjya/pricing_everything_as_if_they_are_the_next_amzn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/koyjya/pricing_everything_as_if_they_are_the_next_amzn/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 16:55:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the things that amazes me currently in this market is that, it feels like we are trying to justify every new coming hot tech/growth company as if they are the next AMZN in their field. I think one of the delusions people are having lately is that they look at what people projected for AMZN 5-10-15 years ago and compare that to what actually happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it is true that AMZN exceeded any sort of expectation by a huge margin (and did this consistently, year over year) it feels to me that we are taking perhaps one of the most unique success stories ever and then extrapolate that to others, thinking that as if those sort of growth and expectations are in fact more common and easy to achieve than not, regardless of the industry the subject company is operating in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could discuss this for a number of stocks, I wanted to open discussion for TSLA. As we all know, TSLA stock went up almost 8 fold in the last year. Today, it is common occurrence in the market that analysts are justifying these price levels and state why TSLA is just more than a car company. This argument obviously has its own merits, but aren&amp;#39;t we little ahead ourselves and already attribute &lt;em&gt;from today,&lt;/em&gt; all those things that could potentially be achieved and bake it into the price?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we went back in in time, we could probably say AMZN was more than just a book company, but could we really say that they would have almost monopolistic power in most of the areas they operated in? Could we really say back in 2008 that AMZN would emerge the market leader in something like for instance Cloud? Or, did these things happen and then we realized how great AMZN became, &lt;em&gt;after the fact.&lt;/em&gt; It feels like this was much easier to do in hindsight. But what if AMZN is truly that one outlier, anomaly, in the history of stock markets in terms of sustained growth and market power?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isn&amp;#39;t this what we are trying to do with TSLA here? I do think Elon is one of the greatest minds of our time and can achieve far beyond any other has achieved so I am not comparing Bezos or any other with Elon here. But what I am trying to say is that, just thinking TSLA as a company, aren&amp;#39;t we already saying today that they already have monopolistic power in EV cars, autonomous driving, solar-energy trade, underground tunnels, robotaxis, etc. - you name it, as if they are already there and waiting to be switched on? It&amp;#39;s as if we have already attributed everything we could imagine could happen and already announced TSLA as the winner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now this is the theory side of things. &lt;strong&gt;How about financial side of things?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t want to approach this from a car sales point of view, but I will make certain comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what if we applied AMZN&amp;#39;s growth trajectory into TSLA, without focusing too much on car sales, and just see what growth and valuation that would lead us? If TSLA is just more than a car company, what other example could serve best in terms of growth, thinking from an array of products and technological advantage perspective?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I did a quick and dirty DCF calculation. In there, my starting point is the first year when AMZN hit $24 billion in revenue, which is 2009. TSLA achieved it&amp;#39;s $24 billion in 2019, so from there onwards I am applying AMZN&amp;#39;s growth trajectory for the following 10-11 years. Then, growth is gradually reduced in going into the terminal year. What this means is TSLA will be roughly $900 billion revenue generating company by year 20 (2040). From a car sales perspective, I can&amp;#39;t really project how many cars it could sell in 20 years, but lets say it is 10 million cars. (I think GS said 15 million). Toyota in 2019 sold around this number I believe so with all the competition that will happen in this space, I think this is by no means and under-estimation. In 2019, TSLA sold roughly 367,500 cars and for a total revenue of $19.2 billion (excluding regulatory credits). On average this equates to $52k per car. In 20 years, car prices will be higher than what they are today obviously, but there will be competition and economies of scale to bring the price down. This one is hard to assume but let&amp;#39;s say it grows 1.0% - 1.5% per year with long term inflation, again not necessarily higher because of these offsetting factors. If they do indeed sell 10+ million cars, this is roughly $600-650 billion from cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leaves you with another $200-250 billion or so for other things, whatever you want to attribute this for - AI, robotaxies, insurance, and so on. Now this figure is a future value, so from today&amp;#39;s perspective (using a discount rate of 8% used in my DCF below) that&amp;#39;s roughly $60 billion (revenue). This is again a huge number, as it is almost another Facebook, 2x Coca-Cola etc., or half of GM/Toyota type business from revenue generating capability, again, from &lt;em&gt;today&amp;#39;s perspective - none of which has already happened.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again I want to point out that my revenue projections are not driven by bottoms-up car sales, rather, I am using simply AMZN trajectory in terms of growth, then try to attribute the resulting final revenue figure into parts, obviously majority being from car sales, and the rest from whatever you can think of. (Simply because we don&amp;#39;t know what AI/Robos/Insurance/Transportation businesses can generate from revenue/profitability/market share perspective and more importantly what the competition in those areas can be). If you think TSLA can grow even more than AMZN, then I just want to remind you that you won&amp;#39;t easily justify 40-50% revenue growth rates once you&amp;#39;re in the 50+ billion zone, which is the point of the argument. AMZN, still achieved those growth rates when it had 100+ or 200+ billion, which is what we are already assuming here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in the stock price we have baked in, from a revenue perspective, a car business that will sell at least 10+ million cars (this number can obviously be higher but even 10 million will be big market share),  and other businesses that are worth, today, more than most companies you can think of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now this is the growth side of things. How about margins?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know TSLA generated a last twelve months EBITDA margin of 14% as of Q3 2020. While margins from car manufacturing is certainly improving, most of this margin is actually attributed to sales of regulatory credits, which are by definition almost 100% profit. And so in reality, the margins are much lower, maybe around low single digits between 1-5%. Now this is important because even with all this revenue growth (and if you disagree with me and think it will even be higher), you still need to achieve big margins on your business. I mean really really good margins, we are talking about 15-25% each year. Interestingly, AMZN, while growing its top line crazily over the years and becoming a behemoth as it is today, always lacked in terms of their margins. That goes without saying they are a tech company that typically exhibit great returns on capital. So the point is they had to sacrifice their margins to be able to achieve this growth and this is an important point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my DCF, I am extremely generous. I kept TSLA&amp;#39;s EBITDA margins at 15% for the next 3 years, bumped to 17.5%, 20.0%, then to finally 25.0% every 3 years in going forward. Once again these regulatory credits will not be there forever so those margins are extremely optimistic at this point. They might indeed achieve 25% margins in 10 years or so but it won&amp;#39;t be this smooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these two major factors, other items in the DCF are not super important. The discount rate is 8.0%, which I believe is reasonable, NWC and Capex assumptions are in line with what they are today and I don&amp;#39;t think they would necessarily go down (if not go up). I just want to mention that you may completely disagree with some of the assumptions I outlined above. The point however is no matter what sort of DCF you come up with, you will end up either with lower or slight higher value for TSLA, using very, very aggressive assumptions for 10+ years. So the point and question is around the &lt;strong&gt;margin of safety&lt;/strong&gt; here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems I can&amp;#39;t directly post pictures so here is the link for the DCF:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/mSHDcBh&quot;&gt;https://ibb.co/mSHDcBh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might wonder, well your price is even higher than what it is today so why did you write this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again my whole point in the argument was that the margin of error in TSLA&amp;#39;s stock price right now is non-existent, because we&amp;#39;ve already treated it the next AMZN, gave the best margins possible, attributed big bucks on its other stuff. I think my DCF is still in the unreasonable side, but I wanted to point this out that even a s&lt;em&gt;light change in trajectory would mean a totally different path and stock price for TSLA.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the question is, are we ahead of ourselves with TSLA? This could also apply to others as well, this so called growth companies. It is as if we are pricing everything today and think that they have already achieved incredible market share in everything they touched and it&amp;#39;s only a matter of time that these revenue/profits are realized. Are we taking one anomaly and applying this rationale for every other great company under the name of &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s tech&amp;quot;? Elon is great and TSLA will be great. But the business model may not just allow them to be the next AMZN, regardless of technology or improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One final comment I will make is related to autonomous driving and data TSLA is collecting. While it is for certain that this data gives TSLA an incredible power in developing this technology, I see couple of issues with this as it relates to future of this thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies such as Facebook are big not because of their software, but because of the network effects they exhibit. And because of those network effects they become larger and larger and are able to collect more data, which creates an incredibly profitable cycle for them as they can monetize that data right away. Data for TSLA here only matters in developing that technology. Monetization however, is another story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I am not entirely sure with all this AI story is that if it needs to continuously get updated for use, then how do regulators/companies determine the older version was safe to use to begin with. What I understand is that AI is something that needs to get constantly updated based on data, challenge here is that you are carrying people&amp;#39;s lives here (as opposed to targeting ads) so there needs to be an infliction point where the full autonomous driving AI software should be at a point where it is certainly 100% safe to use. Because if it is not, then the technology fails until it reaches to that point. If it does reach out to that point, then how difficult is it going to be for others to get to that point or use similar technology if what you need is to get from point A to B safely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides there is the price factor in as well. Let&amp;#39;s say TSLA is the only one who can do this. If autonomous driving is too expensive, then how much will people pay for it? Say if the car is 50k and you have to pay extra 50k on top of that - would you do this? Would this have a cannibalization effect? Or if it is monthly subscription fees, would you go on to pay this forever? How significant will the cost be in 20 years from now when others presumably also start providing some sort of service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if it is not expensive and only a fraction of the car price, then how are you going to achieve these growth levels with that data and technology to begin with. It is one thing to have a great technology, another to monetize it. They might license it for sure, but then you lose all that power right away. So the question then becomes, will it be a niche product or commodity at the end of the day - either of which will not allow you to have incredible returns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管大流行，特斯拉还是达到了50万辆的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[型号S/X-54,805(生产)-57,039(交付)

型号3/Y-454,932(生产)-442,511(交付)

总数-509,737(生产)-499,550(交付)

来源：
https://ir.tesla.com/press-release/tesla-q4-2020-vehicle-production-deliveries

埃隆·马斯克预测…产量目标为50万辆]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kozaga/tesla_reached_its_target_of_500k_vehicles_despite/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kozaga/tesla_reached_its_target_of_500k_vehicles_despite/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 16:55:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Model S/X - 54,805  (produced) - 57,039 (delivered)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Model 3/Y - 454,932 (produced) - 442,511 (delivered)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total - 509,737 (produced) - 499,550 (delivered)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.tesla.com/press-release/tesla-q4-2020-vehicle-production-deliveries&quot;&gt;https://ir.tesla.com/press-release/tesla-q4-2020-vehicle-production-deliveries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk forecasted the production target of 500k for 2020 in 2014. This was considered impossible even until recently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中产阶层正朝着穷人的方向发展。有没有人快点做点什么https://t.co/HHHzjQI6Nj]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345113252628475905</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1345113252628475905</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 13:45:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The middled class is heading right for the poors. Someone do something quick https://t.co/HHHzjQI6Nj</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>