<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 10:46:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[以男性角色爲視角的言情小說？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個女孩，但我不知道爲什麼我更喜歡閱讀 從一個男人的角度比。
我是做女生的，尤其是在言情方面，我比較感興趣。
那麼有誰知道有什麼好的言情小說，我們可以看到故事中的
通過一個男主角的眼睛？

我只是希望它是一個... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mh99we/romance_novel_from_the_perspective_of_a_male/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mh99we/romance_novel_from_the_perspective_of_a_male/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 21:45:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a girl but idk why I prefer reading from the perspective of a guy more than I do a girl, especially when it comes to romance, it&amp;#39;s more interesting to me. So does anyone know of a good romance novel where we get to see the story through the eyes of a male protagonist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just want it to be a nice, well written romance where the couple has chemistry and their interactions feel enjoyable to read, like Pride and Prejudice for example. I also want the characters to be more realistic and grounded if possible, and not feel like a fantasy, so preferably no super hot billionare businessman male leads Christian Gray style or sexy supermodel female lead, and the story centers around more normal people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當陀思妥耶夫斯基衝擊聖彼得堡文壇時 亞歷克斯-赫里斯託菲談偉大的俄國作家與名聲和不安全感的鬥爭：]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgt1mw/when_dostoevsky_hit_the_st_petersburg_literary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgt1mw/when_dostoevsky_hit_the_st_petersburg_literary/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 21:00:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[重讀《碟中諜》系列]]></title><description><![CDATA[光榮的5月25日就要到了，我正在重讀特里-普拉切特的。
嫺熟的《碟中諜》系列。事實上，我正在聽這個系列的有聲讀物。
主要由Nigel Planar講述。如果你從來沒有讀過或聽過。
這個系列，你還在等什麼呢？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mh30ug/rereading_the_discworld_series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mh30ug/rereading_the_discworld_series/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 19:46:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The glorious 25th of May is approaching, and I&amp;#39;m re-reading Terry Pratchette&amp;#39;s masterful &lt;em&gt;Discworld&lt;/em&gt; series. In fact, I&amp;#39;m listening to the series as audiobooks, primarily narrated by Nigel Planar. If you&amp;#39;ve never read or listened through this series, what in heaven&amp;#39;s name are you waiting for? Certainly, if you credit yourself as any kind of literary mind--no matter how deep or shallow--you&amp;#39;ll find not only a relatable cast of characters to enjoy, but equally a breadth of satire I didn&amp;#39;t fully appreciate as a young man, and now entering middle age, I find to be quite appealing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel I was misled when I first picked up the series. I had been told by multiple sources that a) you don&amp;#39;t need to read them in order--which is true, but also b) that the first few books aren&amp;#39;t very good and not a good introduction to the series. Though I agree that the first three books may not be the strongest--with book three, &lt;em&gt;Equal Rites,&lt;/em&gt; easily being the weakest of the bunch next to &lt;em&gt;Maurice and His Amazing Rats&lt;/em&gt;--reading the series chronologically vs. thematically is definitely the way to go, in my opinion. Taken chronologically, not only is the series more solid and the worldbuilding better appreciated, but you get to invest time and energy in worthy shares between the thematic characters: Death, The Watch, The Witches, The Wizards, etc. You&amp;#39;re also better informed on the running jokes that flow between the books, but don&amp;#39;t necessarily follow only one cast of characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all, the series reminds me of Shakespeare. There are clowns and lovers and princes and tyrants, witches and wizards and tyrants and soldiers all playing out their roles on the platform of the Disc. (Incidentally, if you like Shakespeare, &lt;em&gt;Wyrd Sisters&lt;/em&gt; is a marvelous send-up on Macbeth) Entrances and exits are applauded, tears are shed, laughter abounds, and the end of each book (if not the series as a whole with the untimely death of Sir Terry), you&amp;#39;re left pondering the deeper questions of life. And that, I think, is the true weakness--the end. With Sir Terry&amp;#39;s death only a few short years ago, the series doesn&amp;#39;t have a proper ending--in my opinion. &lt;em&gt;Raising Steam&lt;/em&gt; is an excellent book, but I don&amp;#39;t feel you get a proper curtain on the books as a whole. If, as it is so often interpreted, Prospero&amp;#39;s last speech in &lt;em&gt;The Tempest&lt;/em&gt; is Shakespeare&amp;#39;s farewell to the stage and audience, then the readers of the disc are left asking: what comes next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? Have you read it? What&amp;#39;s your favorite book or your favorite set of characters?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我做了一個20世紀詩人朗讀作品的Spotify播放列表。有29個多小時的詩歌和文字，由那些寫他們的人閱讀，包括詹姆斯-鮑德溫，羅伯特-弗羅斯特，威廉-卡洛斯-威廉姆斯，葉芝，T.S.艾略特，西爾維婭-普拉斯等人的錄音! 你有什麼想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大約在20世紀50年代，Soundmark唱片公司推出了相當多的唱片，其中包括
作家和詩人閱讀他們的作品，包括詹姆斯-鮑德溫、羅伯特-弗羅斯特。
Ezra Pound, Sylvia Plath, William Carlos Williams, E.E. Cummings, T.S. Eliot,
威廉-巴特勒-葉芝，蘭斯頓-休斯等等。錄音...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mh9mby/i_made_a_spotify_playlist_of_20th_century_poets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mh9mby/i_made_a_spotify_playlist_of_20th_century_poets/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 17:56:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around the 1950s, the label Soundmark Records put out quite a few records of authors and poets reading their work, including James Baldwin, Robert Frost, Ezra Pound, Sylvia Plath, William Carlos Williams, E.E. Cummings, T.S. Eliot, William Butler Yeats, Langston Hughes and more. The recordings include a mix of excerpts of novels and poetry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year I discovered some albums of 20th century writers reciting their work and eventually I came across these albums. I recently realized that there were a huge volume of these Soundmark recordings, but there doesn&amp;#39;t seem to be anywhere to find them all in one place, so I searched for as many as I could find and compiled them into this playlist. (I&amp;#39;m not sure how many I may be missing, so if you know of any albums I should add, feel free to comment them here or send me a message and I&amp;#39;ll add it!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been really enjoying listening to these writers reading their own words, and I find it&amp;#39;s interesting to hear their different accents and inflections and how lyrically or flatly they individually speak. It&amp;#39;s like discovering another dimension to the written work, since you&amp;#39;re not only experiencing the words of the author but you&amp;#39;re actually hearing the words spoken in their own voice with all their own unique inflections and articulations. I would be interested to know what all your thoughts are on this, and whether you think it adds or takes away from the experience of these texts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINK: It looks like the link keeps getting auto removed, so you&amp;#39;ll have to search for the title on Spotify.&lt;/strong&gt; You can search for the title below, or look at my post history for the recent post in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/poetry&quot;&gt;r/poetry&lt;/a&gt; which includes the link!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soundmark Records - Authors &amp;amp; Poets, The Complete Collection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在尋找作爲一個有心理健康問題的成年人閱讀的輕鬆/易讀的書籍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好！我是來自印度的30歲女人。我是一個來自印度的30歲女人。我小時候是個貪婪的讀者。
但最終我還是有點失去了閱讀的動力，儘管我很想讀。I
最近尋求心理健康治療，並與我的心理醫生討論了關於
上述問題。他們建議我重啓讀...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mh2x3q/in_search_of_lighteasy_going_books_to_read_as_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mh2x3q/in_search_of_lighteasy_going_books_to_read_as_an/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 14:59:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi guys! I&amp;#39;m a 30 year old woman from India. I was a voracious reader as a child but eventually I kinda lost the motivation to read despite wanting to. I recently sought mental health treatment and talked with my psychiatrist about the above mentioned problem. They advised me to restart the reading habit slowly, with light, easy going books. They assured me that with improvement with mental health I&amp;#39;ll find the lost reader in me again. I&amp;#39;ll be grateful if you guys can help me by suggesting books which are easy on the mind. Thank you in advance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nggĩ wa Thiong'o的《完美九世》是第一本用非洲本土語言寫的作品入圍國際布克獎的作品，我覺得很厲害。如果你讀過這本書，很想聽聽你對這本書的評價!]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mh0yr4/ngũgĩ_wa_thiongos_the_perfect_nine_is_the_first/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mh0yr4/ngũgĩ_wa_thiongos_the_perfect_nine_is_the_first/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 09:52:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們是否過於強調結局？]]></title><description><![CDATA[結局不好也能成爲好書嗎？糟糕的結局也能成爲好書嗎？
結局？以最後20頁來評判一本500頁的書是否不公平，或者說是
遊戲的一部分？結局平淡無奇，是不是意味着前480頁沒有設定好
正確嗎？最重要的是（對我來說），是否需要一個 "聖...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgv72h/do_we_put_too_much_emphasis_on_endings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgv72h/do_we_put_too_much_emphasis_on_endings/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 09:00:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can a book be good even if it has a bad ending? Can it be great with a bad ending? Is it unfair to judge a 500 page book on the last 20 pages, or is that part of the game? Does a meh ending mean that the first 480 pages weren&amp;#39;t set up correctly? Most importantly (to me), does the need for a &amp;quot;holy shit&amp;quot; ending sometimes mean the writer makes poor choices earlier in the book? Just something I&amp;#39;ve been thinking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[納奧米-諾維克，我會跟着你去任何地方！]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在去年的某個時候讀過《連根拔起》，非常喜歡諾維克扭曲的方式。
一個熟悉的童話故事。在某種程度上，它讓我想起了《睡美人》、《美女與野獸》、《睡美人》等。
獸》和《移動城堡》，但也有很多原創和
偉大的寫作，使它看起來不僅僅是這些的總和... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgza4r/naomi_novik_ill_follow_you_anywhere/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgza4r/naomi_novik_ill_follow_you_anywhere/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 08:51:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read &lt;em&gt;Uprooted&lt;/em&gt; sometime last year and really enjoyed the way Novik could twist a familiar fairy tale. In a way, it reminded me of Sleeping Beauty, Beauty and the Beast, and Howl&amp;#39;s Moving Castle, but there was plenty of originality and great writing to make it seem more than just the sum of these parts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two days ago, I started &lt;em&gt;Spinning Silver&lt;/em&gt;, and though I was planning to make it last for the whole week...I just &lt;em&gt;couldn&amp;#39;t!&lt;/em&gt; I stayed up until 1 AM (a big deal for me, since I get up at 6) to finish it, and then had to look up fanfiction afterwards. Ugh, it was just. so. good. The characters were amazing, the story was tense and creative, the writing phenomenal, and the resolution was...*chef&amp;#39;s kiss*. It&amp;#39;s been awhile since I&amp;#39;ve been so invested in a story that I just have to know, right away, how it ends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone else a fan? Has anyone read the Temeraire series? Normally I don&amp;#39;t order books online (I live in Taiwan and shipping is &lt;em&gt;pricey&lt;/em&gt;), but I&amp;#39;m enough of a fan now that if anyone tells me it&amp;#39;s worth it, I&amp;#39;ll believe you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For anyone who isn&amp;#39;t a fan but likes twists on traditional fairy tales, I can&amp;#39;t recommend &lt;em&gt;Spinning Silver&lt;/em&gt; enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天輪到你，明天就輪到我了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Reddit上有一個著名的故事，關於一個人的車在邊上拋錨了
的路上，有一家人停車幫忙。那是一個炎熱的日子，而
這位先生很少講英語（如果我沒記錯，他是墨西哥人）。

該男子幫助這個赤貧的人，通過分享他們的食物來喂他。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgqwms/today_its_your_turn_tomorrow_it_will_be_mine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgqwms/today_its_your_turn_tomorrow_it_will_be_mine/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 06:57:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a famous story on Reddit about a guy who&amp;#39;s car breaks down on the side of the road, and a family pulls over to help.  It was a hot day, and the gentleman spoke very little English (if I remember correctly, he was Mexican).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The man helps this destitute individual, fed him by sharing their lunch and refused money at the end, only saying, &amp;quot;Today you, tomorrow me.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m reading &lt;em&gt;Blindness&lt;/em&gt; by José Saramango, ©1995, and I&amp;#39;m three pages in when I come across this, &amp;quot;I have no words to thank you, and the other replied, Now then, don&amp;#39;t give it another thought, today it&amp;#39;s your turn, tomorrow it will be mine, we never know what might lie in store for us...&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just thought I&amp;#39;d share, it&amp;#39;s always fun when you have books that collide in some way with things you never expected them to.  Can&amp;#39;t wait to keep digging into this book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛讀了菲利普-K-迪克的《安卓人夢見電羊嗎》。很棒的書，但我對結局有點迷茫。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這本書在三個層面上是成功的。首先，它是一本激動人心的警察與逃犯的故事。
驚悚片。其次，這是一個有趣的荒誕世界，地球在衰落，人們在。
核戰爭後的絕望。第三，它具有哲學或心理學上的。
我被告知菲利普-迪克有的心術元素。我讀了...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgsmsf/just_read_do_androids_dream_of_electric_sheep_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgsmsf/just_read_do_androids_dream_of_electric_sheep_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 03:42:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is success on three levels. First, it&amp;#39;s an exciting cops-and-fugitives thriller. Second, it&amp;#39;s an interesting dystopia of earth in decline and people in despair after nuclear war. Third, it has the philosophical or psychological mindfuck elements that I was told Philip K Dick had. I read the whole thing in two days because it was so engaging, and it was one of the sadder books I have read, though not as sad as Earth Abides was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously empathy, and the lack thereof was a pretty major theme of the book. The androids are distinguished from humans by their lack of genuine empathy (but just barely), yet the bounty hunters who go after them seem even less empathic sometimes. There is an entire religion of empathy, which is what some of my questions are about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second theme I noticed is how much of a difference there is between &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;not real&amp;quot;. The humans and androids are barely distinguishable from one another, and sometimes the androids are actually easier to sympathize with rather than the humans. The religion of mercerism is proven &amp;quot;fake&amp;quot; yet it still gives supernatural visions to people (mere hallucinations don&amp;#39;t give tactical positions, telling you who is coming up behind you). At the end, Iran (the woman not the country) decides that the fake elctronic frog is important to Deckard even if it&amp;#39;s not a &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; frog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a little confused as what to make of Mercerism by the end of the book. On one hand, it&amp;#39;s briefly compared to Hitler when Buster Friendly is publically debunking it, probably because of how androids can&amp;#39;t be join in the shared feelings of empathy that the religion is based on. On the other hand, it also seems to embody just how important empathy is to human life. So what am I to make of mercerism - is it kindly empathy or psuedo-Nazism? I also do not understand why Mercer is telling Deckard that it is wrong to kill the androids yet he must do it anyways. Is Mercer pro or anti-android?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m also not sure what to make of the androids themselves. Luba Luft was probably the most &amp;quot;human&amp;quot; of the androids, maybe moreso than the human who shot her. On the other hand, the androids who John Isidore (a pretty sad character) was trying to help were pretty morally repulsive by repaying his attempts to help by torturing to death a spider that he tried to rescue. I had mixed feelings about them - they seemed to be in genuine suffering over being hunted and their generally crappy lot in life, yet they demonstrated several times just how selfish and uncaring androids are, living up to the stereotypes of androids all too well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there a &amp;quot;correct&amp;quot; view towards Mercerism and the androids? If I understood those two elements a little better I think the whole story would fall into place for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book I got also had Man in the High Castle, Stigmata of Palmer Eldritch, and Ubik. I might read Ubik next. Or a Dunsany novel. Or some medieval poetry. I change my mind a lot about whatever I read next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I forgot to say this earlier. The theme of empathy also reminded me of how empathy has been measurably declining in society for some time now. There is some research about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/radio/sunday/the-sunday-edition-for-june-9-2019-1.5165327/empathy-makes-us-human-but-research-suggests-it-may-be-on-the-decline-1.5166354&quot;&gt;decline&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wordonthestreets.net/Articles/549246/The_decline_of.aspx&quot;&gt;of&lt;/a&gt; empathy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/research/action/speaking-of-psychology/empathy-narcissism&quot;&gt;linked&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;#39;s a little bit of dystopian non-fiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mistborn. 我不明白]]></title><description><![CDATA[每一個地球和火星上的書友都給予這本書很高的評價，但我開始。
每次文都會提醒自己，讓別人接近你的時候，都會打一針。
只會導致背叛。從字面上看，第四章背靠背的段落重複
有了這句話，文筆也就好不到哪裏去了。I…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgubwu/mistborn_i_dont_get_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgubwu/mistborn_i_dont_get_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 03:42:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every booktuber on earth and Mars gives this book high praise but i started to take a shot everytime Vin reminded herself that letting people get close to you will only lead to betrayal. Literally chapter 4 back to back paragraphs repeat with that statement and the writing doesn&amp;#39;t get much better. I will never understand why authors put the &amp;quot;rolled his eyes&amp;quot; line, it&amp;#39;s clichéd. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll give credit where credit is do; the magic system is cool and unique and adds layers of world building I really enjoyed. The plot is simple and straight forward which I also like as certain books (looking at you Dune) get pretty difficult to keep track of who is who and what is what. But characters here just didn&amp;#39;t work for me. Vin is the overly done special peasant girl who is good despite living in the underworld. Maybe I&amp;#39;m wrong in wanting her to be like Arya stark who gets darker as she tries to survive but that&amp;#39;s basically Vin&amp;#39;s upbringing. Anyway I needed to get this off my chest and curious to hear what you have to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛看完丹-西蒙斯的《海伯利安》，我不知道該怎麼想。]]></title><description><![CDATA[神父的故事很吸引人，父親的故事很耐人尋味，甚至是
領事的故事很好。私家偵探的故事還不錯，而那個...
詩人的故事，我認爲是有點跛腳。所以基本上，這本書的一半是
驚人的另一半，我翻了我的眼睛在15個性愛場景... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mglzw6/just_finished_hyperion_by_dan_simmons_and_i_dont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mglzw6/just_finished_hyperion_by_dan_simmons_and_i_dont/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 02:53:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The priest’s story was captivating, the fathers story was intriguing, and even the Consul’s story was good. The private investigator’s story was okay and the poets story I thought was kinda lame. So essentially, half of the book was amazing and the other half I rolled my eyes at the 15 sex scenes throughout. I mean, I don’t mind sex in books but it was a little much and not very well written in my opinion. But the ENDING made me mad. Holding hands and singing the freaking Wizard of Oz... are you kidding me dude. I don’t know, it felt so cheesy to me and I felt like I wasted my time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after I dealt with my emotions on the ending of this book, I look up reviews for the book and literally everyone is loving it. I seemed to be the only one who didn’t think it was the bee’s knees. It wasn’t the worst book I’ve ever read but it certainly wasn’t a 10/10. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How did you guys feel about Hyperion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有哪些書能讓你記憶深刻？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我並不是說他們要有一個有爭議的話題（強姦、亂倫、身體折磨）。
等），但只是好的屁股閱讀與偉大的故事，讓你想知道的事情。
或讓你提心吊膽。
我讀過的一本書就是這樣的（不同的、古怪的），是《房子》。
馬克-Z-丹尼爾夫斯基的《葉子》。你能...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mghmqo/what_are_some_books_that_will_stick_with_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mghmqo/what_are_some_books_that_will_stick_with_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 23:57:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do not mean them to have a controversial topic (Rape, Incest, body torture etc) but just good ass reads with great story that makes you wonder about things or keep you on your toes.&lt;br/&gt;
One book I read that was like this (as in different and quirky) was house of Leaves by  Mark Z. Danielewski. Can you recommend some others like this? Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不知道該讀什麼]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好！ 我剛剛讀了《穿條紋睡衣的男孩》 我剛剛讀了《穿條紋睡衣的男孩》，我很喜歡這本書。
我想讀一些類似於故事的講述方式和曲折的故事。
結束。我很想知道是否有類似故事的系列書籍，因爲...
我總是很難過，當沒有另一本書... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mggbmj/i_dont_know_what_to_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mggbmj/i_dont_know_what_to_read/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 18:37:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! So I’ve just read “The boy in the striped pyjamas” and I really liked it. I want to read something that’s similar to how the story is told and the twisted end. I would love if there was any series of books with a similar story, because I always get sad when there isn’t another book to continue the story. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[女性如何發明了讀書會，徹底改變了閱讀和自己的生活。在奧普拉和里斯-威瑟斯彭之前的150多年裏，女性開始集體閱讀。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgftoj/how_women_invented_book_clubs_revolutionizing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgftoj/how_women_invented_book_clubs_revolutionizing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 15:53:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每個人都應該讀史蒂文-金的《站臺》]]></title><description><![CDATA[背景--當我還是個孩子的時候，我們有一個未完成的地下室，總是有一個。
一堆老舊的氣味盒子藏在角落裏。我們以前經常在下面玩
一直在那裏，所以自然而然地，我最終看完了其中的大部分。在一個
是這本巨大的千頁書與舊封面的... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgbufe/everyone_should_read_the_stand_by_steven_king/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mgbufe/everyone_should_read_the_stand_by_steven_king/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 11:49:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context -&lt;/strong&gt; When I was a child, we had an unfinished basement that always had a bunch of old smelling boxes tucked away in the corner. We used to play down there all the time so naturally I ended up looking through most of them. In one was this huge thousand page book with the old cover for the complete and uncut editon (The coolest cover btw). Around this time I had fallen in love with reading and wanted to get my hands on everything. When my I asked my dad if I could read it all he said, &amp;quot;No, its way to scary.&amp;quot; For years I always wondered what was so spooky about it. Eveyone I asked said the same thing and even when I got older I was still never allowed to read it. That is untill I got really bored and decided to read it stuck in my appartment during quarintine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It really is that spooky -&lt;/strong&gt; Books have never scared me, but this one did. Usualy when you think of being scared you think of a jump scare of something like that, this was completely different. It is more like a long spiraling decent of a jump scare. When I was finished reading it I was unsettled for like 2 days. I have never been left with that sort of feeling durring and especially after finishing a book. What makes it worse is the cotent of the book and what is going on today. I could not have picked a better book to read durring this time and I am super glad I did. So for anyone who likes 1000 page books that are deeply disturbing and biblical and have all this really cool stuff, this one is for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[孩子們還在讀關於我童年英雄的書! Yay!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的文學英雄在我的少年時代一直喜歡咖啡和千層餅，討厭
星期一（每隻好貓都應該這樣，對吧......），並噴出了一個永恆的。
諷刺之流完全符合我的幽默感。現在，我正在除草和
評估加菲貓的書爲我的YY收藏， 並很高興... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfssje/kids_are_still_reading_books_about_my_childhood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfssje/kids_are_still_reading_books_about_my_childhood/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 07:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My literary hero throughout my teen years LOVED coffee and lasagna, HATED Mondays (as every good cat should, right...), and spurted out an everlasting stream of sarcasm perfectly aligned with my sense of humor. Now I&amp;#39;m weeding and evaluating Garfield books for my YA collection, and am thrilled to see that kids (and adults) are still reading them, all these years later. Who were your literary heroes as a teen?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[蔚藍海里的房子》是一本精彩而溫暖的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我讀這本書之前，我聽到很多人對這本書的好評
以及它是多麼的神奇，所以我自然決定試一試。我的同事
紅學家們，我還沒有準備好這本小說給我帶來的感受。它
只是散發着溫暖、魅力和奇思妙想。

故事方面，這是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfzg0h/the_house_in_the_cerulean_sea_is_a_wonderful_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfzg0h/the_house_in_the_cerulean_sea_is_a_wonderful_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior to my reading of the book, I had heard many folks raving about this book and how fantastic it was, so naturally I decided to give it a try. My fellow Redditors, I was not prepared for the feelings this novel engendered in me. It just radiated warmth, charm and whimsy.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Story-wise this is defintely a unique one. It follows a man who has a job that entails writing reports on orphanages that house magical children. One day he is given a task of going off to an orphanage where the &amp;quot;dangerous&amp;quot; magical children stay...
The book sparks discussions about whether we should condemn groups of people based on their exterior or look deeper and if objectivity is really the best way of going about matters that have to do with people&amp;#39;s livelihood. It shows the negligence of bureaucratic control  and the corrupt nature of people fearing what they cannot understand. There are parallels that could be made between some situations in this book and our world which adds to just how much of a good layered story this book is. The writing is brilliant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The characters are all fantastic (well not all but the main characters). Linus Baker you poor bastard, how many times did you have to suffer an almost heart attack at the sight of Anti-Ch-, sorry, &lt;em&gt;Lucy&lt;/em&gt;? But in all seriousness I loved reading from his pov. His self-deprecating disposition and his desire to flee certain situations but finding himself unable to made me cackle alot. This book is flipping funny yall! Its crazy the amount of times I burst out laughing! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talia is my favourite character out of all the kids. I love every single one of them though. They are all unique, loveable, charming and absolutely brave. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall this is a story I will be revisting in the future and one that is sure to stay with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我真的很喜歡《哈爾的移動城堡》，也很喜歡這樣的東西。]]></title><description><![CDATA[幾乎和它一模一樣。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mfx3sa/i_just_really_loved_howls_moving_castle_and_would/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mfx3sa/i_just_really_loved_howls_moving_castle_and_would/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 02:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost exactly like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[前幾天重讀了《了不起的蓋茨比》，過去一年完全改變了我的閱讀方式。]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以和地球上的其他人一樣，我在學校裏學習了《了不起的蓋茨比》。I
很喜歡，後來又讀了幾遍。我一直有一個很
欣賞菲茨傑拉德在故事中傳達民族情緒的技巧，但...。
我最近的重讀是一種全新的體驗。

之間的相似之處...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mg1raw/reread_the_great_gatsby_the_other_day_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mg1raw/reread_the_great_gatsby_the_other_day_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 02:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So like everyone else on the planet I studied the Great Gatsby at school. I loved it, and have read it a few times since. I’ve always had a great appreciation for Fitzgerald’s skill at conveying a national mood in a story, but my recent re-reading was a totally new experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The parallels between the 1920s and 2020s are a cliche at this point, and it’s only 2021, but I do think this last year gives a new kind of reading to the book where you feel the atmosphere so readily it’s almost dizzying. I did some academic reading recently about the cultural amnesia of the 1918 influenza pandemic, because (along with WW1 of course) it was this staggering global trauma, but it undoubtedly contributed to the glorious, dangerous hedonism explored in Gatsby. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Between the traumatised hedonism and rampant socio-economic inequality that, imo, form the axes of the Great Gatsby, I honestly think the collective experience of the last year(s) lends a whole new dimension to reading this classic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電子書銷量在2020年同比增長16%，達到了迄今爲止的最大總量，創下了圖書銷售的總體記錄--來自尼爾森圖書研究公司的《圖書與消費者調查》。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfng3w/ebook_sales_rose_16_year_on_year_in_2020_to_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfng3w/ebook_sales_rose_16_year_on_year_in_2020_to_their/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 21:54:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有人覺得馬修-麥康納的《綠光》有很多紅旗嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜歡他在電影中的表現，所以我下載了他的有聲讀物版本。
回憶錄/宣稱的自助書《綠燈》。它的評分爲4.26分。
近62,000個評分。我很興奮。

他的解說很有魅力，聽起來很有趣，然而當他開始。
隨便說說國內的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfoo2g/anyone_else_feel_mathew_mcconaugheys_greenlight/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfoo2g/anyone_else_feel_mathew_mcconaugheys_greenlight/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 17:35:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I like him as an actor in films, so I downloaded the audiobook version of his memoir/proclaimed self help book, Greenlights. It has a 4.26 rating out of nearly 62,000 ratings. I was excited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His narration was charming and fun to listen to, however when he started casually mentioning the domestic violence that goes on between his parents (both ways), I thought ok, he&amp;#39;s probably going to be exploring his childhood trauma or something, but no, he says &amp;quot;some may call this xxx but we called it love.&amp;quot; I write xxx because I can&amp;#39;t recall the specific word he used, similar vein to DV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was his parents throwing and breaking plates at other, shouting and swearing. Fighting to the point of talking about divorce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then pretty early in the book, he says he stole someone else&amp;#39;s poem for a writing contest(or a piece of homework that won something), he said his mum&amp;#39;s idea was if you don&amp;#39;t get caught it&amp;#39;s not stealing. He was laughing while narrating and it sounded like a fond memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there was his first meeting with his wife, can&amp;#39;t recall the details but I remember cringing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;#39;t really find any reviews talking about these things, some negative ones criticize him being a narcissist, but most find him and his behaviour charming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I also just remembered how he had to beat the shit out of someone who badmouthed his dad for his dad to finally recognise him(Mathew) as a &amp;#39;good son&amp;#39; &amp;#39;real man&amp;#39;....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[喬治-RR-馬丁簽下5年8位數的合約，爭取更多的HBO項目。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfp0wl/george_rr_martin_signs_fiveyear_eightfigure_deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfp0wl/george_rr_martin_signs_fiveyear_eightfigure_deal/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 17:35:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在維多利亞時代的文學作品中，對話是經過潤色的，還是他們實際的說話方式？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直有很多的麻煩，因爲無論我怎麼努力，我
無法想象人物說話的樣子......那樣。拿海倫的這句話來說
簡愛》中的伯恩斯

> 生命對我來說太短暫了，不能把時間花在培養敵意或登記上。
> 錯誤。我們是，也必須是，一體的，... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfssi5/in_victorian_literature_was_the_dialogue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfssi5/in_victorian_literature_was_the_dialogue/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 17:35:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been having a lot of trouble with this because no matter how hard I try, I can&amp;#39;t picture the characters talking like...&lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt;. Take this quote from Helen Burns in Jane Eyre:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life appears to me too short to be spent in nursing animosity or registering wrongs. We are, and must be, one and all, burdened by faults in this world; but the time will soon come when, I trust, we shall put them off in putting off our corruptible bodies...I hold another creed, which no one ever taught me, and which I seldom mention, but in which I delight, and to which I cling; for it extends hope to all; it makes Eternity a rest—a mighty home, not a terror and an abyss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helen Burns is fourteen. FOURTEEN. Try to picture a 14 year old saying that. It just doesn&amp;#39;t work. But take Tom Sawyer. It was published just about 29 years later, but with the exception of a bit of outdated slang, the characters could easily be from the present. And I read somewhere that Tom Sayer was one of the first popular books to use &amp;quot;vernacular speech&amp;quot;. Does that mean that Jane Eyre used speech that was formalized in writing? Or did everyone speak formally? Help me out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幫幫一個可愛的老太太吧？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有一個70多歲的朋友，她因爲...
covid相關的關注。在過去的一年裏，她一直在努力研究zoom
(由於經濟原因無法退休)，我真的希望她能抓緊時間休息!

有一件事讓她度過了這一切，那就是戴安娜... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mfig7m/help_for_a_lovely_old_ladyoutlander_fan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mfig7m/help_for_a_lovely_old_ladyoutlander_fan/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 12:21:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a dear friend in her 70s who is pretty holed up in her apartment due to covid related concerns. She&amp;#39;s been working hard on zoom for the past year (unable to retire due to finances) and I really wish she could catch a break!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that&amp;#39;s been getting her through all this is Diana Gabaldon&amp;#39;s Outlander series on Audiobook, as expertly narrated by Davina Porter, but she&amp;#39;s listened to it twice now and is looking for something new !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She says the Outlander series is a good mix of historical tidbits and intrigue, but also something you can semi tune out of here and there (not too dense or requiring a huge amount of focus). Honestly, to hear her tell it, it&amp;#39;s been one of the very few things that has brought her real comfort during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think her admiration for Davina Porter is on the same level of her appreciation for the author&amp;#39;s writing! She even said she listened to some biography of Elizabeth I that Porter narrated, just to give you an idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She&amp;#39;s also indicated a (variable) fondness for Isabel Allende; she liked House of Spirits and Island Beneath The Sea, but expressed an indifference towards some of her other works (which I wish I could remember, gah. I think she said A Long Petal Of The Sea didn&amp;#39;t really grab her ?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m basically looking for audiobook recommendations of similar works (or works read by Davina Porter), hopefully available thru libby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much all ;_;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你讀過或正在讀哪些與你的小衆興趣或愛好相關的書籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我注意到這個子只真正圍繞着小說，可能是因爲它是
廣爲流傳，與大家息息相關。

不過我自己主要是看非虛構類的小說，我覺得你可以算是看到了裏面的內容。
一個人的更深層次的興趣，通過看他們讀什麼類型的非小說。

例如，我...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mf8k41/what_books_have_you_read_or_are_reading_that_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mf8k41/what_books_have_you_read_or_are_reading_that_are/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 03:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I noticed this sub only really revolves around fiction, probably because it&amp;#39;s widely accessible and relevant for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I myself mostly read non-fiction though and I think you can kind of see inside someone&amp;#39;s deeper interests by seeing what type of non-fiction they read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, I&amp;#39;m becoming more interested in the intersection of science, technology, and politics within history, and two books I&amp;#39;ve been reading are &amp;quot;Cybernetic Revolutionaries&amp;quot; about the socialist Allende government in Chile and their use of very low tech computing to solve economic problems through planning, as well as using the emerging systems engineering philosophy of &amp;quot;cybernetics.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other book I&amp;#39;m reading is &amp;quot;Red Revolution, Green Revolution&amp;quot; about the early efforts in communist China to revolutionize and modernize the agriculture of the nation through a mixture of traditional knowledge and modern scientific techniques and technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我讀過《麥田守望者》，我不明白爲什麼它這麼受歡迎。]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我看完《麥田守望者》後，我還是不明白... ...
爲什麼今天很多人都把它奉爲名作，因爲我會把它描述爲：。
它不過是一些娘娘腔在紐約附近打打鬧鬧。如果有人能給
我的解釋，這將是很好的。

還有，我對...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfazrp/i_read_catcher_in_the_rye_and_i_dont_get_why_its/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mfazrp/i_read_catcher_in_the_rye_and_i_dont_get_why_its/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 23:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time I had finished Catcher in the Rye, I still didn&amp;#39;t really understand why it&amp;#39;s held as a masterpiece to a lot of people today, since I would describe it as nothing more than some twat faffing around Newyork. If anyone could give me an explanation, that would be nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, my thoughts on the book are that it was alright. Nothing really special, didn&amp;#39;t really have anything to say, I&amp;#39;m sure it was more controversial when it first came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also also, I&amp;#39;m an aussie, so it might just be an american thing I don&amp;#39;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這本價值2.2萬美元的書刊登了西斯廷教堂藝術的真人大小照片。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mf81t8/this_22000_book_features_lifesize_photos_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mf81t8/this_22000_book_features_lifesize_photos_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 22:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[與The Library at Mount Char相似]]></title><description><![CDATA[過去有幾篇文章點名推薦的是
和這本書相似，但我更想看! 這真是一本奇怪的怪書，我...
我喜歡它，我想要更多的這種脈絡。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mf6tzm/similar_to_the_library_at_mount_char/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mf6tzm/similar_to_the_library_at_mount_char/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 21:42:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a few posts in the past that have named recommendations that are similar to this book but I want even more!  It&amp;#39;s such a weird strange book and I love it and I want more in this vein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[發現斯蒂芬-金的時間很晚（30多歲），他很快就成爲我最喜歡的作家。尤其是他對死亡的感情處理得很好，給我留下了深刻的印象。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道，在美國和許多其他西方國家，金是一個極其。
人紅是非多，書到用時方恨少。
這是我的印象）。) 我在印度長大，英語並不是我的母語。
語言，我甚至沒有聽說過他，直到我20多歲。我有...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mex78g/discovering_stephen_king_late_in_life_30s_and_he/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mex78g/discovering_stephen_king_late_in_life_30s_and_he/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 20:27:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that in the US and many other western countries King is an extremely popular author and people read his books when they are teenagers (at least that&amp;#39;s my impression). I grew up in India, and English was not my first language, and I didn&amp;#39;t even hear about him until my late 20&amp;#39;s. I have always been a horror lover but in many forums, I have always heard that King&amp;#39;s books are for teenagers and basically not great. So I put off reading his books. I did then picked up one of his books, called Duma Key, and that did not suit my style at all. So I thought he is not my author then. But then, great horror is hard to come by, and I saw a suggestion of Pet Semetary here. So I gave him a second chance with that book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And wow, Pet Semetary has become one of my most favorite books of all time. More than the ghost part, I am bowled over by how well he deals with the feelings surrounding death. &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;The grief of the parents and the constant premonition of &amp;#39;sometimes dead IS better&amp;#39; was so well done! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I read Salem&amp;#39;s Lot and now reading  IT. I have watched the movie, but the book is so much more. &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;The part where Bill is struggling with his brothers&amp;#39; death and describes the cold space between his parents just hits hard. A 10-year-old grieving for his 6-year-old dead brother becomes such an intimate scene for the reader! &lt;/span&gt; He is my favorite horror author now. He may not have the best prose or a beautiful flowery writing style, but his direct and intimate writing style works for horror very well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just want to say to this group that thank you for suggesting Pet Semetary. If there are any older readers hesitating to start reading King, my advice is that there&amp;#39;s a lot to love in his books even if you are grown up now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你如何處理不記得多年前看過的書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[想到多年前讀過的一些書，有些也許更讓我難過
最近，我就是記不起任何實質性的東西。我經常試圖記錄
我喜歡的段落，情節的轉折，人物，但這些都會被遺忘。
短時間內。

最近我看了幾...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mf3b9n/how_do_you_deal_with_not_remembering_books_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mf3b9n/how_do_you_deal_with_not_remembering_books_you/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 20:27:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It saddens me to think that there are books I read years ago, some maybe more recently, where I just cannot remember anything substantial. I often try to note down passages I like, turns in the plot, characters, but these get forgotten within a short space of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I looked over a few novels that I read about five years ago and could not remember much about the plot other than a few key features. All the intricacy that drew me to the novel? Vague notions recalled, but very little details have stayed in my head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d like to reread some of these books to recover what I lost, but I also think that life is short and there is so much out there to enjoy, why read things more than once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you all manage with this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你如何看待圖書外借？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜歡鼓勵閱讀，如果我認爲有人會喜歡一本書，我會。
常常從二手書店給他們買。但我覺得我的
讀書人的名聲，引起了一些對我好奇的朋友對
進入閱讀，把我看成某種圖書館，就像... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/memwmo/how_do_you_feel_about_lending_books_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/memwmo/how_do_you_feel_about_lending_books_out/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 19:44:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love encouraging reading, and if i think that somebody would enjoy a book i’ll often buy it for them from a second hand book store. But I feel like my reputation as an avid reader has caused some of my friends who are curious about getting into reading to see me as some sort of library, and like a library they don’t return the books for years, or sometimes ever. I often want to re-read books or value them for their edition, or because i’ve had a growing experience with them. Reading requires self discipline that a lot of people don’t maintain, so I am hesitant to lend books out now unless I have a reason to believe the person will return it in due time. Am I the asshole? How do you all feel about this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我創建了r/booksidisliked !]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我不知道我是否可以在這裏宣傳自己，但我有。
創建了一個社區，在這裏我們可以自由地談論我們不喜歡的書。
以及爲什麼我們不會向人們建議他們。你可以做你自己，而我
不會允許任何仇恨的評論或類似的東西。大家...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mf0rlt/ive_created_rbooksidisliked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mf0rlt/ive_created_rbooksidisliked/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 16:08:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello all, I’m not sure if I’m allowed to promote myself on here but I have created a community where we can all freely speak about books that we dislike and why we wouldn’t suggest them to people. You are allowed to be yourself and I will not allow any hate comments or anything like that. Everyone has their own opinions! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve never been a moderator before, and would love if some people would like to help me grow our community and grow something beautiful! If anyone would be In interested in being a moderator too I’d love a message or email! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if this is something you all are interested in! &lt;a href=&quot;/r/booksidisliked&quot;&gt;r/booksidisliked&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: added in community link&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只有我一個人在看書的時候打開書只是一點點，所以平裝書的背面不會有那些線條在裏面？]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我不看書的時候，書不在我的書櫃裏，我就把它放在一個保護性的
書套，所以它不會彎角。當我看完一本書後，它
看起來不像是被讀過的。當有人要求借書時，我就會給他們。
清楚地說明我希望那個人如何照顧我的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mewza3/am_i_the_only_one_who_opens_a_book_just_a_little/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mewza3/am_i_the_only_one_who_opens_a_book_just_a_little/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 11:48:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I don&amp;#39;t read the book and it&amp;#39;s not in my bookcase I put it in a protecting book sleeve so it doesn&amp;#39;t bend the corners. When I am done reading a book it doesn&amp;#39;t look like it&amp;#39;s been read. When someone asks to lend a book I give them clear instructions on how I want that person to take care of my book. Not everyone is allowed to lend a book from me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friends and parents think I am crazy for being so overly protective about my books. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a couple of second hand books and it is okay for those to bend bc they&amp;#39;re already in that state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I accedently make a bend in the back of a new book it can ruin my mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can&amp;#39;t tell me I am the only one right? Tell me what you think about it and how you treat your books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我竟然等了這麼久纔讀到《簡愛》!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我今年45歲，從我記事起就開始熱衷於讀書。我把
關閉閱讀這本書，因爲我認爲這是一個浪漫，這是我最不
喜歡的類型。說實話，這本書第一頁就把我吸引住了! 它是如此
美麗的，寫得很好。我在不到48小時內就把它喫完了。I…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/menojj/i_cant_believe_i_waited_so_long_to_read_jane_eyre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/menojj/i_cant_believe_i_waited_so_long_to_read_jane_eyre/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 05:59:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m 45 years old and have been reading avidly as long as I can remember. I put off reading this book because I thought it was a romance, which is my least preferred genre. Honestly, this book had me hooked by the first page! It is so beautiful and well written. I devoured it in less than 48 hours. I can&amp;#39;t believe I waited so long to read it! It does have a love/romance thread but what human life doesn&amp;#39;t? It is about so much more than romance though, and I absolutely fell in love with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這裏有沒有人從kindle換回紙質書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我每週在兩臺電腦前坐40個小時，我的另一個主要愛好是----。
遊戲，這是另一個屏幕多個小時一個星期。

我一直在使用只有一個kindle paperwhite在大流行期間，我只是不喜歡。
它。這感覺就像我在讀一篇Reddit文章，而不是沉浸在一個。
故事...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mel07s/has_anyone_here_switched_back_from_kindle_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mel07s/has_anyone_here_switched_back_from_kindle_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 05:04:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I sit in front of two computers 40 hours a week and my other main hobby is gaming which is another screen multiple hours a week.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using only a kindle paperwhite during pandemic and I just don’t like it. It feels like I’m reading a Reddit article instead of immersing myself in a story written down.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need a break from screens during the week and reading paper books is just more cozy to me.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just got my first vaccine dose so I’m excited to be able to head to the library again very soon 😬&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凌晨3點會讓你哭的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如書名所示，我正在尋找能讓我嚎啕大哭的書。
凌晨三點眼睛都要瞪出來了，因爲我放不下它。有這種效果的書
我。

給阿爾傑農的花

一個小生命

跑風箏的人

所有明亮的地方

最後他們都死了

阿基里斯之歌

亞里士多德...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mepo5a/books_that_will_make_you_cry_at_3_am/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mepo5a/books_that_will_make_you_cry_at_3_am/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 04:37:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exactly as the title suggests, I&amp;#39;m looking for books that will make me bawl my eyes out at 3 AM because I couldn&amp;#39;t put it down. Books that had this effect on me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flowers for Algernon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little life&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The kite runner&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the bright places&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They both die at the end&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The song of Achilles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aristotle and Dante discover the secrets of the universe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were liars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the light we cannot see&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any genre is fine, but I&amp;#39;m leaning more towards the heartwrenching romance type beat lmao Thanks guys!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛看完《準備好的玩家1》，比電影還喜歡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[現在，我有這個空白，我需要用一本未來主義的太空冒險書來填補。任何
建議？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/meeuas/just_finished_ready_player_one_and_i_liked_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/meeuas/just_finished_ready_player_one_and_i_liked_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 02:15:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now I have this void I need to fill with a futuristic space adventure book. Any suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scholastic撤掉了《內褲隊長》作者的人氣童書。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mei7sy/scholastic_pulls_popular_childrens_book_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mei7sy/scholastic_pulls_popular_childrens_book_from/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 19:29:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[可以在這裏發一些避免看的書嗎？我真的不喜歡的書？]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/med7ht/is_it_okay_to_post_books_to_avoid_here_ones_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/med7ht/is_it_okay_to_post_books_to_avoid_here_ones_i/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 15:49:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一個理論。喬治-R-R-馬丁並不打算完成他的《冰與火之歌》系列作品]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年來，人們一直在質疑他是否會完成。
系列，但似乎沒有人思考他甚至不打算
來完成它。下本書似乎沒有什麼進展。
同時，他還忙着寫其他相關的作品（如《世界的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/me717b/a_theory_george_rr_martin_doesnt_intend_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/me717b/a_theory_george_rr_martin_doesnt_intend_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 14:26:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been questions for years about whether or not he will finish the series, but no one seems to ponder the possibility that he doesn&amp;#39;t even intend to finish it. There seems to be little forward movement with the next book. Meanwhile, he&amp;#39;s been busy writing other, related works (e.g. World of Ice &amp;amp; Fire, Dunk and Egg, and Fire &amp;amp; Blood [which is just the first of two volumes from what I understand]) and developing TV shows. To me, it seems that Martin has simply lost interest in competing the series. I think there is a possibility that he doesn&amp;#39;t intend to finish the last two books, but will not say so for two reasons: 1) his publisher would throw a fit, and possibly take legal action if they paid him anything in advance, and 2) the fandom would chase him down with pitchforks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think this is possible? Do you think I&amp;#39;m crazy? Let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我4月份就要當阿姨了，我剛買了26本兒童讀物，練習大聲朗讀。我是一個熱衷於閱讀的人，但我很擔心語氣和流利度。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我(30)只是超級興奮，但我擔心讀書時的語氣。儘管
作爲一個熱衷於閱讀的人，我有點擔心我會聽起來很無聊，當我讀出
我的句子不是很流利，因爲我有時會把單詞讀出來。
秩序。我真的很喜歡孩子。所以我要練習大聲朗讀....。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/me72dm/im_gonna_become_an_aunt_in_april_and_i_just/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/me72dm/im_gonna_become_an_aunt_in_april_and_i_just/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 11:48:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m (30) just super excited but I’m worried about tone when I’m reading. Despite being an avid reader, I’m a bit worried I’ll sound boring and when I read out loud my sentences aren’t very fluent because I sometimes read words out of order. I really love kids. So I’m gonna practice reading out loud. I know it’s still super early but I love books, I’ve always dreamed of reading out loud to loved ones like Mo from Inkheart, and I hope they’ll love them too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯蒂芬-金的《漫漫長路》被低估了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個狂熱的斯蒂芬-金的讀者，我只是不能相信它花了多長時間，我的閱讀。
進入這本書，一天下來，我已經快看了一半了。我不是那麼
進入荒誕派寫作，但這已經完全把我的襪子。

這本書最好的一點是，它不涉及任何... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdvjhc/the_long_walk_by_stephen_king_is_soo_underrated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdvjhc/the_long_walk_by_stephen_king_is_soo_underrated/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 23:48:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am an avid Stephen King reader and I just can&amp;#39;t beleive how long it took me to get into this book, I am almost halfway into it after one day. I am not so much into dystopian writing but this has completely taken my socks off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best thing about the book is that it doesn&amp;#39;t involve any supernatural phenomenon or characters but it succeeds in freaking you out. The characters are larger than life (as usual) and the story unfolds in a way that you can&amp;#39;t stop yourself from flipping through the pages (had to force myself to put it down and sleep) taking each step with the characters and hoping against all hope that you won&amp;#39;t get a ticket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would highly recommend this book to all Stephen King fans and you won&amp;#39;t regret taking it up your reading list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[從精神病患者的角度看書]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我很喜歡《夜裏的狗奇遇記》這本書，這本書從
一個自閉症男孩的觀點。我想知道是否有人知道一本書
從一個精神病患者的角度或以精神病患者爲主要對象
主角。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mdus8r/books_from_the_perspective_of_a_psychopath/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mdus8r/books_from_the_perspective_of_a_psychopath/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 21:25:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I enjoyed &amp;quot;The curious incident of the dog in the night&amp;quot; which is a book from the perspective of an autistic boy. I was wondering if anyone knows of a book from the perspective of a psychopath or with a psychopath as a major protagonist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國西部小說家拉里-麥克默特里去世，享年84歲。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdrbv7/larry_mcmurtry_novelist_of_the_american_west_dies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdrbv7/larry_mcmurtry_novelist_of_the_american_west_dies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 18:52:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只用4個字就讓大多數讀者瘋狂。]]></title><description><![CDATA[讓我們玩一個有趣的遊戲。我的例子是 "只讀CliffNotes""電影是
"我只看暢銷書""沒人有時間了""我把你折騰的
蓋。" "平淡無奇，讓人有想象力！！" "背面的Spoiler""Deckled
邊緣是最好的！"

我只有這些了。你有什麼辦法... ...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdidfc/make_most_readers_mad_in_just_4_words/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdidfc/make_most_readers_mad_in_just_4_words/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 18:52:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s play a fun game. My examples are:
“Only read the CliffNotes”
“movie is always better”
“I only read Bestsellers”
“No-one has time anymore”
“I bent your cover.”
“Blandness allows for imagination!!”
“Spoiler on the back”
“Deckled Edges are best!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all I got. What are some you can come up with?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[納尼亞這樣的書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近剛開始看《納尼亞傳奇》，一鼓作氣看完了。I
我不明白爲什麼我沒有早些讀到這些書 現在，我正在尋找
對於類似的東西是。我喜歡一般的幻想書，但我在尋找
現在爲類似的東西光。我喜歡沒有洞的感覺...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mdleex/books_like_narnia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mdleex/books_like_narnia/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 17:05:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just recently started the chronicles of Narnia and went through it one rush. I can&amp;#39;t understand why I haven&amp;#39;t read them earlier jn my life. Now, I am looking for something similar-is.
I do love fantasy books in general, but I am looking now for something similar light. I love how there is no holes in the plot, no back and forth in the time line, no complicated universe, mostly happy endings... . I want something as easy and smooth and wholesome as the Narnia books.
Any suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有爭議的意見。我希望高中時被迫讀一些難讀的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tl;dr：我討厭不能理解書本的深層含義，如果我是。
被迫在學校裏找，也許我現在可以做到。

經常看到這樣的帖子："十五年後，我終於又開始讀書了。I
以前經常讀書，但到了高中就被迫讀書，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdnto8/controversial_opinion_i_wish_i_was_forced_to_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdnto8/controversial_opinion_i_wish_i_was_forced_to_read/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 14:27:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tl;dr: I hate not being able to understand deeper meanings of books and if I was forced to find them at school, maybe I could do it now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often see posts like &amp;quot;I finally started reading again after fifteen years. I used to read a lot but then at high school I was forced to read and overanalyze books and poems and I hated them and my teacher basically killed my passion for reading for a long time&amp;quot;. Let me start by saying that I don&amp;#39;t try to invalidate that feeling. I just want to put here my perspective as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First let me give you some context. I think this holds for a lot of schools in my country (Czechia), but I know it&amp;#39;s definitely not the case in every school. We were taught about books and autors, but I don&amp;#39;t think I was ever forced to try to read and analyze something - usually someone read some excerpt of a book outloud and then we either simply continued, or sometimes the teacher explained it more in depth. And that was very rare. Only way in which we were forced to read was that for making our finals we were given a list of something like 100 or 200 books and we were to read 20 of them (with some restrictions - at least this many novels/plays/poetry/czech/foreign/20th century/18-19th century/before 17th century). At the finals we picked one of our chosen books at random and we were supposed to talk about it for some time and answer questions. Needless to say you usually didn&amp;#39;t need to actually read the books - some summary usually sufficed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to be clear, I used to love this model. I thought it was chosen well. And I don&amp;#39;t even claim now that it is a bad model. All I&amp;#39;m saying is that currently I wish I had been forced to do more at high school. Because nowadays I often read and I just feel that I&amp;#39;m missing the point, but I don&amp;#39;t know what it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read a lot of books that I didn&amp;#39;t actually enjoy that much, until I read what other people reading about it think - and what they can find in it. I am rarely capable of noticing beautiful prose unless someone points it out for me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year I dared myself and I read &lt;em&gt;Gravity&amp;#39;s Rainbow&lt;/em&gt; with the group on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/ThomasPynchon&quot;&gt;/r/ThomasPynchon&lt;/a&gt; and it was so great. Just to be clear, I definitely can&amp;#39;t say that the reading itself was always enjoyable - I was very frustrated very often. (And me not being native English speaker didn&amp;#39;t help.) But I always loved reading what other people see in it. And while I usually stop thinking about books quite soon after finishing them, I finished Gravity&amp;#39;s Rinbow in the fall of last year and I don&amp;#39;t think there was a week since then when I didn&amp;#39;t think about it once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this is super rare. I usually read what other people think about a book after I finish it, but it&amp;#39;s kinda hard to appriciate it in retrospect - I like to see the things while I read. But I don&amp;#39;t want to reread the book I just finished and I also don&amp;#39;t want to read other peoples thinkpieces beforehand, because I kinda hate spoilers. So unless I can find those things myself, it&amp;#39;s a lose-lose situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m getting better in destiling the meaning (and other things) out of books, but I still don&amp;#39;t really know what to do - and I wish that I had a high school teacher who would force me to try it (lets be honest, this analysis is kinda hard, and, well, it&amp;#39;s hard to force myself to do hard things) and who would give me feedback about what I find and what I don&amp;#39;t. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try to do this with poems. Poems seem to me as perfect format for learning analysing - they&amp;#39;re short, usually with nice prose and usually with some &amp;quot;deeper&amp;quot; meaning. I try to read a poem a day this year, but out of the more than 80 poems I read this year, I feel like I at least kinda succeded in analysing only about three or four. And poetry is hard, because I don&amp;#39;t know where to find analyzies of czech poems, so nobody really tells me what the &amp;quot;correct answer&amp;quot; is. (Yes, I&amp;#39;m aware, there is not really such thing as correct or incorrect analysis - but I wish I had &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; answer.) And while I often read novels in english, I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; struggle with english poems, so I don&amp;#39;t like this alternative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for being rambly, I just wanted to share my contraopinion to the succesful worldview I see in here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[適合6歲孩子看的冒險書，但寫得好的書，成年人又能真正喜歡？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我給兒子讀了《霍比特人》，他很喜歡（當然我也一直很喜歡這本書
次，我讀過）。) 它是我的興趣和魔法的完美平衡。
兒子，同時對我來說也足夠 "成熟"。

我們也讀過尼爾-蓋曼的《幸運牛奶》，這是一本非常不同的書。
風格，但它的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mdi3tt/adventure_books_that_are_appropriate_for_a_6_year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mdi3tt/adventure_books_that_are_appropriate_for_a_6_year/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 13:33:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read The Hobbit to my son and he loved it (and of course I’ve loved it all the times I’ve read it). It was the perfect balance of interest and magic for my son, while still being “mature” enough for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve also read &lt;em&gt;Fortunately the Milk&lt;/em&gt; by Neil Gaiman which is a very different style but it’s still about an adventure, and while the story itself is pretty childish it is witty and clever enough that I genuinely enjoyed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roald Dahl books could also fit in this category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find most kid’s chapter books are overly simplistic in their vocabulary and plot, with predictable one-dimensional characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what are some other good adventurous chapter books that are either for adults but good for kids, or written for kids and good enough for adults? I want depth and clever writing and interesting plot and characters, but still on a level that a kid can understand and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- I prefer it not be a series since there’s a decent chance my kid will lose interest and not let me read multiple books&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020年，當旅行被禁止的時候，我決定用閱讀世界上每個國家的書來代替。我把已經讀過的地方畫了出來，並開始撿拾新地方的文學作品。目前站在50個國家，期待着更多的國家。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdnw7v/in_2020_when_traveling_was_banned_i_decided_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mdnw7v/in_2020_when_traveling_was_banned_i_decided_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 13:33:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>