<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:50:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[美國通脹預期創下了12年多來的最高水平，因爲聯邦政府將再發行2萬億債務，而美聯儲卻憑空製造貨幣來購買。(這不是洋蔥網，而是真實發生的) https://t.co/swyNXiTmYJ。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370140346856902659</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370140346856902659</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:46:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[再見MongoDB，你好PostgreSQL(2015)]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26420665</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26420665</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:46:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每天早上檢查GME]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ttbz/checking_gme_every_morning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ttbz/checking_gme_every_morning/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何克服自己是個白癡？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，我上週買了20個AMD期權(.50美分/股)，2021年5月95美元的行使權，當。
AMD一直處於底部。我觀察AMD已經有一段時間了，我是造PC和
認爲他們的價值普遍被大大低估了，所以我想參與其中。但是
然後我在週五賣掉了它們，並買入了GME期權，以...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2z9w9/how_to_get_over_being_an_idiot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2z9w9/how_to_get_over_being_an_idiot/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I bought 20 AMD options last week(.50 cents/share), May 2021 $95 strike, when AMD has been at bottom. I have been watching AMD for a while, I build PCs and think they are generally hugely undervalued, so I wanted to get in on this. But then I sold them on Friday and bought GME options for the &amp;#39;squeeze&amp;#39; instead. My logic was that even if there is only a 20% chance of GME hitting 1k, I will be massively rich from that, to the point that it was worth risking the nearly &amp;quot;sure thing&amp;quot;(I saw it as maybe 90% that it would print in the next month, not this quickly though) of AMD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AMD options have gone from the 50 cents I bought them up to 2.50 per share...I basically lost out on 4k so far( a lot for me, I invest 100/week on a tight budget mostly as a hobby) and my GME options are tanking. Now, after doing more research, I think the squeeze is bullshit and I just FOMOed in, convincing myself in the moment that it was a rational decision. I am regretting this so much :(. I have a feeling like I missed out on a good opportunity I will never have again(even though of course there will be other plays, I hate this feeling so much)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[讓我們真正的談話，弱智。今天好玩嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想真誠地聽聽你們這些深陷蛋蛋的猿人今天有多開心。
我在$GME。我需要像今天這樣的衝動。我有一個爆炸。我開始在一個高從
市場前的數字。打了一些爵士白菜看早。失去了我的屎
與中午的懸崖。失去了更多的我的狗屎與... ...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2efv8/lets_real_talk_retards_how_fun_was_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2efv8/lets_real_talk_retards_how_fun_was_today/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to genuinely hear how fun today was for you apes that are balls deep with me in $GME. I needed a rush like today. I had a blast. I started on a high from pre market numbers. Hit some jazz cabbage watching the morning. LOST MY SHIT with that midday cliff. LOST EVEN MORE OF MY SHIT with that light speed bounce back that made this whole community looks like an autist brotherhood instead of a retard brotherhood for like 5 minutes. Polished off the jazz cabbage coasting through the afternoon with the absolute goldmine of content y’all were producing. I’m proud to be a member of this community and this revolution. Thank you for the journey. Diamond. Fucking. Hands. 💎🤝💎&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[永不放棄....，永不投降]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2hdvl/never_give_upnever_surrender/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2hdvl/never_give_upnever_surrender/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DeepFuckingValue - 電影預告]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2x00k/deepfuckingvalue_movie_teaser/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2x00k/deepfuckingvalue_movie_teaser/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME YOLO最新消息：回款超過500萬美元! (20,000股) ✋💎🤚昨天的過山車很好玩。🚀🚀🚀🚀老實說，我喜歡的股票，萊恩-科恩，貓，遊戲，雞肉和威士忌，沒有特別的順序。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2wt8j/gme_yolo_update_back_over_5000000_20000_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2wt8j/gme_yolo_update_back_over_5000000_20000_shares/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[那些對沖基金仍然沒有學會]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2s7c7/those_hedge_funds_still_havent_learned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2s7c7/those_hedge_funds_still_havent_learned/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我不喜歡尾風CSS]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26422286</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26422286</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的銀行給我寄了64張同一張借記卡的複印件。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26428453</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26428453</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 22:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的經紀人沒有限制我的成本基礎]]></title><description><![CDATA[我決定將我的一個賬號獻給PDT/免費乘車的違章大神。
而我的經紀人並沒有限制我每天的成本基礎。結果是，你可以看到在
圖片：https://imgur.com/Uq3a19s

我的問題是，這種瘋狂的成本基礎，對一個人來說有什麼影響嗎？
帳戶上有5千美元...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2oy8e/my_broker_didnt_limit_my_cost_basis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2oy8e/my_broker_didnt_limit_my_cost_basis/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:55:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided to sacrifice one of my accounts to the PDT/Free Ride violation gods, and my broker didn&amp;#39;t limit my daily cost basis. The result was as you can see in the picture: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/Uq3a19s&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/Uq3a19s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question is, are there any repercussions for this insane cost basis on an account with a $5k value?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ULTA美妝($ULTA)在報告售後市場時，收入與前景有上揚空間。用美國精神病患者來說明收入DD。]]></title><description><![CDATA[報告的第四季度營收數據將導致未來價格走勢>+-10%。
周。我看多並傾向於兩位數的上漲，原因如下。
共識的收入預期是21億美元，這意味着按年下降在兩個
總銷售額和同店銷售額。如果數據比...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2o0p7/ulta_beauty_ulta_upside_in_revenue_outlook_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2o0p7/ulta_beauty_ulta_upside_in_revenue_outlook_when/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reported Q4 revenue number will lead to price moves of &amp;gt;+-10% over the next week. I&amp;#39;m long &amp;amp; leaning towards a double digit upswing for reasons below:
Consensus revenue expectation is $2.1 billion which means yoy declines in both total sales &amp;amp; same-store sales. What if the numbers are better than expected? Obviously there are bulls expecting a beat but what if (pardon my language here) the Q4 revenue beat beats expectations? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;REASONS for the &amp;quot;beat beat&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s start with these internal facts: 1.ULTA makes 32% of its annual revenue in Q4. 2. ULTA current ytd revenue is only half of full year revenue for the previous year? Do you see where I&amp;#39;m going with this? Ulta&amp;#39;s Q4 revenue for this year should be higher as customers haven&amp;#39;t shopped that much ytd. (Relative to historical annual spend) ULTA will beat based on restocking and holiday splurges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now consider this scenario: you are Patrick Bateman and buy your cosmetics and skincare from ULTA Beauty. There&amp;#39;s a pandemic in 2020 so you slow down on shopping because you can&amp;#39;t risk catching covid in the store. As the year goes, you start ordering a few things online but not as much as you did in store (in person) pre-pandemic. However by Q4 you have WFH fatigue and you&amp;#39;re now ready to restock all your face creams, shower gel and makeup. Gotta show Paul Allen you&amp;#39;re still the MVP. You decide to order some essentials online plus it&amp;#39;s Christmas so you add some extras. You then realize that you&amp;#39;ve only spent half of what you normally spend at ULTA so you also get Evelyn an ULTA voucher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we look at Sephora&amp;#39;s numbers to test the beat beat view. Context: Sephora is owned by LVMH and is ULTA&amp;#39;s main competitor. Sephora only sells the fancy beauty (Think Dior &amp;amp; Estee Lauder) the high-life nothing cheap. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two things to note on these numbers:
Firstly, Sephora&amp;#39;s numbers are reported in the Selective Retailing Section of LVMH results. Selective Retailing combines Sephora with LVMH&amp;#39;s travel retailers (e.g DFS - which you see at the airport).
Secondly, there&amp;#39;s a date mismatch, Sephora year end is Dec vs Jan for ULTA, so ULTA quarters are a month ahead. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LVMH reported a recovery in selective retailing from a low of -38% in Q2 to -26% in Q4 in it&amp;#39;s 2020 annual results. Now -26% sounds bad but LVMH&amp;#39;s travel retailers account for the bulk of the decline. No travel = no revenue for DFS. Travel retail accounts for 20-35% of division revenue so adjusting for the collapse in travel leads to improved metrics for Sephora. This means SEPHORA IS BACK! IT&amp;#39;S RECOVERED TO PRE PANDEMIC REVENUE. Sephora revenue is global but makes a good read-through for the US market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we&amp;#39;re on Sephora as an ULTA long I&amp;#39;m not sleeping well since Sephora announced a store arrangement with Kohl&amp;#39;s which will be a long term headache for ULTA. Kohl&amp;#39;s unlike JCPenney (RIP) has locations in US strip malls which is Ulta&amp;#39;s niche. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LVMH&amp;#39;s numbers IMO offer the best peer comparison despite their opacity. It&amp;#39;s tempting to compare ULTA with general beauty sales data but ULTA has historically had low correlation to general retail data and 2020 just made general data even less useful. When large stores like Macys and other department stores report lower sales this counts for most of the decline in market data which makes it hard to assess smaller players like ULTA. This increases the uncertainty in the Q4 revenue number. Good setup for option opportunities but I excluded trades as my DD on the &amp;quot;beat beat&amp;quot; view. Please share options strategies in the comments. &lt;a href=&quot;http://ir.ultabeauty.com/financial-reports/quarterly-reports/default.aspx&quot;&gt;ULTA Financials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lvmh.com/investors/investors-and-analysts/publications/&quot;&gt;LVMH Financials &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/股票每日討論與期權交易 星期四 - 2021年3月11日]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是每天的討論，所以任何與股票有關的東西都可以，但主題是什麼？
今天是關於股票期權，但如果期權不是你的事，那麼就忽略了
主題和/或發表你的反對意見......。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2n9tl/rstocks_daily_discussion_options_trading_thursday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2n9tl/rstocks_daily_discussion_options_trading_thursday/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme for today is on stock options, but if options aren&amp;#39;t your thing then just ignore the theme and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+semiannual+arguments+against+TA%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;post your arguments against options here&lt;/a&gt; and not in the current post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful day to day links, including news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=amd&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required info to start understanding options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/c/calloption.asp&quot;&gt;Call option Investopedia video&lt;/a&gt; basically a call option allows you to buy 100 shares of a stock at a certain price (strike price), but without the obligation to buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/putoption.asp&quot;&gt;Put option Investopedia video&lt;/a&gt; a put option allows you to sell 100 shares of a stock at a certain price (strike price), but without the obligation to sell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the following word cloud and click through for the wiki:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/wiki/options-themed-post&quot;&gt;Call option - Put option - Exercising an option - Strike price - ITM - OTM - ATM - Long options - Short options - Combo - Debit - Credit or Premium - Covered call - Naked - Debit call spread - Credit call spread - Strangle - Iron condor - Vertical debit spreads - Iron Fly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is delta,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia delta&amp;quot; and click the investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場休市。
 
✧ S&amp;P 500 △ 1.04%。                 
✧ 納斯達克 △ 2.52%。            
✧ 羅素2K △ 2.31%。                 
✧ 道瓊斯 △ 0.58% https://t.co/F1sOOuwwj5]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370117553360678915</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370117553360678915</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:35:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shift（$SFT）DD：Carvana的一個快速增長的競爭對手，似乎被低估了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[什麼是Shift？

 * Shift是一個在線平臺，你可以購買二手車和/或出售你的二手車。
   車。他們的主要競爭對手是Carvana和Vroom。

我從來沒有聽說過Shift......他們甚至可以與Carvana這樣的大公司競爭嗎？

 *二手車的銷量其實一直都比新車大...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2rh7l/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2rh7l/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:22:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is Shift?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift is an online platform where you can buy used cars and/or sell your used car. Their main competitors are Carvana and Vroom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never heard of Shift..can they even compete with big players like Carvana?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used car sales are actually consistently greater than new car sales in the US, and for over a decade, the rate of used car sales has been growing faster than the rate of new car sales. The total used car market in the US was $841b in 2019, yet less than 1% of all car sales in 2019 occurred on an ecommerce marketplace like Carvana or Shift. This is at odds with the trends, as more consumers are moving towards doing most if not all of their shopping online. This trend was accelerated with the COVID 19 pandemic. There is plenty of space for growth in this category for several major players. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What separates Shift from their competitors, such as Carvana and Vroom?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift has several unique features compared to their competitors. They are the only service in their space that offers free test drives at your home. If you see the car you like online, you can request to test drive it, and Shift will bring it to your door for you to test drive with no commitment to buy. They also focus on older cars compared to their competitors, specifically cars that are 3-5 and 6-10 years old. They also focus on cars that are less than $20k in price, with 40% of their sales being $10k-$20k and 16% being &amp;lt;$10k. Cars of this age and price range are the largest segment of the used car market. For reference, 1-3 year old car listings comprise 48% of Carvana&amp;#39;s and 68% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings, compared to just 25% of Shift&amp;#39;s. Cars priced over $20k comprise 79% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings and 27% of Carvana&amp;#39;s, compared to 20% of Shift&amp;#39;s. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where does Shift operate?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They currently operate primarily in the west coast including California, the state with the largest number of vehicles sold per year, Portland, Oregon and Seattle, Washington. In Q4 of 2020, they launched four hubs in Texas, the state with the third largest vehicle market, in Dallas, Fort Worth, Austin and San Antonio, with more plans for future expansion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Numbers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s how Shift&amp;#39;s current numbers stack up against their competitors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Feature&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Shift&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Carvana&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Vroom*&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Share price as of 3/10/2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$260.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$34.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Market Cap&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$716M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$44.8B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$4.62B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Total Enterprise Value (TEV)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$497M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$46.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$3.92B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 Revenue&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$195.7M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$5.58B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$1.36B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue (average of analysts)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$445M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$2.51B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue Growth %&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;127%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;56%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;85%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.54x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8.3x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.88x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.1x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5.36x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.56x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/EBITDA&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.41x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-563x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-16.2x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note that Vroom is down nearly 33% this month and is just now approaching levels comparable to Shift at its current price level. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the table above, we can see that by buying Shift, you are paying a lower multiple even when factoring in analyst&amp;#39;s average estimates of larger growth (over 100%) in 2021 compared to their competitors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recent Earnings (3/09/2021)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift has been growing very rapidly and shows no signs of slowing down: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Q4 of 2020, they sold 4,666 units earning $73.4m revenue, representing 147% and 168% year over year growth and ended the year at $195.7m in total revenue (18% YoY growth) with 13,135 units sold. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their margins have also drastically improved, with their adjusted gross profit per unit in 2020 being $1,350 compared to $811 the year before, a 66% change. This has been largely due to their focus in 2020 on building up their in-house recondition (repairs/maintenance) team instead of relying on 3rd party mechanic vendors, with only 14% of cars being reconditioned by 3rd parties in Jan of 2021 compared to 45% at its peak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they have grown their in-house reconditioning team&amp;#39;s ability to process cars in house, they have invested significantly in acquiring inventory, and have increased their sellable inventory by 148% from December 2020 to March 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec 31st, 2020, the company had $234m in cash and cash equivalents and $49m in inventory, with $312m in total assets and $74.9m in total liabilities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2021 Guidance:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Q1 of 2021, they are guiding revenue of $90m-$95m, representing 200-217% YoY growth. For 2021, they are expecting $450M in revenue, a 130% YoY increase and is inline with analyst&amp;#39;s expectations, with $1,600 adjusted gross profit per unit, a 19% YoY increase, which is on track for their target of $2,500 in the next few years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hold shares in Shift and continue to buy at these prices as I am bullish on the company. Thanks for reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在30天內做60次技術面試時看到的危險信號]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26426602</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26426602</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:45:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天早上我把9萬塊錢扔進了GME。不要讓我失望，APES的朋友們。🦍🚀💎]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rvim/i_threw_90k_into_gme_this_morning_dont_let_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rvim/i_threw_90k_into_gme_this_morning_dont_let_me/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲了紀念GME達到200歲--我買了100件披肩在巴林發放。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2u8en/in_honor_of_gme_hitting_200_i_bought_100/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2u8en/in_honor_of_gme_hitting_200_i_bought_100/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年3月10日]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2jcgj/march_10th_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2jcgj/march_10th_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場調整和收益率的說法似乎已經結束，新的主動上行序列正在進行中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在這一點上。報道了CPI，本週進行了國債拍賣。
今天30年債券還有一個）。

看來市場改變了說法。收益率連同收益率曲線
控制不再是說法。下週，FED有FOMC，但很可能是
不會有任何行動或...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ve17/market_correction_and_yield_narrative_looks_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ve17/market_correction_and_yield_narrative_looks_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point: CPI was reported and treasury auctions took place this week (there is one more for 30 year bonds today).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It looks the market changed the narrative. The yield along with Yield Curve Control is no more the narrative. Next week, the FED has the FOMC but likely there will be no action or hint but may introduce some temporary volatility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the market looks to be starting a new active sequence upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我和我的紙手GF]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2kmjq/me_and_my_paperhanded_gf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2kmjq/me_and_my_paperhanded_gf/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 20:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[用Godot和Nakama製作在線多人遊戲。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26416545</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26416545</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:55:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shift（$SFT）DD：Carvana的一個快速增長的競爭對手，似乎被低估了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[什麼是Shift？

 * Shift是一個在線平臺，你可以購買二手車和/或出售你的二手車。
   車。他們的主要競爭對手是Carvana和Vroom。

我從來沒有聽說過Shift......他們甚至可以與Carvana這樣的大公司競爭嗎？

 *二手車的銷量其實一直都比新車大...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2qd6k/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m2qd6k/shift_sft_dd_a_rapidly_growing_competitor_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:41:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is Shift?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift is an online platform where you can buy used cars and/or sell your used car. Their main competitors are Carvana and Vroom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never heard of Shift..can they even compete with big players like Carvana?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used car sales are actually consistently greater than new car sales in the US, and for over a decade, the rate of used car sales has been growing faster than the rate of new car sales. The total used car market in the US was $841b in 2019, yet less than 1% of all car sales in 2019 occurred on an ecommerce marketplace like Carvana or Shift. This is at odds with the trends, as more consumers are moving towards doing most if not all of their shopping online. This trend was accelerated with the COVID 19 pandemic. There is plenty of space for growth in this category for several major players. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What separates Shift from their competitors, such as Carvana and Vroom?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift has several unique features compared to their competitors. They are the only service in their space that offers free test drives at your home. If you see the car you like online, you can request to test drive it, and Shift will bring it to your door for you to test drive with no commitment to buy. They also focus on older cars compared to their competitors, specifically cars that are 3-5 and 6-10 years old. They also focus on cars that are less than $20k in price, with 40% of their sales being $10k-$20k and 16% being &amp;lt;$10k. Cars of this age and price range are the largest segment of the used car market. For reference, 1-3 year old car listings comprise 48% of Carvana&amp;#39;s and 68% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings, compared to just 25% of Shift&amp;#39;s. Cars priced over $20k comprise 79% of Vroom&amp;#39;s listings and 27% of Carvana&amp;#39;s, compared to 20% of Shift&amp;#39;s. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where does Shift operate?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They currently operate primarily in the west coast including California, the state with the largest number of vehicles sold per year, Portland, Oregon and Seattle, Washington. In Q4 of 2020, they launched four hubs in Texas, the state with the third largest vehicle market, in Dallas, Fort Worth, Austin and San Antonio, with more plans for future expansion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Numbers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s how Shift&amp;#39;s current numbers stack up against their competitors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Feature&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Shift&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Carvana&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Vroom*&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Share price as of 3/10/2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.55&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$260.45&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$34.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Market Cap&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$716M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$44.8B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$4.62B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Total Enterprise Value (TEV)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$497M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$46.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$3.92B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 Revenue&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$195.7M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$5.58B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$1.36B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue (average of analysts)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$445M&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$8.7B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$2.51B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Estimated 2021 Revenue Growth %&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;127%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;56%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;85%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2020 TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.54x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8.3x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2.88x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/REV&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.1x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5.36x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.56x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;NTM TEV/EBITDA&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-4.41x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-563x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;-16.2x&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note that Vroom is down nearly 33% this month and is just now approaching levels comparable to Shift at its current price level. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the table above, we can see that by buying Shift, you are paying a lower multiple even when factoring in analyst&amp;#39;s average estimates of larger growth (over 100%) in 2021 compared to their competitors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recent Earnings (3/09/2021)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift has been growing very rapidly and shows no signs of slowing down: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Q4 of 2020, they sold 4,666 units earning $73.4m revenue, representing 147% and 168% year over year growth and ended the year at $195.7m in total revenue (18% YoY growth) with 13,135 units sold. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their margins have also drastically improved, with their adjusted gross profit per unit in 2020 being $1,350 compared to $811 the year before, a 66% change. This has been largely due to their focus in 2020 on building up their in-house recondition (repairs/maintenance) team instead of relying on 3rd party mechanic vendors, with only 14% of cars being reconditioned by 3rd parties in Jan of 2021 compared to 45% at its peak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they have grown their in-house reconditioning team&amp;#39;s ability to process cars in house, they have invested significantly in acquiring inventory, and have increased their sellable inventory by 148% from December 2020 to March 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec 31st, 2020, the company had $234m in cash and cash equivalents and $49m in inventory, with $312m in total assets and $74.9m in total liabilities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;2021 Guidance:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Q1 of 2021, they are guiding revenue of $90m-$95m, representing 200-217% YoY growth. For 2021, they are expecting $450M in revenue, a 130% YoY increase and is inline with analyst&amp;#39;s expectations, with $1,600 adjusted gross profit per unit, a 19% YoY increase, which is on track for their target of $2,500 in the next few years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hold shares in Shift and continue to buy at these prices as I am bullish on the company. Thanks for reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜在大流行期間悄悄開始打造連鎖雜貨店。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-11/amazon-quietly-began-building-a-grocery-chain-during-pandemic

雜貨店分析師表示，亞馬遜生鮮店很可能廉價推出，甚至是
運行成本更低--這是在一個衆所周知的環境中長期佔有一席之地的完美武器。
低利潤行業。

分析師...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ss0t/amazon_quietly_began_building_a_grocery_chain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ss0t/amazon_quietly_began_building_a_grocery_chain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-11/amazon-quietly-began-building-a-grocery-chain-during-pandemic&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-11/amazon-quietly-began-building-a-grocery-chain-during-pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grocery analysts say Amazon Fresh stores are likely cheap to launch and even cheaper to run—the perfect weapon to stake a long-term claim in a famously low-margin  industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts have long expected Amazon to bring its cashierless technology to larger stores. The company currently operates two Go Grocery locations, the largest of which is about 13,000 square feet—or roughly six times the size of the original convenience stores. Fresh stores are substantially larger, ranging from from 25,000 square feet to 45,000 square feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon is always looking for a way to defend from walmart and target, amazon fresh store is the perfect answer. Amazon keep improving the logistic warehouses and expanding the delivery network, the fresh store will be easily managed and capturing the low margin market share. Amazon is providing an unlimited growth opportunity for shareholders, for investor who bought amazon under $3k for the latest pullback, congratulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[由於每分鐘都要檢查價格是如此的緊張，我選擇了一個自動化的解決方案，這使我的生活變得更加輕鬆！我的生活是如此的簡單。💎💎💎🖐🖐🖐🚀🚀🚀]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ncx1/as_checking_the_price_every_minute_was_so_nerve/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ncx1/as_checking_the_price_every_minute_was_so_nerve/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[深度造假。DFV在2069年以69億美元的價格賣出他的GME頭寸。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2obpb/deepfake_dfv_sells_his_gme_position_in_2069_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2obpb/deepfake_dfv_sells_his_gme_position_in_2069_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME--圖表，同樣的事情在第一次擠壓前幾天也發生了。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ltnf/gme_chart_the_exact_same_thing_happened_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2ltnf/gme_chart_the_exact_same_thing_happened_days/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘿，婊子，你想賺點錢嗎？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rgaj/gme_hey_bitch_do_you_want_to_make_some_fucking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2rgaj/gme_hey_bitch_do_you_want_to_make_some_fucking/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME警示錄]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天的蘸料真他媽好喫，但也讓我們學到了一些東西。

1.) 撤掉你他媽的止損，這他媽怎麼還需要說。爲什麼要這樣說呢？
你是讓機器人📄🙌🏻給你嗎？

2.) 一半的人都是他媽的神誰買了浸，並得到了一個該死的STEAL的
一些保證彩票...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m28ibs/gme_cautionary_tale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m28ibs/gme_cautionary_tale/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s dip was fucking delicious but it taught us a few things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) Remove your fucking stop losses how the fuck does this need to be said. Why are you letting a robot 📄 🙌🏻 for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) Half of y’all are fucking gods who bought the dip, and got a damn STEAL on some guaranteed lottery tickets 💰💰💰&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.) The other half of y’all weren’t actually waiting on a dip (even though you guys spam it for upvotes like fucking degenerate gremlins) and pussied out when it was time our time to put our NUTS on the hedgies chin. 🌰🌰🌰&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actual important shit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) They are running out of ammo, those drops had fuck all volume behind them. That short attack topped any of the previous attacks, even going back to January. They’re running out of short volume and they know it. We are (for real this time) in the endgame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) CNBC and other shill outlets are tightly gagged, we are seeing tangibly less coverage across the board than at this far up in the share price a month ago. Only rarely to be released to revel in any tiny downtick of the share price. This is for a reason. Last time everybody was shitting themselves over GME, it was everywhere. And because of this, MANY retail investors hopped on the train and sucked up a lot of volume in a short period, hence the silence now. This is potentially a good thing because it means no influx of uneducated monkeys who know jack shit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.) We need educate new members of this fuck wagon on what is going on. IN THE SIMPLEST TERMS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: NEWBIES! YOU’LL KNOW WHEN THE SQUEEZE IS HAPPENING! IT WILL FUCKING SKYROCKET *$5000+ MINIMUM. DONT SELL (unless you have to I know everyone has varying circumstances) DONT BUY UNLESS YOURE READY FOR A HIGH VOLATILITY STOCK. SHIT GOES UP DOWN BACK FORWARD, FUCKING BACKFLIPS. Stop asking stupid shit and hold on&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR; Remove your stop losses. Weaponize the newly born apes. Everything has led to now. The media has sorta fucked off, paper hands are long gone. The shorts have one bullet in the gun and they’re saving it to shoot themselves in the mouth. Hang on and have fun. Love you apes &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not a cat, I’m an ape.
This is not financial advice. 
🙌🏻💎🙌🏻💎🙌🏻💎🙌🏻💎🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: ok fuck 5k minimum&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: get clickbaited lul. GO SET LIMIT BUYS STOP GIVING AWARDS HAHAHA THANKS BUT FUCK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年3月11日的GME Megathread第二部分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的天啊，我的天啊？]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2uy4f/gme_megathread_part_2_for_march_11_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2uy4f/gme_megathread_part_2_for_march_11_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;holy moly! holy moly? ... &lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;holy&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;moly.&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME和AMC的圖表今天在那次大規模下跌中。一模一樣？可以說是戰術上的。人的情緒對市場的買入和賣出起着很大的作用，這些對沖基金就是想通過這些協同攻擊來觸發你的賣出。保持💎🙌🏼，記住你爲什麼買股票，保持遲鈍。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2bjre/gme_and_amc_charts_today_during_that_mass_drop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2bjre/gme_and_amc_charts_today_during_that_mass_drop/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲了一隻幾乎沒有研究過的股票，向所有的人和大家表示敬意。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2t9a2/shoutout_to_anyone_and_everyone_putting_it_all_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2t9a2/shoutout_to_anyone_and_everyone_putting_it_all_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我超級樂意看惡霸剃掉GME和AMC的1/3？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，WSB，這是我第一次正式發帖，但我很自豪地看到我們是如何的
都HODL一起真的很強。

我自2019年10月30日起，5月29日增持1670股，在GME
2020年，我希望能截圖證明我的話，但我的保管員。
帳戶不允許任何...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m25szi/why_im_super_happy_to_watch_evil_hedgies_shave_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m25szi/why_im_super_happy_to_watch_evil_hedgies_shave_13/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello WSB, this is my first official post, but I&amp;#39;m very proud to see how we have all HODL together really strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been in GME since 30 Oct 2019 with an additional 1670 shares on 29 May 2020 and I wish I could take a screenshot to prove my words, but my custodian account does not allow any screenshots out of &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; reasons. I currently hold over 6 digits of value in GME and I hope to reach my 7 digits and possibly 8. After what happened today, my 7 digits is certain, 8 digits possible. With more crayons maybe I&amp;#39;ll reach 9.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said I like to share and encourage with everyone why this nosedive drop we seen today is actually the BEST affirmation we really need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s been wonderful DD that the Short interest are still extremely high and that the data in FINRA is entirely unreliable. Let&amp;#39;s be honest, before what happened today, no matter how certain we are, we weren&amp;#39;t 100% sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m an expert in Chinese history, and I&amp;#39;ll quote Sun Tzu, the famed author recognised for writing the Art of War over 2000 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles. If you know yourself but not the enemy, for every victory gained you will also suffer a defeat. If you know neither the enemy nor yourself, you will succumb in every battle.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truth is we never really knew what the hedges were up to and this week was really fishy, with the absence of obvious short ladders and peaceful markets. Other than occasional dips everyday after reaching a peak, we couldn&amp;#39;t tell much. Some people have speculated that maybe the hedges were buying calls in order to reduce their risks, but I think we can all agree now that there is a good possibility that the dips we&amp;#39;ve been seeing the last few days are just a test for hedges to see how much the price can be affected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let&amp;#39;s be honest with ourselves, that was a coordinated attack. I have no idea how long they have planned that, but looking from what we&amp;#39;ve seen, it&amp;#39;s definitely a lot of time. At that scale it&amp;#39;s not possible for 1 or 2 hedge funds to pull this off by themselves. And YET!! This is where we recovered strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what this means is this. The hedges are panicking. They are worried. And they have proven that the shorts &lt;em&gt;HAVE NOT BEEN COVERED&lt;/em&gt;. If they have been covered to the large extent they claimed to, today&amp;#39;s coordinated attack wouldn&amp;#39;t have happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just did they admit with their actions that they are fearing us, they also basically highlighted to us what stocks they are all massively shorting. AMC, KOSS, NOK, BB all are in this together with us GME Army! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know it&amp;#39;s like Harry Potter, where Voldemort basically handed the weapons to Harry by his own hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on Chinese History, there&amp;#39;s this clever strategist Sun Tzu. For him before he executes any clever maneuvers for war, he will always test them first. If the hedges we are up against are the same smooth brain people like Sun Tzu, this fall is only a test. But it&amp;#39;s costly to them and we have held strong. With the current prices, supposing they did buy some shares to cover their losses, all those buys from 180 to 250 are all gone. Now they are forced to buy shares above 260 and its only going to cost them even more. Much better for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fellow apes, they are really afraid of our gamma squeeze this week and next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now... We strike back, by doing NOTHING!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/aTaF8j6&quot;&gt;to the skeptics who need proof for everything&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I obviously have better things than to post everything on social media like a attention seeking person. I&amp;#39;m a retarded ape not a peacock. Your tongues will wag too no matter what even if my picture has shown my platform to be ancient. But that&amp;#39;s nothing to do with my investing preferences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For you skeptics who need proof for everything and choose to always doubt and flake, here it is. &amp;quot;A confident man does not live for the applause and approval of the non-worthy&amp;quot;. Your skeptical outlook has only said to me that you clearly did not see Gamestop for what it really was earlier on, and even if DFV&amp;#39;s DD was shown to you in those days, you were a late adopter. It has also shown me that you have the paper hands tendency when you don&amp;#39;t see potential and when the going gets tough. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought I have surpassed and ignored most silly comments, but thanks to the 1% of negative words, you have helped me see I still react to silly nonsense and it&amp;#39;s something I need to change in myself. You are a Hyena and this is a community of apes. Reflect on yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[用HackRF和1.2米衛星天線接收SpaceX獵鷹9號遙測數據。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423406</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423406</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 19:01:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有人在牛市中不舒服嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[作爲一個喜歡買跌停板的人，並且在各個板塊中擁有大量的股票。
(除科技股外)他們想買... 我覺得牛市的發生在
至少一個月左右，然後通脹率在5月份又回升了。

但不管出於什麼原因，我覺得很不滿意，很沮喪，對... ...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2k8hk/anyone_else_uncomfortable_in_a_bull_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2k8hk/anyone_else_uncomfortable_in_a_bull_market/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As someone who likes to buy the dip and has plenty of stocks in various sectors (other than tech) they want to buy... I sense a bull market happening for at least a month or so, and then inflation popping it&amp;#39;s head back up in May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for whatever reason, I feel very dissatisfied and frustrated on &amp;quot;up&amp;quot; green days, and get massive FOMO when most of the stocks on my watchlist are up 3-5% and the one&amp;#39;s at worst are in the -1-+1% range. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people panic or get emotional when stocks go down, but I feel much more comfortable there with buying opportunities. It&amp;#39;s times like these where I get anxious and feel I didn&amp;#39;t do &amp;quot;enough&amp;quot; on a given day (or in prior days ESPECIALLY on down days where I bought maybe 2-3 stocks and could have in retrospect bought 5-6) especially when my portfolio only goes up maybe .25% or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is coming from someone  who looked at stocks in past months and realized had they gotten them then, they would virtually all be at higher valuations today. Also as someone who is trying to transition out of tech into other sectors, but so far is not quite there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[賣出認沽期權，想確定我是否瞭解風險。]]></title><description><![CDATA[試圖在r/Options [/r/Options]中發佈這個帖子，但作爲一個新的交易者被刪除。
的問題。是不是要向有識之士學習交易期權，我
不明白嗎？總之，也許這裏有人能讓我放心。

在過去的6年裏，我對基本期權交易有了更多的瞭解。
幾個月。I…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s5f9/selling_put_option_want_to_make_sure_i_understand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s5f9/selling_put_option_want_to_make_sure_i_understand/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tried posting this in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/Options&quot;&gt;r/Options&lt;/a&gt; but removed as a new trader question.  Isn&amp;#39;t the point to learn trading option from knowledgeable people I don&amp;#39;t get it? Anyhow, maybe someone here can reassure me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve gotten a bit more comfortable with basic options trading over the past 6 months. I still consider selling a put option a basic task but very important to add to the repertoire for setting up more complex strategies. I want to start getting more comfortable with this type of trade as well. I want to keep the first one small just to make sure I don&amp;#39;t screw it up or lose a bunch of money. I&amp;#39;ll outline the trade below and just want to make sure there&amp;#39;s no huge potential for loss here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to own Palantir (PLTR) at $23.5, it is currently trading at $26. My assumption is that I can sell the put option (sell to open) contract for a strike price of $23.5 for whatever date I choose (looking short term just to start off - say April 1). If the price of PLTR drops to $23.5 at any point during that period and gets executed, I am assigned the shares at the strike price of $23.5 (minus the premium I receive so actually less than $23.5 overall). If it never hits the strike price of $23.5, the contract expires I get no shares but I collect the premium. Am I missing something on this that might cost me a bunch of money? I know that I need to ensure I have the capitol in my portfolio to cover the cost of the contract if it gets executed, that&amp;#39;s not an issue. But my concern is my Brokerage states my maximum loss potential is $2,239 which scares me. I&amp;#39;m assuming that the $2,239 loss is actually just the cost for purchasing the shares minus the premium received, but that to me is not a loss I still own an underlying equity worth $2350 (i.e. no loss).  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲何蘋果股票拋售是黃金買入機會 $AAPL]]></title><description><![CDATA[山西瑞思林 [https://www.benzinga.com/users/shanthi-rexaline] , Benzinga
撰稿人

蘋果公司 AAPL 1.65%[https://benzinga.com/stock/aapl#NASDAQ]股價可能有
在最近的科技股拋售中遭受打擊，但Wedbush分析師的一位分析師
表示，他對該股的信念只...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s8x9/why_apples_stock_selloff_is_a_golden_buying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2s8x9/why_apples_stock_selloff_is_a_golden_buying/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:31:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/users/shanthi-rexaline&quot;&gt;Shanthi Rexaline&lt;/a&gt; , Benzinga Staff Writer &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://benzinga.com/stock/aapl#NASDAQ&quot;&gt;AAPL 1.65%&lt;/a&gt; shares may have taken a beating in the recent tech sell-off, but an analyst at Wedbush analyst said his conviction in the stock has only increased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Apple Analyst:&lt;/strong&gt; Daniel Ives has an Outperform rating and $175 price target for Apple shares, with the bull case price target at $225. Wedbush added the stock to its &amp;quot;Best Ideas&amp;quot; list. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Apple Thesis:&lt;/strong&gt; After a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/21/01/19370036/apple-analysts-lift-price-targets-following-jaw-dropper-q1-4-sell-side-takes&quot;&gt;stellar December quarter&lt;/a&gt;, when Apple managed to crush iPhone estimates, some cuts in the iPhone forecasts for fiscal year 2021 were discounted by the market, Ives said in a note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is reflected in the stock&amp;#39;s sell-off over the last month, the analyst said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wedbush&amp;#39;s Asia checks are markedly bullish, suggesting over 230 million units for 2021, he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initial build forecast for the iPhone 13 indicates the supercycle will continue into fiscal year 2022, Ives said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Geographically speaking, demand in China looks strong coming out of the Chinese New Year and remains a linchpin to our Apple bull thesis.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The analyst also sees continued uptick in ASPs due to a higher mix of the iPhone Pro and Pro Max, with the Mini being significantly scaled down around production/demand globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/21/02/19766821/why-apple-will-hit-a-3-trillion-market-cap-by-the-end-of-2021&quot;&gt;$3-trillion valuation in sight&lt;/a&gt; for Cupertino, the recent sell-off in share creates a golden buying opportunity, according to Wedbush. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AAPL Price Action:&lt;/strong&gt; Apple shares lost 0.91% in Wednesday&amp;#39;s session, closing at $119.98. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞典太陽系]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26424090</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26424090</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通貨膨脹的一個定義是 "太多的錢追逐太少的商品"。我們借了數萬億美元來給超過一億人送免費的錢，這些人在大流行期間從未失去工作/收入--這是第三次。如果這不會造成通貨膨脹，那麼什麼都不會。https://t.co/eFLT2fiKgo。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370025005107404815</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1370025005107404815</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir宣佈4月21日舉辦 "雙擊 "演示活動]]></title><description><![CDATA[文章。
https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-announces-double-click-demo-114500595.html

文章複製粘貼，供夠懶的你參考。Palantir技術
(NYSE:PLTR)今天宣佈，將舉行 "雙十一 "活動。
點擊》演示活動於2021年4月14日（週三），...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2q0v6/palantir_announces_double_click_demo_event_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2q0v6/palantir_announces_double_click_demo_event_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Article: &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-announces-double-click-demo-114500595.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/palantir-announces-double-click-demo-114500595.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copy and Paste of Article for those of you lazy enough:
Palantir Technologies (NYSE:PLTR) today announced that it will hold the first in a series of &amp;quot;Double Click&amp;quot; demo events on Wednesday, April 14, 2021, at 11:00am ET.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir software is used by customers across 40 industries worldwide. Double Click is Palantir&amp;#39;s series of software demo events that showcase how the company&amp;#39;s platforms are used across these industries and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first event will feature in-depth demonstrations of Palantir Foundry for life sciences and industrials. Palantir’s customers in these verticals include Merck, NIH, NHS, 3M, bp, PG&amp;amp;E, LANXESS, Doosan, and others. The software demos at Double Click will showcase how customers can use Archetypes, Palantir’s solution to deploy end-to-end use cases in a matter of clicks, on top of Foundry, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life Sciences: harmonized patient view, clinical and observational data curation, prognostic model management, accelerated discovery via scientific research collaboration&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Industrials: end-to-end quality assurance, production optimization, high-scale IoT analytics, supply chain optimization&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advance registration is required, and is available at &lt;a href=&quot;https://palantir.events/doubleclick&quot;&gt;https://palantir.events/doubleclick&lt;/a&gt;. Capacity is limited, and registration will close 24 hours prior to the event. For any questions regarding the event, please email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:double-click@palantir.com&quot;&gt;double-click@palantir.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didn&amp;#39;t see anyone post about it yesterday, so I thought I&amp;#39;d create a thread and see what people have to say. I think these kinds of demo events will only boost PLTR, especially in the long-term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[旭Linux進展報告。2021年1月/2月]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26421963</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26421963</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[簡單書寫]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423090</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26423090</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 17:15:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fda審批跳轉，提前得到消息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿嘿

我想看看是否有任何方法可以獲得自動更新或實時更新。
爲什麼東西得到FDA批准？

總是有一個跳躍。對於50-300％，從我最近看到的和任何東西，
可以幫助獲得領先的曲線和之前stocktwits等將是巨大的!]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ls9d/fda_approval_jumps_and_getting_the_news_early/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ls9d/fda_approval_jumps_and_getting_the_news_early/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:28:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was looking to see if there are any ways to get auto updates or live updates for when things get FDA approved?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theres always a jump. For 50-300% from what I&amp;#39;ve seen recently and anything that can help get ahead of the curve and before stocktwits etc would be great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[高速公路標誌US9號南。💎💎💎🖐🖐🖐🚀🚀🚀🌚]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m29uzz/highway_sign_us_9_south/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m29uzz/highway_sign_us_9_south/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 16:28:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[現實中，你主動交易的股票有多少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於各位活躍的交易者來說，你是堅守在少數幾隻股票上，還是嘗試在
把它分散到所有東西上？我發現很難集中精力，當有...
市場上發生的事情太多了! 我可能會忽略我想做的事情。
通過追逐其他股票來完成。你如何管理你的...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2gddn/realistically_how_many_stocks_do_you_actively/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2gddn/realistically_how_many_stocks_do_you_actively/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:45:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For you active traders, do you stick to a handful of stocks or do you try to spread it out over everything?  I&amp;#39;m finding it hard to concentrate when there&amp;#39;s so much going on in the market!  I can lose sight of what I am trying to accomplish by chasing other stocks.  How do you manage your stocks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thank you for your comments and insight!  I think I&amp;#39;ve just been stretching myself too thin, and it&amp;#39;s been exhausting.  I will stick to a handful of the stocks I know and we&amp;#39;ll just see what happens!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年3月11日的全球環境監測系統Megathread。]]></title><description><![CDATA[由於我們又回到了評論的極限，我將發佈一個GME的大討論。
第二部分中午左右。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2q39b/gme_megathread_for_march_11_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m2q39b/gme_megathread_for_march_11_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:27:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since we&amp;#39;re back to hitting comment limits, I&amp;#39;ll be posting a GME megathread part two around noon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME突破300美元！讓我們讓這枚火箭繼續強大起來，讓埃隆爸爸感到驕傲]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m21szq/gme_broke_300_lets_keep_this_rocket_going_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m21szq/gme_broke_300_lets_keep_this_rocket_going_so/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:27:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福島事件10年後，核電期待重振雄風]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26419334</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26419334</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:26:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我通宵工作，由於時間安排的原因，我從來沒有機會在市場開盤時參與主動買入。昨天我錯過了一個機會。我有一個問題要問輪班工人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天我下了一個RBLX的限價單，當我下午5點左右醒來的時候看到我的
訂單一直沒有成交，因爲價格馬上飆升。

這已經不是我第一次錯過買入機會了。我可能不會
反正買了這麼多，但我可能買了幾個... ...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ostv/i_work_overnight_and_because_of_my_schedule_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m2ostv/i_work_overnight_and_because_of_my_schedule_i/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:47:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I put in a limit order for RBLX and when I woke up around 5 pm saw my order was never filled because the price shot up right away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t the first time I&amp;#39;ve missed a buying opportunity. I probably wouldn&amp;#39;t have bought the same amount this high anyway but I may have bought a few shares if I was awake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is anyone else in my situation? And how would you proceed without seeing the active market when you&amp;#39;re sleeping?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to set another limit order before bed in a half hour but I&amp;#39;m debating on whether or not it&amp;#39;s worth it at this price. Not looking for specific advice on buying this particular stock. I&amp;#39;m more or less wondering how you would handle buying shares when you&amp;#39;re sleeping. Probably sounds like an obvious question to some but I&amp;#39;m about 6 months into this now and I&amp;#39;m still learning a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>