<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 10:59:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[在這裏經常被推薦的、你不喜歡的書是什麼？還有一本你從未想過自己會喜歡的書，但最後卻喜歡上了它？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有一個正在進行的書單，我在這裏經常看到有人推薦，因爲我想把它們都讀完。
因爲我想把它們都讀完，而且很多書都很好！但遺憾的是，我正在讀瑪德琳-米勒的《Circe》，但我就是讀不進去

但不幸的是，我正在讀瑪德琳-米勒的《Circe》，我就是無法進入這本書！我已經讀了一半多，但我就是沒有感覺到聯繫，也不知道該怎麼辦。
我已經讀完了一半以上的書，但我就是感覺不到有什麼聯繫，也不知道該怎麼辦。
被吸引了，這...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o83ulz/what_is_a_book_that_is_frequently_suggested_here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o83ulz/what_is_a_book_that_is_frequently_suggested_here/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:52:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have an ongoing list of books I see suggested here a lot because I want to read them all, and so many have been great! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But sadly, I am reading “Circe” by Madeline Miller and I just can’t get into it! I have gotten through over half the book and I just don’t feel connected or captivated, which makes me sad because I know so many people swear by this book and it has great feminine energy which I like, I just don’t find myself really thinking about it beyond the times I am reading, and I never feel “engrossed”. I am disappointed in myself for this one, I’m sorry guys, I know it’s a great story. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has this happened to any of y’all? What is something you thought you’d love and ended up not? Also, what is a book you didn’t think you’d enjoy but you did?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛剛讀完《人鼠之間》!]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是第一本我真正喜歡的小說之一（另一本是《像房子一樣安全》）。
as Houses）。)

書中的人物給人以真實的感覺，文字的描述也令人難以置信。
你很容易迷失在其中，因爲你可以很容易地在腦海中構建每個環境和人物的每一個方面。
每一個環境和人物都在你的腦海裏。你...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7zg9h/just_finished_of_mice_and_men/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7zg9h/just_finished_of_mice_and_men/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:55:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was one of the first novels I’ve ever actually liked (the other one is Safe as Houses).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The characters all feel so real and the writing is so incredibly descriptive. It’s so easy to get lost in it since you can easily construct every last aspect of every setting and person in your head. You can understand precisely what the characters do and exactly why they do it, this is quite possibly the greatest thing I’ve ever read&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傻瓜的聯盟》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[先生們，我剛剛讀完這本書。這是一本精彩的讀物。我完全
我非常喜歡伊格內修斯的世界觀，他想發動一場革命，瑞麗夫人的轉變，聖誕老人不在乎的態度，曼庫索的無助，瓊斯的無助。
變化，聖誕老人不在乎的態度，曼庫索的無助，瓊斯的
瓊斯想造成破壞，達琳的天真無邪，拉娜的態度......。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7kfji/a_confederacy_of_dunces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7kfji/a_confederacy_of_dunces/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:16:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sirs,
I just finished reading the book. It was a wonderful read. I thoroughly enjoyed Ignatius’s worldview, his wanting to start a revolution, Mrs Reily’s transformation, Santa’s don’t care attitude, Mancuso’s helplessness, Jones’s wanting to cause a sabotage, Darlene’s innocence, Lana’s attitude, Mr and Mrs Levy’s drama and so on.
This book has stood the test of time and has become a classic. 
How is it relevant in this generation/society?
Are there any other viewpoints from which the book should be viewed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,
Your Working Boy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完《東方快車謀殺案》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道該說什麼，我懷疑他們都是一夥的，在大揭祕之前的幾頁就已經有了。
我懷疑他們都參與其中，在大揭祕之前的幾頁。我想也許M.Bouc也會參與其中，並組織了
作爲火車的經理，我沒有看到任何事情發生。

懷疑這是一起集體謀殺案，只是因爲波洛纔有可能......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t87l/i_just_finished_the_murder_on_the_orient_express/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t87l/i_just_finished_the_murder_on_the_orient_express/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 05:19:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know what to say, I suspected that they were all in on it, pages before the big reveal. I thought maybe M.bouc would have been in on it and organized being the manager of the train but I didn&amp;#39;t see anything coming. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;suspecting that it was a group murder was only possible due to Poirot feeding us the information in the third act. I love being surprised by mystery stories and hate completely obvious ones, this is a reason that keeps me coming back to Agatha christie&amp;#39;s books. I completely ruled out Mrs. Hubbard as a suspect, but my jaw dropped when I found out, I guess you should not rule out the most unlikely suspect in an Agatha Christie novel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would keep reading a bad story for the characters but a good story without characters I find interesting or I&amp;#39;m attached to is a story I wouldn&amp;#39;t be invested in. luckily this book had the best of both worlds, great characters and a wonderful plot and mystery that I did not grow tired of. I liked other stories of christie&amp;#39;s like five little pigs and the amazing murder of roger Ackroyd but I was not attached to the characters and found the characters of the former book rather tedious. here christie balanced a large cast in a short book and kept them interesting enough in their short interviews and I have to say I appreciated the little map of the train that I went back to every once and a while to capture the setting of the train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story was amazing, I had a feeling I would love it and I&amp;#39;m glad I didn&amp;#39;t watch the movie. The fact that they all agreed to look the other way for a justified murder was also a great end. This one is one of my favorite Agatha christie books so far. next to read is and then there were none.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在過去的十年中，是否有任何巨大的打擊？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好!

在過去的十年裏，圖書行業是否有任何巨大的衝擊（如哈利波特的規模）？
過去的十年裏，有什麼巨大的成功嗎？我說的不是後來流行起來的書，例如
我說的是那些一經發行就大受歡迎的書。
發佈。

這個問題來自於觀看《神祕的世界》（The Mystery of...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7v50n/has_there_been_any_huge_hit_in_the_past_decade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7v50n/has_there_been_any_huge_hit_in_the_past_decade/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello !  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has there been any huge hit (like Harry Potter scale) in the book industry the past decade ? I&amp;#39;m not talking about books that got popular afterwards such as the GoT books, I&amp;#39;m talking about books that got insanely popular right from release. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This quesion rose from watching &amp;quot;the mystery of Henri Pick&amp;quot; with my girlfriend and it got us thinking about the popularity of books nowadays. We do read books but we do not follow the news of the litterature world at all, we are clueless about the new releases or rising authors and such.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can&amp;#39;-t really think about any book in the past decade that got so popular that EVERYONE heard about it and got many people to read it. We thought of Twilight and 50 shades but we feel like they&amp;#39;re actually quite niche and too controversial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[青春期書籍中主角的誇大才能]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道是我的原因還是我讀的書的原因，但我發現越來越多的
我發現主角（或至少是我們被設計爲支持的主要人物）越來越常見。
我發現主角（或至少是我們要支持的主角）擁有誇張的才能。

我的意思是，幾乎每個主人公都同時擁有一系列的天賦。
這些天賦包括...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7o856/the_inflated_talents_of_protagonists_in_ya_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7o856/the_inflated_talents_of_protagonists_in_ya_books/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if it’s just me or the books I am reading but I am finding it more common place for protagonists (or at least main characters we are designed to root for) to posses inflated talents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean is, almost every protagonist has an array of gifts all at once. These talents consist of things such as being brilliant at music, well read, gifted at art, extremely athletic, potential world leading scientist, scholarship offers…all snowballed into one character. This is not to say these characters cannot exist or impossible to believe but I often feel that in stories in which, for example; That because the protagonist is unhappy or depressed that the reader is expected to feel more sad because of what is implied by their potential. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not to say, that books that use characters such as these are overall poorly written - but come across quite bland and copy and paste. Or perhaps it is me…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just curious to see if anyone else felt the same?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[似乎不能像我年輕時那樣超級沉迷於書籍，這很糟糕。]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我還是個孩子的時候，進入書中--並停留在那裏--似乎很容易。
超級容易。這方面最好的例子，不僅僅是對我，對很多人來說都是如此。
人來說，最好的例子是《哈利-波特》。如果我手裏有一本新的《哈利-波特》，我就必須要看完。
就必須在當天讀完它，睡覺也不例外，而世界......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7org9/cant_seem_to_get_super_engrossed_in_books_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7org9/cant_seem_to_get_super_engrossed_in_books_like/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 22:00:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back when I was still a kid, getting into a book - and staying there - seemed super easy. Probably the best example of this, not just for me but for a lot of people, was Harry Potter. If I got a new Harry Potter in my hands I just had to finish it that same day, sleeping be damned, and the world would stay with me for weeks after finishing it. It was the kind of story where you just felt compelled to go online and find communities to keep discussing it over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve tried to re-create this feeling since that time and I&amp;#39;ve never really found it. The closest was probably Game of Thrones/Song of Ice and Fire in terms of recreating this magical need for more information and discussion but otherwise, nothing much. I actually just put a bookmark at a Dresden book about ~50 pages from the ending and while I&amp;#39;ll obviously still finish the book, I have 0 urgency to do it. I&amp;#39;ve also tried reading Rowling&amp;#39;s other books as Robert Galbraith, wondering if it was her writing style that did it but the book was just nowhere near as engaging as any of her previous work. I just really want that super excitement at picking up a new book and I&amp;#39;m just not finding it, which makes me way less excited to read in general (and I hate it!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;m wondering, do you guys still regularly get deeply invested in the books you read? Do you think we feel that way less as we get older? Do some authors or genres inspire this more than others? What are your thoughts and experiences?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當我閱讀時，我假裝自己是一個電影製片人，當我閱讀時，我想象 "我的電影 "的每個 "場景 "會是什麼樣子。這很傻很有趣，但它使文學作品變得更令人興奮]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想這是一個衆所周知的普遍現象，但我最近才意識到這一點
而我一直是個貪婪的讀者! 在此之前，我一直都是那種
"我必須專注於每一個字，而不是其他，否則我就會迷路 "的那種孩子。I
我的腦子裏不能有其他事情發生，除了......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t048/when_i_read_i_pretend_i_am_a_filmmaker_and_as_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7t048/when_i_read_i_pretend_i_am_a_filmmaker_and_as_i/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 21:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I assume this is a well known common thing but it only clicked with me recently and I have been a voracious reader! Before then, I&amp;#39;ve always been one of those &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;I must focus on each word and nothing else or I will get lost&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; kind of kid. I could not afford anything else happening in my head other than my own voice saying the words or else I&amp;#39;d lose track of what would be happening. But now, I have aquired this...hmm... would &amp;#39;Skill&amp;#39;? be too pretentious a word? I don&amp;#39;t know but it feels like I&amp;#39;ve gone to the next level of reading! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it all started with the Grapes of Wrath which I finished a few days ago. Everytime I opened the book, the &amp;quot;movie&amp;quot; would start playing and it was so consistent and concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GOP felt like an entire film playing in my head. From page one to the last. I guess, with practice, I was able to envision how character would look, how they would sound, what the lighting of each scene would like, the location, the &amp;quot;close up shots&amp;quot; of certatain conversations and monologues and what music would be playing. All this as I read. It was..sooo...goddamn enjoyable!! I have have felt so immersed before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also just finished the Raymond Carver short story - &amp;#39;Preservation&amp;#39; only minutes ago! And duuuude lol, It took me like 15 minutes to finish but it felt like a proper short film was happening right there in my head! I envisioned what the house looked like, their accents, their facial expressions, and of course the music!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I want to go back and re-read all my favourite books! I feel so happy right now lol. I&amp;#39;ve always loved reading but now it feels like I&amp;#39;ve aquired this next level love everyone is always talking about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[書籍是否讓你活着？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我今天和一個朋友談起從考試壓力中抽身出來閱讀一些有趣的書。
他的回答是 "噗......真是個書呆子！"。
這是通常的反應，我通常不會真的去想它。但現在我開始
思考--我沒有什麼社交生活，也沒有持久的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mi9j/are_books_keeping_you_alive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mi9j/are_books_keeping_you_alive/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:52:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was talking to a friend today about taking a break from exam stress to read some interesting books, and his reply was &amp;quot;pfftt..what a nerd!&amp;quot;, which is the usual response and I don&amp;#39;t really think about it usually. But now I started thinking- I don&amp;#39;t have much of a social life, nor do I have lasting friendships. College is still underway, so I am not making strides in my career. Essentially, I don&amp;#39;t have any billionaire-ish achievements in my kitty. I could but don&amp;#39;t want to club/party and so I am content at home. But I do wake up everyday with the goal of completing all my other work till a predetermined time and finally get on with my book (s). Do you, like me, also feel this way? If you do, is it healthy to have this sort of a dependence (the friend in question told me, I think playfully, that I shouldn&amp;#39;t be dependent on anything for my happiness)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please just tell me I am not alone. This is not like a phase for me. It is really a therapeutic activity-reading. I feel the happiest when books surround me and I need to be engaged in the task to feel like I did something with my day. I mean I will get on with other things in life too, but I don&amp;#39;t know whether as an old person, I&amp;#39;ll be very different or adventurous or doing exciting things. I&amp;#39;m happy and content where I am- cozy in my reading nook :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BookTok的崛起：認識那些將書籍推上排行榜的青少年影響者]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mwhi/the_rise_of_booktok_meet_the_teen_influencers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7mwhi/the_rise_of_booktok_meet_the_teen_influencers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:46:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所以，我剛剛發現了P.G. Wodehouse。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在這個網站上隨機看到一個關於幽默書的帖子，其中提到了P.G.
Wodehouse的Bertie and Jeeves系列出現了。

我想我已經很多年沒有在一本書上笑得這麼開心了！（《伍斯特的密碼》）。(The Code of the Woosters)
(The Code of the Woosters)必須是最有趣的關於奶牛擠奶器的書......可能是唯一的一本。
可能是唯一的一本，但重點是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7miic/so_i_just_discovered_pg_wodehouse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7miic/so_i_just_discovered_pg_wodehouse/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:20:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across a random post on this sub regarding humorous books and P.G. Wodehouse&amp;#39;s Bertie and Jeeves series came up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think I laughed so much at a book in years! (The Code of the Woosters) had to be the funniest book about a cow-creamer out there... probably the only one but the point stands!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Right Ho, Jeeves) has a public speaking scene that... I&amp;#39;m sorry but if you don&amp;#39;t start chuckling at the start of it then something is wrong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me this was a very pleasant surprise. I wasn&amp;#39;t expecting much out of a series published 100 years back. So tell me, what book surprised you? A book you weren&amp;#39;t expecting to like but was forced by the author to change your mind?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想感謝這個子!]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，一開始我就需要誠實地提到，直到今年3月，我已經15年沒有讀過小說了。
直到今年3月，我已經有15年沒有讀過小說了。在禁閉期間，有些事情發生了變化，我內心燃起了改變的火花。
鎖定期間發生了一些變化，我內心燃起了改變的火花，所以我成爲了這個
分論壇。我需要感謝所有貢獻和發佈的人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7kejq/i_want_to_thank_this_sub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7kejq/i_want_to_thank_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:33:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, right off the bat I need to be honest and mention that I had not read a novel in 15 years until March of this year. Something changed during the lockdown and a spark ignited within me for change so I became a member of this subreddit. I need to thank all the people who contributed and posted their book suggestions making me click the save button so many times. Since joining this subreddit I have purchased and completed book number nine since March. I currently have a massive list of books I need still need to purchase, read, and eventually add to my new bookshelf. Thank you all for helping me focus on reading and making me splurge on a fancy new wood bookmark!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛讀了《鍊金術士》...]]></title><description><![CDATA[而且我很生氣。我甚至無法用語言來表達我有多討厭那種
嬰兒第一哲學的廢話。爲什麼每個人都這麼喜歡這本書？誰能給我解釋一下
誰能給我解釋一下，我應該從這個經歷中得到什麼？
我是不是太傻了，不能 "理解"？它是如此......基本。如此的表面水平....]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7iht5/i_just_read_the_alchemist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7iht5/i_just_read_the_alchemist/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 09:27:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;and I&amp;#39;m livid. I can&amp;#39;t even express in words how much I hated that baby&amp;#39;s-first-philosophy BS. Why does everyone love this book so much? Can somebody please explain to me what I was supposed to get out of this experience? Am I just too stupid to &amp;quot;get it?&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s so... basic. So surface level. What&amp;#39;s there to get?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[玩火的女孩》和《踢馬蜂窩的女孩》值得在觀看《龍紋身的女孩》這部電影后閱讀嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看了大衛-芬奇的那部!

我能夠理解這兩部作品嗎？或者我應該把這3本書都讀完。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7eapz/is_the_girl_who_played_with_fire_and_the_girl_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o7eapz/is_the_girl_who_played_with_fire_and_the_girl_who/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:26:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I watched David Fincher&amp;#39;s one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I be able to understand both of them?
Or should I read all the 3 books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不難讀的經典之作]]></title><description><![CDATA[我腦子太小，無法吸收很多必讀的經典，但我真的想讀一些。
但我真的想讀一些。有什麼建議嗎？

編輯：謝謝你到目前爲止的建議！！補充一下，我非常喜歡的一些類型是
小說、歷史小說、幻想、驚悚片、好的懸疑片，以及任何能得到這些東西的東西。
引起這個問題......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o74wdv/classics_that_arent_too_difficult_to_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o74wdv/classics_that_arent_too_difficult_to_read/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:26:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;pls i am too small brained to absorb a lot of the must read classics but i really wanna get into reading some. any suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: thanks for the suggestions so far!! to add, some genres i really like are fiction, historical fiction, fantasy, thriller, a good mystery, and anything that gets this small brain thinking about its life for days after finishing a book. i also do not mind books that’ll make me sob :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次閱讀莎士比亞的作品。這是一個完整的體驗，現在是一個新的愛好!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我今年21歲，以前從未讀過莎士比亞，直到最近三四天。我
在過去的幾天裏，我一直在閱讀和研究莎士比亞的人物和故事。
故事。

我的書架上有兩本他的作品，是在一次拍賣會上買的，我從最薄的那本開始讀起。
最薄的一本。它是《如你所願》，是一本快速的2-3頁的書。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7f06f/read_shakespeares_work_for_the_first_time_it_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7f06f/read_shakespeares_work_for_the_first_time_it_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 05:15:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am 21 and I have never read Shakespeare before untill the last 3-4 days. I had spent last days just reading and studying about Shakespeare&amp;#39;s characters and stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had 2 of his work in my shelf bought at a sale, I started off with the thinnest one. It was As you like it, It was a quick 2-3 hour read but then I started to analyze all these dialogues and plot. I thought it was very funny and amazingly sarcastic on the tone. Rosalind is a great character, and so is Touchstone. If I am not mistaken As you like it is a metaphor about how life simply has no greater meaning, it&amp;#39;s ephemeral at best. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next I read A Midsummer Night&amp;#39;s Dream,  another comedy this at times did remind me of As you like it, I could see a similar notion about an entire different progression of story. I think out of two that I&amp;#39;ve read I see love is a theme he uses constantly,  and also comments on what makes people fall in love generally beauty and appearance. There was more of a romantic input on this story then the other one which was more playful. I really liked the play within the play. 
- Also, I think I can see Puck being close friends with Touchstone, not going to lie. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I will spend rest of my life reading and studying more and more about his work. I have found more of his book at a local bookstore.  And I have found Othello and Macbeth which I am going to read next.  I think Shakespeare is the foundation of many stories I have seen in my life before in various Tv shows and movies. It takes time but it totally worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[翻開大流行病的一頁。紐約市圖書館將重新開放]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7ddcl/turning_the_page_on_the_pandemic_nyc_libraries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7ddcl/turning_the_page_on_the_pandemic_nyc_libraries/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 02:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完卡勒德-侯賽尼的《千秋萬代》，說實話.....，那是什麼東西？]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我看完這本書的一半時，我忍不住想在互聯網上爲自己掃掃興
在互聯網上爲自己劇透。這本書實在是太引人注目了。老實說，它是我讀過的最好的--甚至是最好的--書之一。
它是我讀過的最好的--甚至是最好的--書之一。我覺得自己很無知，不知道
知道阿富汗的情況有多嚴重。而這兩個...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7bvpi/i_just_finished_read_a_thousand_splendid_suns_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o7bvpi/i_just_finished_read_a_thousand_splendid_suns_by/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 02:12:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was halfway through the book, I couldn&amp;#39;t resist the urge to spoil it for myself on the internet. The book&amp;#39;s just so compelling. Its honestly one of the best - maybe even the best - books I&amp;#39;ve ever read. I feel so ignorant about not knowing how severe Afghanistan&amp;#39;s situation is. And the two main characters are portrayed perfectly. Everything&amp;#39;s perfect about this book. My only &amp;quot;problem&amp;quot; with it was that it was so depressing. No seriously, it was so very depressing and sad and not like the other books I&amp;#39;ve read. No it was sad on a whole other level I never even knew existed. I&amp;#39;m still trying to process everything I read and I&amp;#39;m rambling and I dont think what I&amp;#39;m saying makes any sense but whatever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所以，我討厭《哈利波特與死亡聖器》的結局]]></title><description><![CDATA[(可能的破壞者)

我最近讀完了（第一次）所有的《哈利-波特》書籍，並且
我真的很討厭最後的結局。它看起來如此倉促，而且沒有詳細說明
主要人物的死亡對他們之後的生活有何影響。對我來說，結尾似乎是 "哦，我們贏了，我們贏了"。
結局似乎是 "哦，我們贏了，現在......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o784bj/so_i_hated_the_ending_of_harry_potter_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o784bj/so_i_hated_the_ending_of_harry_potter_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 01:15:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(possible spoilers) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading (for the first time) all the Harry Potter books, and I really hated the very end. It seemed so rushed and it didn&amp;#39;t go into detail on how the deaths of major characters impacted their lives afterwards. 
To me, the ending seemed like &amp;#39;oh we won, now let&amp;#39;s skip to nineteen years later.&amp;#39; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please tell me other people were disappointed with the ending of the books!? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;ve still never seen The deathly hallows part two movie)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[根據書的質量和敘述者，最喜歡的有聲書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在取消我的賬戶之前，我有8個Audible圖書積分可以使用。
我想在7月1日我的下一個信用額度出現之前使用。因此，我需要儘快挑選8本書。
我發現一些好書被糟糕的解說員毀掉了，而一些平庸的書
有了合適的人才，就會大放異彩。你認爲什麼是最好的書？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o71jcj/favorite_audiobooks_based_on_both_book_quality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o71jcj/favorite_audiobooks_based_on_both_book_quality/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have 8 Audible book credits to use before canceling my account, which I would like to do before my next credit hits on 7/1. So, I need to pick 8 books ASAP. I’ve found some great books are ruined by a bad narrator, and some mediocre ones shine with the right talent. What are the best books you have listened to, based on both the quality of the book AND the narrator? I’m more interested in fiction, any genre. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[祝屋大維婭-巴特勒生日快樂!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想提請大家注意，屋大維婭-巴特勒的生日是
本週早些時候。她是一位文學和科幻界的遠見卓識者和開拓者。她
她是第一個（我想也是唯一一個）獲得麥克阿瑟天才獎的科幻小說作家。
天才獎。她的作品和在該流派中的代表作幫助她的作品在世界範圍內得到了認可。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o70knn/happy_birthday_to_octavia_butler/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o70knn/happy_birthday_to_octavia_butler/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 15:51:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to bring attention to the fact that  Octavia Butler&amp;#39;s birthday was earlier this week. She was a literary and sci fi visionary and trailblazer. She was the first (and I think only) science fiction author to recurve the MacArthur Genius grant.  Her work and representation in the genre helped to create the foundation for many of the fantastic new voices we have had the opportunity to enjoy in spec fiction, especially over the last decade. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started Parable of the Sower recently. The world is captivating, main character is strong, and themes are focused. I&amp;#39;m very much enjoying my first foray into Butler and plan to check out more of her work. I&amp;#39;ve now started the second book in the series and her ability to see the future we were heading towards is eerie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I highly encourage fans of her work and novices alike to pick up one of her books or short stories to experience her work and celebrate her contributions to literature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;There&amp;#39;s nothing new under the sun, but there are new suns.&amp;quot; - Octavia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是什麼讓阿加莎-克里斯蒂的書如此偉大？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我昨天下午開始讀《東方快車謀殺案》，只是感覺到
被迫讀到了晚上。

今天早上，我很驚訝。不僅很久沒有一本書讓我睡不着覺了
我最近讀的書也沒有像克里斯蒂的《東方快車謀殺案》那樣讓我喫驚或發笑。
克里斯蒂的偉大故事....]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6z9r4/what_makes_agatha_christies_books_so_great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6z9r4/what_makes_agatha_christies_books_so_great/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 13:44:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started to read &lt;em&gt;Murder on the Orient Express&lt;/em&gt; yesterday afternoon and just felt compelled to read through well into the night. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning, I was surprised. Not only had it been a long time since a book kept me up, my latest reads had not surprised me or made me laugh like Christie&amp;#39;s great story. This is not my first Christie, but I am surprised to have almost forgotten how this lady&amp;#39;s pen can snatch you out of everyday life for a moment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering what others like about Christie&amp;#39;s books, what they feel when reading them. If you care to share your experience that would be great !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, I think it narrows down to the simplicity of it all at the end... Although at first glance Christie&amp;#39;s murder mysteries seem complicated, they are supported by many simple facts of everyday life... Like nicknames can be misleading about gender, narrators aren&amp;#39;t always reliable, truth can be found behind some strong emotional reactions...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在讀Catch-22。這一段我看不懂......誰能幫忙解釋一下？]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是第一章的內容，也是我對這本書的第二次嘗試。上一次
我試圖閱讀，我不明白這一段，它使我放棄了閱讀
這讓我對這本書的其他部分產生了懷疑。段落在下面。

"上校在通信部門，他日夜忙碌着
發送......"。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6zf61/reading_catch22_this_paragraph_is_indecipherable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6zf61/reading_catch22_this_paragraph_is_indecipherable/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is from the first chapter and my second attempt at the book. The last time I tried reading, I didn’t understand this paragraph and it put me off reading the rest of the book for some reason. Paragraph is below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The colonel was in Communications, and he was kept busy day and night transmitting glutinous messages from the interior into square pads of gauze which he sealed meticulously and delivered to a covered white pail that stood on the night table beside his bed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亞的大部分文學遺產都已絕版。拯救國家失落書籍的鬥爭]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6v4ct/most_of_australias_literary_heritage_is_out_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6v4ct/most_of_australias_literary_heritage_is_out_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 11:58:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[指環王》雜誌]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道這是一個不受歡迎的觀點，但我剛剛讀完《指環王》的前兩部。
指環王》的前兩部書，這是一個罕見的情況，我喜歡電影，而不是原著。
電影比原著更受歡迎。

在小說中，我只是從未感受到人物所面臨的真正的絕望和壓倒性的困難
角色所面臨的真正的絕望和壓倒性的困難。這部電影是我最喜歡的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6qgth/lord_of_the_rings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6qgth/lord_of_the_rings/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 08:41:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know it is an unpopular opinion but I just finished the first two Lord of the Rings books and it has been one of those rare instances where I enjoyed the movies way more than the source books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the novels I just never felt the true desperation and overwhelming odds facing the characters. The book just felt more of a historical text; like reading a textbook vs watching an immersive documentary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some books where I can separate the text from the movie, especially when there is great divergence between the story  (King vs Kubrick&amp;#39;s The Shining) but the LotR movies are fairly faithful adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure I would have liked to see a bit of Tom Bombadil but I think the trade-offs with the movie interpretation are well worth it. One example: when Gandalf frees Theoden from the influence of Wormtongue - in the novels was a bit underwhelming, kind of like... hey, come get a few breaths of fresh air and a Snickers, you good boss? Look at the blue sky  (and his wrinkles smoothed. The end.) VS the movie interpretation when we can see the drastic  driving out of Sarumon&amp;#39;s influence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a hot take here and I&amp;#39;m not looking to change anyone&amp;#39;s opinion or try to take away from Tolkien&amp;#39;s masterpiece, I&amp;#39;m just surprised with myself that this has been my takeaway through the first two books and wanted to know your take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼書中的人名或地名用"-: "代替？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近在很多很多年後再次開始閱讀。目前我已經讀了
基督山伯爵》和《弗蘭肯斯坦》（均來自古騰堡項目）。
然後我目前正在讀芬蘭語的《傲慢與偏見》。我認爲在所有這些
這些書中，都有一些地名或人名......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6m2b1/why_are_names_or_some_persons_or_places_in_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6m2b1/why_are_names_or_some_persons_or_places_in_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 05:57:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently started reading again after many many years. I&amp;#39;ve currently read the Count of Monte Cristo and Frankenstein in English (both from project Gutenberg) and then I&amp;#39;m currently reading Pride and Prejudice in Finnish. I think in all of these books, there has been some names of places or persons that are replaced with &amp;quot;–:&amp;quot;. Example could be something like &amp;quot;They went to visit the McCoys in –:&amp;quot;. Why are some names hidden like this? I tried to Google but could not find any good search terms to find info. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有誰知道有什麼好的科幻和/或歇斯底里的書能讓你反思人生？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想要一本真正讓你思考生命/人類的書，有科幻的
因爲這些東西很酷。
感到非常空虛的書，並且在我看完之後還能在我腦海中停留很久。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6p9if/anyone_know_any_good_scifi_andor_dystopian_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6p9if/anyone_know_any_good_scifi_andor_dystopian_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 04:57:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i want a book that really makes u think about life/humanity that has sci-fi themes because that stuff is cool. im also looking for a book that will leave me feeling very empty when i finish it and be stuck on my mind long after i finish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[五代人的閱讀習慣[信息圖] 。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6g4qy/the_reading_habits_of_five_generations_infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6g4qy/the_reading_habits_of_five_generations_infographic/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 21:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你讀了什麼並喜歡上了它，因爲它是在這個子上推薦給你的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我幾乎每天都來這裏 -- 我有時會想，如果我們很多人都接受了我們彼此提供的建議
建議，以及這些建議對讀者的作用如何。
所以，告訴我們......你有哪些超級書籍，有哪些偉大的閱讀體驗？
因爲本子上有人推薦？是什麼書或...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6e7xy/what_did_you_read_and_love_because_it_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o6e7xy/what_did_you_read_and_love_because_it_was/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 20:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I come here almost every day -- and I sometimes wonder if lots of us take the suggestions we all offer one another, and how they work out for the readers -- so, tell us... what super books, what great reading experiences did you have because someone on this sub suggested it? What was the book or author you are grateful this sub introduced you to? Pass it on so others can know your reading joys and share in your favorite read from a recommendation. I figure if you loved it, maybe I will, too! I&amp;#39;m always looking for something new and great!   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll start with an author I had never considered, but was suggested to me on a thread I started a while back about gritty rural fiction. Someone suggested Michael Farris Smith&amp;#39;s Blackwood -- and I absolutely loved it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想要英雄"。科大教授Devon Mihesuah撰寫了第二本以美國本土偵探爲主角的小說]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6ctl8/i_want_heroes_ku_professor_devon_mihesuah_pens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6ctl8/i_want_heroes_ku_professor_devon_mihesuah_pens/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 19:42:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[殺死一隻知更鳥》是一部非常精巧的文學作品]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天剛剛完成，我花了15天時間，但最後我可以驕傲地說
它值得所有的時間和關注；它是這樣一個傑作。

英語是我的第二語言，我必須承認，對我來說，這是一本難讀的書。
然而，我很喜歡它。作者在書中描繪了 "我 "與 "我 "之間的關係。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o68eyi/to_kill_a_mockingbird_is_very_well_crafted_piece/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o68eyi/to_kill_a_mockingbird_is_very_well_crafted_piece/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 17:44:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Completed just yesterday, took me 15 days but at the end I can say it proudly that it deserve all the time and attention; it&amp;#39;s such a masterpiece. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;English being my second language, I must admit that it was a hard read for me, nevertheless I enjoyed it. The way in which the author paints the incidents in the mind of the reader is so profound and indelible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from the writing style I loved the characters too, especially Atticus, his way of parenting is commendable. Also, the bonding between Scout and Jem is very warming, seemed to me like they are the epitome of the saying &amp;#39;made for each other&amp;#39; .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Americans are lucky to have it in their curriculum, like I had Gulliver&amp;#39;s Travel which I barely enjoyed myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[必要的有趣的書。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我想要一本讀起來很有趣的書。我剛剛悟出一個道理
我一生中大部分時間都在讀那些獲得好評的書。
那些 "必讀 "的書，以及那些我想說我讀過的書。I
從那時起，我意識到，我只想享受閱讀，而我...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o69u95/essential_fun_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o69u95/essential_fun_books/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, I want a book that’s fun to read. I have just come to a realization that I’ve spent most of my life reading books that have received critical acclaim, books that are “must reads” and books that I wanted to be able to say I read. I have since realized that I just want to enjoy reading, and I’m really not feeling academic right now. What are the first books that come to mind that just scream a great time. Can be anything I am not really pigeon holed into a certain genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪些書讓你大喫一驚，讓你質疑另一個人怎麼可能想出這些想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[例如，我正在閱讀金-斯坦利-羅賓遜的火星三部曲，我對他所掌握的科學知識感到敬畏。
我對他所擁有的大量科學知識感到敬畏。物理學、化學和生物學知識
知識，以令人信服的方式講述火星地球化的故事，並使其
顯得如此可信，沒有任何莫名其妙的技術廢話......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o62xvt/what_books_blew_you_away_that_they_made_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o62xvt/what_books_blew_you_away_that_they_made_you/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, I&amp;#39;m reading through Kim Stanley Robinson&amp;#39;s Mars trilogy and I am in awe of how much scientific knowledge he has. The physics, chemistry, and biology knowledge to convincingly tell the story of the terraforming of Mars and make it seem so believable without any inexplicable technobabble is beyond my mind, and he&amp;#39;s done this in several of his other books too. Even more mainstream historical fiction novels like those of Bernard Cornwell, while excellent for what they are (fun, swashbuckling, hero adventures) I still can&amp;#39;t imagine knowing all the small details that go into period specific writing, even when it&amp;#39;s just formulaic fun books. Like I don&amp;#39;t know anything about Napoleonic clothing, travel, weaponry, the common sentiments people had, horses/livestock, the age of sail... so much detail. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What books rocked your perception like that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有聲讀物毀了我]]></title><description><![CDATA[它開始於禁閉期間。無論我是在打掃衛生、鍛鍊身體，還是蜷縮在牀下的
我都可能在聽一個精彩的故事。
由一個了不起的配音演員講述的精彩故事。從那時起，我的牀頭書堆就越來越多。
因此，我終於拿起了《刀鋒戰士》，雖然我真的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o616p2/audiobooks_have_ruined_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o616p2/audiobooks_have_ruined_me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:28:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It started during lockdown. Whether I was cleaning, exercising, or curled up in the fetal position under my bed, I could be listening to a wonderful story, narrated by an amazing voice actor. Since then my bedside book stack has grown, so I finally picked up The Blade Itself and, while I’m really enjoying it, I’m also struggling. It’s harder to become immersed in the story, and I keep wanting to hear someone read it to me whenever I’m doing something that occupies my body but not my mind. I’m sure I’ll get back into the flow of it soon enough, but it is a strange feeling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[節目《好預兆》是對該書的一個該死的良好表現。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看完書後，剛看完這個系列，劇中遺漏的一切都被彌補了。
彌補了這些缺憾，大衛-坦南特和邁克爾-希恩的表演也很精彩。
和邁克爾-辛的精彩表演。我通常對改編的電影持懷疑態度，但我覺得
但我覺得我可以很容易地把它傳給沒有讀過這本書的人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6c8um/the_show_good_omens_is_a_damn_fine_representation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6c8um/the_show_good_omens_is_a_damn_fine_representation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:15:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just finished the series after reading the book, everything the show left out it made up for with tasteful additions and an amazing performance by David Tennant and Michael Sheen. I&amp;#39;m usually skeptical of movie adaptations, but I feel like I could easily pass this off to someone who hasn&amp;#39;t read the book and feel like they&amp;#39;re missing out on only small details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[愛爾蘭神話]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在尋找一本關於愛爾蘭神話的書，它能像尼爾-蓋曼的《北歐神話》一樣容易理解。
神話》一樣容易理解。也許能把四個週期的內容細分爲
詳細的書。歡迎任何建議。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o63moe/irish_mythology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o63moe/irish_mythology/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 13:24:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am looking for a book about Irish Mythology that is as accessible as &amp;quot;Norse Mythology&amp;quot; by Neil Gaiman. Maybe something that breaks down the four cycles into detail. Any suggestions are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[虛假的社交媒體的憤怒正在使作者改變他們書中的臺詞。認爲一個虛構人物的言論反映了作者的實際信仰的愚蠢想法正在蔓延。]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6b6rr/bogus_social_media_outrage_is_making_authors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o6b6rr/bogus_social_media_outrage_is_making_authors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 12:59:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[皮拉內西之後]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年年初，我收到了皮拉內西的生日禮物，對它一無所知。
這本書讓我大喫一驚。我現在看到它在這個子上被推薦，它總是得到
很多人的喜愛。所以我的問題是，對於那些喜歡皮拉內西的人來說，還有什麼是你今年排名前三的？
在你今年的前三名名單上？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o60zhs/after_piranesi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o60zhs/after_piranesi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 04:52:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I received Piranesi for my birthday earlier this year and knew nothing about it. This book blew me away. I now see it recommended on this sub and it always gets lots of love. So my question is, for those of you who loved Piranesi, what else has been on your top three list this year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對90歲老人的建議，拒絕音頻和電子書，興趣狹窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要是尋找神祕小說。她認爲任何類型的 "巧合 "小說都很平淡。
在另一端，不能太黑暗/殘酷/性。沒有吸血鬼、超自然現象。
科幻小說，或直接的浪漫主義。1830年以前的歷史題材都不行。她真的
她很喜歡《世界新聞報》，這導致了《埃爾默-凱爾頓》，她也很喜歡這本書。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5xywq/suggestions_for_90_year_old_refuses_audio_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5xywq/suggestions_for_90_year_old_refuses_audio_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 03:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primarily looking for mystery fiction. She finds &amp;quot;cozies&amp;quot; of any stripe insipid. On the other end, can&amp;#39;t be too dark/brutal/sexual. No vampires, paranormal, sci-fi, or straight-up romance. Nothing historical before 1830&amp;#39;s.
She really liked News of the World, which led to Elmer Kelton, which she also liked. She also likes Southern U.S. settings or context, but not a requirement.
She reads 3-4 hours daily, and it&amp;#39;s exhausting to keep up. Loves Grisham (but read everything) &amp;amp; courtroom settings, but knows there&amp;#39;s not all that much of that that doesn&amp;#39;t have dark or brutal 2d story). Spies/Intrigue is ok, but no torture/terrorism.
Any suggestions appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什麼好的關於日本黑社會的非虛構書籍嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[關於他們的歷史、文化、習俗等方面的內容!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5t990/are_there_any_good_nonfiction_books_on_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5t990/are_there_any_good_nonfiction_books_on_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 01:31:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something about their history, their culture, practices, etc!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否曾經讀完一本書，然後當你不得不用谷歌搜索剛纔發生的事情時，感覺有點愚蠢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我讀完了《我想結束一切》，總的來說我認爲這是一本有趣的書。
一本有趣的書，直到我讀到最後。我他媽的根本不知道
結局是想告訴我發生了什麼，以及它對之前發生的故事意味着什麼。
故事中發生的部分意味着什麼。我不得不去谷歌上查找...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5vf6q/do_you_ever_finish_a_book_and_then_feel_kinda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5vf6q/do_you_ever_finish_a_book_and_then_feel_kinda/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:21:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finished reading &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m Thinking of Ending Things&amp;quot; which overall I thought was an interesting book, until I got to the end. I had no fucking clue what the ending was trying to tell me had happened and what it meant for the previous parts of the story that happened. I had to go to Google to figure out what the hell had happened and that alone made me rethink if I can even say I enjoyed the book if after all that I couldn&amp;#39;t even figure out exactly how it ended on my own. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure if I was just having a bad day and my brain decided not to work, if the ending was in fact confusing, or I&amp;#39;m just getting dumber with age. I believe the book was made into a film or movie so I am curious as to how they did it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else read this book or are there books out there where you had to look up the ending to make sure you understood it right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛讀完《動物農場》，想知道哪些象徵意義不是最明顯的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜歡這個諷刺性的寓言故事，喜歡奧威爾通過象徵性手法出色地展示了
奧威爾通過象徵性的手法，出色地展示了壓迫、暴政和宣傳的動態。我覺得它
低調地講述了各地失敗的革命。我特別想知道
我可能錯過了哪些象徵意義，或者也許不是最...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5hps8/just_finished_reading_animal_farm_and_would_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5hps8/just_finished_reading_animal_farm_and_would_like/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I loved this satirical allegory and how Orwell brilliantly demonstrated the dynamics of oppression, tyranny, propaganda through symbolism. I feel like its lowkey just about failed revolutions everywhere. I was, in particular, wondering what symbolisms I might have missed or maybe weren&amp;#39;t the most obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very interested in discussing and knowing the different allegorical symbolisms of certain events other than the apparent representations of political figures, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[太空中的猶太人。關於猶太作家的無名歷史和科幻小說的誕生]]></title><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5px7r/jews_in_space_on_the_unsung_history_of_jewish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5px7r/jews_in_space_on_the_unsung_history_of_jewish/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:17:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你讀過的最有趣的書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你讀過的最有趣的書是什麼？請提供一行情節摘要
不帶破壞性的。謝謝!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5jhje/funniest_book_youve_ever_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5jhje/funniest_book_youve_ever_read/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 18:56:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the funniest book you have read? Please provide a line of plot summary with no spoilers. 
Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[奧斯卡-馬丁內斯（Oscar Martinez）在《野獸》中對薩爾瓦多-美國移民之路的描述，是我讀過的最令人信服和恐怖的書之一。]]></title><description><![CDATA[奧斯卡-馬丁內斯是一位來自薩爾瓦多的獲獎記者，也是 "ELFARO.N "的創始人之一。
elfaro.net的共同創始人，這是薩爾瓦多的一份在線報紙。他是我遇到過的最無畏的非小說記者之一。
我在非虛構作品中遇到過的最無畏的記者之一，他漂亮地捕捉到了以下兩點
這些移民所面臨的可怕條件，同時又...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5q7kn/oscar_martinezs_account_of_the_el_salvadorus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5q7kn/oscar_martinezs_account_of_the_el_salvadorus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 18:31:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oscar Martinez is an award winning journalist from El Salvador and cofounder of elfaro.net, an online newspaper in El Salvador. One of the most intrepid journalists I&amp;#39;ve ever encountered in nonfiction, he beautifully captures both the horrific conditions these migrants face while simultaneously highlighting the perseverance and bravery of the migrants he encounters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pardon my language, but he didn&amp;#39;t half-ass this story. He literally jumps the train (aka &amp;quot;The Beast), riding the same rails that have maimed and killed so many before him. He heads deep into cartel territory to try and capture the fear that they&amp;#39;ve gripped the nation with. He interviews trafficked women to try and bring their story to light. One of his contacts on the journey calls him as he&amp;#39;s captured by the cartel. He encounters corrupt officials and indifferent law enforcement officers. It&amp;#39;s an absolutely harrowing journey that he somehow captures with steadfast determination and grace. Anyone who is at all interested in this subject matter, or even if you&amp;#39;re not, should absolutely read this book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only regret I don&amp;#39;t have is that I don&amp;#39;t speak Spanish and had to read a translated version. Those who do speak the language, I&amp;#39;d recommend reading the original entitled &amp;quot;Los migrantes que no importan&amp;quot; (The Migrants Who Don&amp;#39;t Matter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於神話和故事的書籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好!

我正在尋找有關阿拉伯神話的書籍。我已經讀過 "一千零一夜"，所以如果你們有任何推薦，我將很高興參加。
和一個晚上"，所以如果你有任何推薦，我很樂意看一下。
看一看 :)

我對其他類型的神話也很感興趣--中國、日本或北歐神話。
北歐的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5l1gx/books_about_mythology_and_tales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o5l1gx/books_about_mythology_and_tales/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:16:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi All!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for books about Arabian mythology. I have already read &amp;quot;One thousand and one nights&amp;quot;, so if you have any recommandations, I will be happy to take a look :) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also interested in other kinds of mythologies - Chinese, Japanese or Nordic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼每個人都知道北歐神話或貝奧武夫，卻不知道芬蘭的卡勒瓦拉？好吧，終於有一個以卡勒瓦拉（Tolkien's LOTR和Silmarillion的主要靈感來源）爲背景的系列作品了，我太興奮了！"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這本書叫《熊族的標記》，作者是大衛-施萊弗。這是一本不知名的
我已經在論壇上關注了很久，但我非常興奮
現在它終於發行了。卡勒瓦拉（Kalevala）可以歸功於，至少是
部分歸功於我們今天在幻想中看到的大量原型。在《卡勒瓦拉》中，我們可以看到很多的原型。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5ojwt/why_does_everyone_know_of_norse_mythology_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o5ojwt/why_does_everyone_know_of_norse_mythology_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kalevala can be attributed, at least partially, to a ton of the archetypes we see in fantasy today. In large part, that’s due to the fact it inspired Tolkien and quite a few elements, and even some characters, of the Lord of the Rings come right out of the Kalevala. Despite that, it seems like no one knows about it! I remember reading Beowulf in school TWICE and never even knew about the Finnish epic poems. Is that common everywhere? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well now there’s at least a series set within that mythos. I only know about it from specific forums, but the book is Mark of the Bear Clan by David Schlaefer.  I hope these books make the Kalevala more well known, because I think it’s so underrepresented right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是一本必讀的書--《西遊記》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這本書是世界上我絕對喜歡的書。它的作者是埃倫
拉斯金寫的，她是一位著名的兒童讀物插畫師。她沒有爲這本書打草稿
也沒有書面的基礎設施，但她卻寫出了一個非常相互聯繫和
精緻的故事。該書獲得了1979年紐伯瑞獎。

這本書...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o582r2/this_is_a_must_read_the_westing_game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o582r2/this_is_a_must_read_the_westing_game/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 07:59:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is my absolute favorite book in the world. It was written by Ellen Raskin, a pronounced children&amp;#39;s book illustrator. She did no drafts of the book and no written infrastructure, yet she produced a very interconnected and exquisite story. The book won the 1979 Newbery Medal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book follows 16 people who have chosen to become heirs of an estate worth over $200 million belonging to a famous game-loving millionaire, Sam Westing. No one knows why Sam Westing has chosen 16 seemingly random people to inherit his vast fortune, but that won&amp;#39;t stop him from playing one last game, even if it is from beyond the grave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genre: Mystery, Action&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Published 1978 by Ellen Raskin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookshop.org爲響應Prime Day，今明兩天免運費]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bookshop.org爲您從當地書店購買的商品提供貨源，這是一項偉大的服務。
它是一項偉大的服務，有助於支持當地企業，否則這些企業將在網絡競爭和電子書中掙扎。
在線競爭和電子書。在今天和明天，他們提供免費
來與亞馬遜總理日競爭。有一本書你可以...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o55mm3/bookshoporg_has_free_shipping_today_and_tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o55mm3/bookshoporg_has_free_shipping_today_and_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 22:25:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bookshop.org sources your purchases from your local bookstores, it&amp;#39;s a great service that helps support local businesses that are otherwise struggling with online competition and e-books. For today and tomorrow they&amp;#39;re offering free shipping to compete with Amazon Prime Day. There&amp;#39;s a book you can contemplating, it&amp;#39;s a good time to snatch one up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[讓你感到快樂和冒險的書籍，讓你再次愛上生活，沒有太多的悲傷或悲劇的書籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一段有毒的關係之後，我正在經歷一個非常艱難的分手。淚水已經夠多了
現在我想找回那種火花，再次享受生活。

我更喜歡沒有愛情的書，但如果是一個小的次要情節也可以。請幫助
我吧!]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o4r0dx/books_that_make_you_feel_happy_and_adventurous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o4r0dx/books_that_make_you_feel_happy_and_adventurous/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:11:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going through a very tough breakup after a toxic relationship. Enough tears have been shed, now I want to find that spark back and enjoy life again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I prefer books without romance but if it&amp;#39;s a small subplot it&amp;#39;s ok. Please help me out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>