<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:40:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[1 Big App - 力用戶的必備條件。18 個 1 合 1 應用程序。不斷增長的應用收藏]]></title><description><![CDATA[1個大應用--功能盡在指尖。你總是得到所有應用程序的最新版本。應用程序集合定期更新。你可以要求的功能]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/ph/1-big-app</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/ph/1-big-app</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 18:32:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>1 Big App - functionality at your fingertips. You always get the latest version of all the apps. App collection updated regularly. You can request features!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[民調：拜登計劃取消難民上限是他最不受歡迎的行政行動｜TheHill]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/redirect/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.google.com%2F__i%2Frss%2Frd%2Farticles%2FCBMidGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlaGlsbC5jb20vcG9saWN5L25hdGlvbmFsLXNlY3VyaXR5LzUzODI5My1iaWRlbi1wbGFuLXRvLWxpZnQtcmVmdWdlZS1jYXAtaXMtbGVhc3QtcG9wdWxhci1leGVjdXRpdmUtYWN0aW9u0gF4aHR0cHM6Ly90aGVoaWxsLmNvbS9wb2xpY3kvbmF0aW9uYWwtc2VjdXJpdHkvNTM4MjkzLWJpZGVuLXBsYW4tdG8tbGlmdC1yZWZ1Z2VlLWNhcC1pcy1sZWFzdC1wb3B1bGFyLWV4ZWN1dGl2ZS1hY3Rpb24_YW1w%3Foc%3D5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/redirect/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.google.com%2F__i%2Frss%2Frd%2Farticles%2FCBMidGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlaGlsbC5jb20vcG9saWN5L25hdGlvbmFsLXNlY3VyaXR5LzUzODI5My1iaWRlbi1wbGFuLXRvLWxpZnQtcmVmdWdlZS1jYXAtaXMtbGVhc3QtcG9wdWxhci1leGVjdXRpdmUtYWN0aW9u0gF4aHR0cHM6Ly90aGVoaWxsLmNvbS9wb2xpY3kvbmF0aW9uYWwtc2VjdXJpdHkvNTM4MjkzLWJpZGVuLXBsYW4tdG8tbGlmdC1yZWZ1Z2VlLWNhcC1pcy1sZWFzdC1wb3B1bGFyLWV4ZWN1dGl2ZS1hY3Rpb24_YW1w%3Foc%3D5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 03:57:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 不要評論一個人在聚會/餐館/餐桌上喫得有多少：這對當事人來說是一種令人難以置信的負面體驗，許多人由於殘缺的、悲慘的疾病而無法一次喫下正常的分量，即使是他們最親近的親人也沒有注意到。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：許多人正在從、已經從或正在從恢復中恢復。
患有厭食症、暴食症等疾病，或患有慢性病，如
作爲癌症或白血病，從字面上看，不能喫得太多，而不覺得。
難以置信的飽腹感和噁心感。其實，你不應該評論... ...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/kue5p4/ysk_dont_comment_on_how_little_someone_eats_at_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/kue5p4/ysk_dont_comment_on_how_little_someone_eats_at_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people who are recovering from, have recovered from, or are struggling with an illness such as anorexia, bulimia, or chronic illnesses such as cancer or leukemia, literally can not eat very much at all without feeling incredibly full and nauseous. In fact, you shouldn&amp;#39;t comment on someone&amp;#39;s eating habits in public AT ALL. You have no idea what their health is like, what it feels like to be them, what their physical limitations are, or what their relationship with food is like. You could be publically humaliting someone in regards to their disease and not even know it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That person who you think is being disrespectful or wasteful at the dinner table may well be very upset at themselves because they can&amp;#39;t finish their meal because of an incredibly tragic mental illness that has changed the size of their stomach and appetite forever, and now someone is upset at them for &amp;quot;not clearing their plate.&amp;quot; Or now the waitress is pointing out to everyone, &amp;quot;You barely touched your meal!&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While that person has to repeat the same things over again, having to conceal these very private, sometimes undetectable by even the most closest people in their lives, illnesses: &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not feeling well is all&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I ate before, I&amp;#39;m just not hungry&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I want to save it for later&amp;quot;, because blurting out &amp;quot;I can&amp;#39;t finish this meal due to my shrunken stomach because of (incredibly sad disease)&amp;quot; is a huge moodkiller during brunch and drinks with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish we would change the dialogue around the dinner table when it comes to people who cannot finish their meal. I wish people would stop pressuring people to eat more or less or this or that. Inevitably the least that could happen is you make that person uncomfortable and embarrassed about their illness in front of everyone, and the worst that could happen is that they become so distraught from the public humiliation, being reminded of the physical consequences of their disease at a time that should feel safe in inclusive, they cry once they&amp;#39;re alone, breakdown, relapse, self-harm, or plan to not eat for a whole day before they ever come to your house again to eat hoping they can finish whatever random amount of food you give them- just so they can prevent that horrible experience from happening again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want people to eat more? Stop telling them they should. You might think you know someone, but many people with eating disorders conceal it so well that they go undetected by even their family members they live under the same roof with, or the person the wake up next to every morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating disorders are the most deadly psychological disease and pose many health issues that you can&amp;#39;t tell by just looking that they have: nausea, heartburn, shrunken stomach, stomachs that need assistance disgesting, IBS, constipation, diarrhea, extreme fatigue, complete loss of appetite (even when a recovered individual WANTS to eat more and gain weight).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People really don&amp;#39;t realize this because there&amp;#39;s not enough awareness, I don&amp;#39;t think people who comment on how little soneone eats are bad people- they usually come from a caring place, but are inadvertently causing harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most deadly psychiatric disease: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/news/20110711/deadliest-psychiatric-disorder-anorexia&quot;&gt;https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/news/20110711/deadliest-psychiatric-disorder-anorexia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permanent appetite loss in recovered individuals, anorexia not driven by the desire to lose weight, but by a lack of appetite due to illness or issues with the brain: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.merckmanuals.com/home/digestive-disorders/symptoms-of-digestive-disorders/loss-of-appetite&quot;&gt;https://www.merckmanuals.com/home/digestive-disorders/symptoms-of-digestive-disorders/loss-of-appetite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果有人在英語中犯了一個微不足道的錯誤，這並不是什麼大不了的事，也不能成爲否定其觀點的依據。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：人們經常嘲笑人們的語法或其他錯誤。
英語來使他們的觀點無效。他們很可能也注意到了，只是
不在乎。他們的觀點如果足夠連貫的話，仍然是滯後的，任何人都會去
不去評論他們的錯誤，要麼是失去了... ...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ksx5nc/ysk_if_someone_commits_a_trivial_mistake_in_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ksx5nc/ysk_if_someone_commits_a_trivial_mistake_in_their/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People often ridicule the grammatical or other mistakes in people’s English to invalidate their point. Chances are they noticed it too and simply don’t care. Their point still stands stall if it’s coherent enough, anyone going out of the way to comment on their mistake is either losing the argument or are too immature to engage in one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s very common in the Indian subcontinent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: About time I made an edit to have my final say and leave. I personally love English and it&amp;#39;s not even my mother tongue. It is, for me, the most beautiful language ever and I want to be as good at it as I can. I made this post because a lot of non-native speakers out there are &lt;em&gt;ridiculed&lt;/em&gt; everyday for bad, incorrect English. While it is important to speak the language you&amp;#39;re speaking as correctly as possible, for some it may not matter so much because they don&amp;#39;t need it anywhere in their life. Also, one should always look for when is one helpfully correcting your mistakes so you may learn and appreciate them. Enough preaching. Over and out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 開車前應先清除前*和*後擋風玻璃、所有車窗、引擎蓋和車頂的積雪。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：任何留在車上的雪都會對你或其他人造成危險。
開車時，車身上的。

車窗上的雪會阻擋視線。

引擎蓋上的積雪會飛起來砸在擋風玻璃上，擋住你的視線。
道路。

後擋風玻璃上的雪限制了你看清後方的能力... ...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/kt19g3/ysk_snow_should_be_removed_from_the_front_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/kt19g3/ysk_snow_should_be_removed_from_the_front_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;em&gt;Any&lt;/em&gt; snow left on your car can become a hazard to you or others if left on the car while driving. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snow on the windows can block visibility.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snow on the hood can fly up and hit the windshield, blocking your view of the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snow on the rear windshield limits your ability to see behind you, even if you have side rear view mirrors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snow on the TOP of your car can either fly off your car onto the car behind you, OR slightly melt from the interior heat of your car enough to slide onto your front windshield if you have to stop suddenly. In my experience this is one area of a car that I commonly see has not been cleared before driving. If you have a tall vehicle, get a telescoping snow brush and/or a small folding step stool to keep in the vehicle for these occasions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be safe out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當你迷戀一個人的時候，你的大腦會釋放出大量的多巴胺進入你的系統，以至於你認爲這個人是完美的。雖然這是一種很好的感覺，但它也會導致你對這個人的癡情回報產生不值得的感覺。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Because although these feelings of euphoria are exciting, they can just...
很容易讓你覺得沒有安全感，不值得你這樣做的人
迷戀。

不要讓你的多巴胺欺騙你相信他們是絕對無懈可擊的。
並認爲你不值得他們愛。

編輯：...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ku2qj6/ysk_when_youre_infatuated_with_someone_your_brain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ku2qj6/ysk_when_youre_infatuated_with_someone_your_brain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Because although these feelings of euphoria are exciting, they can just as easily leave you feeling insecure and undeserving of the person you&amp;#39;re infatuated with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let your dopamine trick you into believing they&amp;#39;re absolutely faultless and that you&amp;#39;re unworthy of their love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Many relationships thrive off continued infatuation. I&amp;#39;m not saying there is anything wrong with relationships like this. This advice is for people with unhealthy levels of infatuation - those that leave you feeling unworthy of love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你身邊的人都是混蛋，不代表你就是混蛋。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：有句話說得好：如果你身邊的人都是混蛋，你可能就是那個
真正的混蛋。以下是爲什麼這並不總是如此。

遭受創傷（特別是童年創傷）的人往往是。
吸引到與他們一起長大的人相似的人。你的大腦不會
管他]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/kturp5/ysk_just_because_everyone_around_you_is_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/kturp5/ysk_just_because_everyone_around_you_is_an/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 21:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: there’s a saying: if everyone around you is an asshole you might be the actual asshole. Here’s why that’s not always the case. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who suffered from trauma (specifically childhood trauma) are often attracted to people similar to the ones they grew up with. Your brain doesn’t care if it’s healthy or unhealthy—your brain cares that it’s familiar. In the same way that you may need to be careful of the partner you choose, be careful of your work environment, friends, and social community. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certain environments attract a certain type of individual, all who might be similarly distasteful or toxic to you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A better quote would be “before you diagnose yourself with low self esteem, be sure you are not, in fact, surrounded by assholes”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is in fact quite possible to be surrounded with toxic people (or at least people you don’t mesh with/people who don’t understand or appreciate you), without being an asshole yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020年度最佳HN]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25600011</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25600011</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我向你道歉]]></title><description><![CDATA[yes]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/youtube/_WfGgl9Q1JQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/youtube/_WfGgl9Q1JQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 15:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>yes</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新解密的信息揭示了中情局爲何得出結論，即俄羅斯很可能爲襲擊駐阿富汗的美國和盟軍提供賞金。
https://t.co/u6BMdt0Q2M]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1318004551878733824</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1318004551878733824</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 01:42:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#比特币减半后为 
2021年1月6日

在第三次减半后的239日。
#BTC%，报34,612美元。

我知道还需要几个月的时间，但还有谁好奇地想知道10月份我们离286,000美元有多近呢？

见10月17日https://t.co/ZSKbJMh0sm👇增长区间的小幅走势]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1311591409032462337</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1311591409032462337</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 08:58:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新解密的信息揭示了中情局爲何得出結論，即俄羅斯很可能爲襲擊駐阿富汗的美國和盟軍提供賞金。
https://t.co/u6BMdt0Q2M]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1318572007928180736</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1318572007928180736</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 09:24:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新解密的信息揭示了中情局爲何得出結論，即俄羅斯很可能爲襲擊駐阿富汗的美國和盟軍提供賞金。
https://t.co/u6BMdt0Q2M]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1315580687861182465</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1315580687861182465</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 09:24:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[KSI-域]]></title><description><![CDATA[收聽蘋果音樂：https://apple.co/3mPpiPJ
康斯坦丁x蓋伊的電影。
“基拉·基拉壯舉”的續集。艾雅娜·李(第一部分)來了。
KSI用新的視覺效果揭開了動作短片的下一個篇章“領域”(Domain)的面紗
(警告：視頻包含咒罵和暴力場面)。
這不是現實生活中的FAM]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/youtube/1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/youtube/1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 1970 07:31:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Listen on Apple Music: https://apple.co/3mPpiPJ
A film by Konstantin x Guy. 
The sequel to ‘Killa Killa feat. Aiyana Lee (Part I)’ is here. 
KSI unveils the next chapter of the action packed short film with new visuals for ‘Domain’ 
(Warning: Video contains expletives and scenes of violence). 
THIS IS NOT REAL LIFE FAM</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[虛擬現實何時起飛？100美元的賭注]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/redirect/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.google.com%2F__i%2Frss%2Frd%2Farticles%2FCBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lndzai5jb20vYXJ0aWNsZXMvd2hhdC1kb2VzLXRoZS1icmV4aXQtZGVhbC1tZWFuLWZvci1maW5hbmNpYWwtc2VydmljZXMtMTE2MDg4MzQwMjfSAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy53c2ouY29tL2FtcC9hcnRpY2xlcy93aGF0LWRvZXMtdGhlLWJyZXhpdC1kZWFsLW1lYW4tZm9yLWZpbmFuY2lhbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy0xMTYwODgzNDAyNw%3Foc%3D5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/redirect/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.google.com%2F__i%2Frss%2Frd%2Farticles%2FCBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lndzai5jb20vYXJ0aWNsZXMvd2hhdC1kb2VzLXRoZS1icmV4aXQtZGVhbC1tZWFuLWZvci1maW5hbmNpYWwtc2VydmljZXMtMTE2MDg4MzQwMjfSAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy53c2ouY29tL2FtcC9hcnRpY2xlcy93aGF0LWRvZXMtdGhlLWJyZXhpdC1kZWFsLW1lYW4tZm9yLWZpbmFuY2lhbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy0xMTYwODgzNDAyNw%3Foc%3D5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 1970 10:45:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Artify Illustrations - tag]]></title><description><![CDATA[虛擬現實何時起飛？100美元的賭注]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/ph/1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/ph/1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 1970 08:47:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A new release from the Artify crew featuring 5000+ unique illustrations available for download in high quality PNG files as well as vector sources, there are over 70 illustration styles from high quality 3D styles to minimalistic and abstract lines!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我盡力了]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 1970 12:17:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉的市值現在比沃爾瑪高出500億美元。

銷售量..。
特斯拉：280億美元
沃爾瑪：5490億美元

淨收入.
特斯拉：5.56億美元
沃爾瑪：200億美元

$TSLA$WMT

通過@ycharts https://t.co/ajSyGIsrOs查看圖表/數據]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 16:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我盡力了]]></title><description><![CDATA[test]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/dankmemes/comments/kc0vb6/i_tried_my_best/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/dankmemes/comments/kc0vb6/i_tried_my_best/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>test</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>