<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:27:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[The new length of bear markets:

Stock market - 18 days

Bitcoin - 18 hours]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349709631661232131</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349709631661232131</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:20:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The new length of bear markets:

Stock market - 18 days

Bitcoin - 18 hours</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FOOD gene editing stocks UPDATE!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Morning everyone.

You may recall I wrote a post on here not too long ago on how GMO food plays
could be the next hot sector.

For those who didn’t and would like to find out more, have a read and read the
comments. It was a great/informative discussion that didn’t revolve around “BUY
PLTR OR BUY…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kx38a3/food_gene_editing_stocks_update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kx38a3/food_gene_editing_stocks_update/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:19:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morning everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may recall I wrote a post on here not too long ago on how GMO food plays could be the next hot sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who didn’t and would like to find out more, have a read and read the comments. It was a great/informative discussion that didn’t revolve around “BUY PLTR OR BUY DKNG”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good DD and suggested plays, enjoy;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/jbc4v7/the_next_hot_sector_food_gene_editing_stocks/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/jbc4v7/the_next_hot_sector_food_gene_editing_stocks/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who did read or had an interest in it, I just thought I would provide an update on how they are going. I think this sector is going to have a huge year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My post was 91 days ago  and my suggested plays were;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corteva (CTVA)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$33.82 Now: $44.13&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Precision Bioscience (DTIL)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$6.52 Now: $9.80&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calyxt (CLXT)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$5.07 Now: $4.76
(offering/dilution occurred soon after, not ideal but has been steadily climbing)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yield 10 Bioscience (YTEN)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$6.49 Now: $7.61&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Origin Argitech (SEED)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$9.63 Now: $16.51&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was getting a lot of DMs about the original post so said it would be easier to do an update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To answer a few questions, I am still very, very bullish on this sector. I think it is only the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My recommendation and largest holding from the above is SEED.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SEED have been working for 10 years to get their GMO right and approved by government, finally they are in and the government is ready to roll out GMO in China. SEED will dominate this space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has had a huge run so far but there are way more catalysts ahead and with a 3 million share float, this going to go parabolic soon. Shorts covering the higher it inevitably goes, think GameStop, Nio, XPEV type of runs , the ones that just look outrageous on your watch list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more about the opportunity for SEED here&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1321851/000110465920094375/tm2027521d1_ex99-1.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1321851/000110465920094375/tm2027521d1_ex99-1.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SEED turned down $24 a share in 2014.
The CFO commented “I tell people the value of this company is Monsanto multiplied by Baidu divided by Google,” Talk about being bullish and keeping the faith. He was right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, before commenting mindless comments, “BUY PLTR” “PUMP IT” , just read the original post where I dived deep or do a quick google on GMO or the stocks above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of newbies, so many pump and dumpers but genuine, informative posts about companies still exist on here. I still love this sub!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a long term investor so I’m not to bothered by short term volatility. SEEDs all time high was around $170 15 years ago. In a few months, SEED can be up at 30-40 and I think in a year , it can be at $100, no problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoyed and hope everyone has a great year investing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fuck Melvin Capital]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know everyone here is excited about GME stock, but have you really sat back
and thought about who and what we're up against? Let me remind you.

Melvin Capital bet that GameStop would go bankrupt. If it had, those assholes
would've been dancing in their New York offices, popping champagne and…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kx5wu9/fuck_melvin_capital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kx5wu9/fuck_melvin_capital/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:19:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know everyone here is excited about GME stock, but have you really sat back and thought about who and what we&amp;#39;re up against? Let me remind you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Melvin Capital bet that GameStop would go bankrupt. If it had, those assholes would&amp;#39;ve been dancing in their New York offices, popping champagne and laughing, completely aware of the damage they were rejoicing in. They tried to capitalize on a global pandemic as the final nail in the coffin for yet another retail company that wouldn&amp;#39;t change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other side, things would&amp;#39;ve been pretty grim. GameStop workers make, what, slightly more than minimum wage? They are probably completely unaware of companies like Melvin Capital who hope their employer goes out of business. They&amp;#39;re just trying to make a buck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GameStop may have an outdated business model that hasn&amp;#39;t adapted to 2011, let alone 2021, but it&amp;#39;s an American institution. Every single one of us has walked into a GameStop at least once and bought a game we were excited about. Our little brothers and sisters would beg us to take them there to buy the 80th edition of Pokemon Red/Blue/Yellow/Gold/whatever. We&amp;#39;ve all perused a Game Informer, hoping to see a 10 rating. You can shit on them for charging too much or not paying enough for a used game, but you don&amp;#39;t hope their people go on unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Melvin Capital and short sellers (lol &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/wxohwokyrab61.jpg&quot;&gt;Frankfurt School Associates&lt;/a&gt;) can go fuck themselves. Go read about these assholes if you want to put a smile on your face, knowing what they&amp;#39;re dealing with right now. I hope Gabriel Plotkin has to sell his $40 million Miami mansion (he just bought it in December). Hell, I hope Ryan Cohen buys it from him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions&lt;/strong&gt;: Half my Roth IRA in GME shares. A few calls. Just like a lot of you, not enough to really make a difference. But together we can slay giants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exit Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;: I have no sell orders. I&amp;#39;ll sell when someone posts a story about Melvin Capital going bankrupt. Fuck em.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t fucking sell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla's Model Y wins 5-star safety rating from NHTSA]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/teslas-model-y-wins-5-star-rating-from-nhtsa

The NHTSA grades vehicles based on a series of scenarios, including frontal
crashes, with subcategories for the driver and passenger seats, side crashes
involving poles and barriers, and a rollover. The Model Y has…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kx6mkw/teslas_model_y_wins_5star_safety_rating_from_nhtsa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kx6mkw/teslas_model_y_wins_5star_safety_rating_from_nhtsa/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:19:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/teslas-model-y-wins-5-star-rating-from-nhtsa&quot;&gt;https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/teslas-model-y-wins-5-star-rating-from-nhtsa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NHTSA grades vehicles based on a series of scenarios, including frontal crashes, with subcategories for the driver and passenger seats, side crashes involving poles and barriers, and a rollover. The Model Y has a rollover risk of 7.9%, the lowest of any SUV recorded to date by the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Model Y is &amp;quot;engineered to distribute crash forces around the cabin and away from vehicle occupants, greatly reducing the risk of injury,&amp;quot; according to the automaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Safety is at the core of every Tesla vehicle, and Model Y benefits from years of immense passion for vehicle safety,&amp;quot; Tesla added. &amp;quot;By providing the most advanced equipment and technologies, our goal is to help customers prevent avoidable accidents whenever possible, and, when they are not avoidable, to help mitigate injury to the fullest extent possible. Indeed, we believe Model Y to be among the safest vehicles available to consumers on the road.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10 years-ish of Elixir]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25776525</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25776525</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:19:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apple reportedly dropped plan for encrypting backups after FBI complained (2020)]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25777207</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25777207</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:19:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook Has Been Showing Military Gear Ads Next to “Insurrection” Posts]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25776590</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25776590</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 17:19:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不知道湯姆-布雷迪有一天退役後會不會推銷比特幣IRA呢https://t.co/I2mtNk7QAY。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349507526010806274</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349507526010806274</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 16:07:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>I wonder if Tom Brady is gonna be pitching bitcoin IRAs someday when he’s retired https://t.co/I2mtNk7QAY</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今日股市新聞｜GME擠壓｜BABA, INTC, TGT, AFRM及其他股市新聞 [01-14] 。]]></title><description><![CDATA[GameStop空頭壓境! 阿里巴巴繼續發力電動車領域。英特爾
飆升，而AMD與TSM則受到影響。讓我們來談談這一點和其他股市
新聞!

大家好，早上好! 那麼，我們先來回顧一下昨天的情況，因爲。
我們看到股市收盤漲跌不一，納斯達克...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kx57p4/stock_market_news_for_today_gme_squeeze_baba_intc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kx57p4/stock_market_news_for_today_gme_squeeze_baba_intc/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 16:07:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GameStop short squeeze is ON! Alibaba continues to push into the EV world. Intel spikes while AMD &amp;amp; TSM suffer. Let’s talk about this and other stock market news!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone and Good Morning! So, let’s start with the recap of yesterday as we saw the stock market finishing mixed, with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/qybhmjC&quot;&gt;Nasdaq Composite&lt;/a&gt; gaining .43%, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/YL4XS6m&quot;&gt;SP500&lt;/a&gt; also gaining .23% while the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/YTFwLcx&quot;&gt;Dow Jones&lt;/a&gt; lost just 8 points to close out the day. We also saw the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/0r28dsT&quot;&gt;VIX&lt;/a&gt; dropping almost 5% again, continuing the downtrend after that huge spike with the Georgia elections, as it sits at similar levels to the ones before Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the positive gains for the broad stock market SP500, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/PrDh7DD&quot;&gt;OVERALL&lt;/a&gt;, we saw about 57% of the companies declining yesterday, with most of them trading below average volumes, as the number of companies trading above the 50-day moving average still sits over 70%, which is pretty high. Yesterday we saw 6 of the 11 &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/wJH4B8C&quot;&gt;SECTORS&lt;/a&gt; finish in the green with Real Estate and Utilities posting gains of more than 1% while the laggards were Energy, Industrials and Materials, as we saw large-cap growth companies finally &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/kKtRY96&quot;&gt;OUTPERFORMED&lt;/a&gt; for once in 2021, with small &amp;amp; mid-caps giving up some of the big gains they have posted in this short year, though, Large-Cap Growth companies are still underperforming by 3% compared to the next factor group in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/Ms0qkCh&quot;&gt;HEAT MAP&lt;/a&gt; from yesterday, which shows pretty mixed results as expected, with most of the big tech companies posting small gains like Apple, Amazon, Google, Netflix and the rest of the bunch, with Alibaba posting a 4% gain after some EV news popped up and Intel also gaining almost 7% and pushed the rest of the Semiconductors down with TSM and AMD both down over 3%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also got a lot of economic data yesterday as the US &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/QXXDBrc&quot;&gt;DEFICIT&lt;/a&gt; fell by $2B to $143B in December compared to the previous month, but is up 10 fold from the $13B deficit from the same period in 2019, and this doesn’t even include any of the $900B stimulus packaged that passed late in December, while the December consumer price &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/n1Jr9G2&quot;&gt;INDEX&lt;/a&gt; increased by 0.4% m/m and Core CPI also increase by 0.1%, coming in-line with expectations, as the Atlanta FED business inflation expectations &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/t2v98jw&quot;&gt;ROSE&lt;/a&gt; to 2.2% in January compared to December, though sales and profit margins compared to normal, decreased since the last month, while one of the FED’s Vice Chairs &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/WtNxQKM&quot;&gt;RESTATED&lt;/a&gt; that the FED won’t raise rates until the average long-term inflation stands at 2% for a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/C79879d&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt; we get lots of important economic data with Jobless numbers in the early morning, which are expected to come around the same numbers as the previous week and end with the Money Supply and FED Balance Sheet while the stock market will also turn its eyes to see what the FED Leader Powell announces in terms of the FED keeping the money printer going, and of course to see what Biden announces about a further stimulus packaged that is expected to be as big as $2T.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In some other stock market news, we saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/9bHNxrx&quot;&gt;Intel&lt;/a&gt; spiking yesterday after the company decided on a change in leadership, this move put some selling pressure on rival companies like TSM, AMD &amp;amp; others, but I think this is more of a “hype move” right now. Intel has still fallen behind it’s competition and it will take massive Capex and R&amp;amp;D investments to catch up, so the selloff in other players should rather be a buying point, especially for AMD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/Phk4N4s&quot;&gt;Target&lt;/a&gt; reporting huge comp sale increases with a 4.3% increase in traffic and a massive 12.3% increase in the average ticket, as comparable digital sales more than doubled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also saw, their same-day services post an impressive growth of almost 200%, as they remain one of the best plays in the consumer discretionary sector, as 95% of their sales were fulfilled by their 1600 store that are within 10miles of ¾ of the US population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, guys, these small cap companies keep on giving me reasons to come back to the same points I have been making in the past weeks, with company after company issuing shares, with the latest ones being &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/qDRKJ7Y&quot;&gt;Nano&lt;/a&gt; Dimension which are diluting their shares by about 20% while &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/27StT0c&quot;&gt;Lemonade&lt;/a&gt; has also increased their stock offering by another 300.000 shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While in another kind of news we saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/pLMSXrb&quot;&gt;GameStop&lt;/a&gt; soar yesterday finishing the day up over 57%, after a huge short squeeze pushed the stock up as high as 90% at one point. This has happened after GameStop has &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/F3S2XTT&quot;&gt;PUSHED&lt;/a&gt; for a change in leadership with plenty of experience in the e-commerce and online marketing world, with 3 veterans from Chewy, which has been an impressive performer in the online e-commerce business. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/y8XVnd7&quot;&gt;STOCK&lt;/a&gt; Is up another 20% in pre-market right now as the short squeeze keeps increasing the pressure on the bears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/vjKdwKW&quot;&gt;Alibaba&lt;/a&gt; making a couple of headlines yesterday, which helped push the stocks 4% higher, after the Wall Street Journal reported that the US is expected to continue to allow investments in Alibaba, Baidu &amp;amp; Tencent, while also continuing their charge into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/0tVsJSS&quot;&gt;EV&lt;/a&gt; world, with a new electric sedan that features wireless charging in cooperation with China’s state owned SAIC Motor. This is their latest push into the EV world, as Alibaba is also an investor in Xpeng. This news, might help the stock see a recovery, that could be boosted if Jack Ma finally appears and the Ant Group IPO eventually receives the green light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And one last piece of &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/Z8RSWQL&quot;&gt;NEWS&lt;/a&gt; is that Affirm went public yesterday and started trading at just over 90$, more than 80% above the IPO price, as the IPO mania keeps on pushing any recent IPO to big pops on the first day of trading, but unfortunately, retail investors do not benefit from this, as the actual return for people who manage to buy right at the open price, is under 10% while also risking a severe drop in the next days. Hopefully more companies will move to direct listings IPOs which will allow retail investors to get part of the action, which will benefit most of the people, not just the “big players” who get in at much lower prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, let’s hope for a good day in the markets as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/T8wRNxc&quot;&gt;WORLD&lt;/a&gt; Markets are in the green while the US &lt;a href=&quot;https://ibb.co/LkrrWtc&quot;&gt;FUTURES&lt;/a&gt; are also pointing to a good open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙏Thank you everyone for reading!🙏 Hope you enjoyed the content! Be sure to leave a comment down below with your opinion on the stock market! Have a great day and see you next time❗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大擠壓--GME拋物線移動的故事。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwwi2m/the_big_squeeze_the_story_of_gmes_parabolic_move/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwwi2m/the_big_squeeze_the_story_of_gmes_parabolic_move/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 16:07:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[他們甚至不知道自己在做什麼--讓他們看看🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kx5cmy/they_dont_even_know_what_theyre_getting_into_lets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kx5cmy/they_dont_even_know_what_theyre_getting_into_lets/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 16:07:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[機器學習。大停滯]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25775740</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25775740</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 16:07:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1912年的巴黎風情]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25775091</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25775091</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 16:07:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[失業金申請。上週又有96.5萬美國人提出新的失業申請]]></title><description><![CDATA[上週新申請的周度失業金人數激增，遠超預期，達到了
由於冠狀病毒大流行和留守訂單的影響，創下五個月來的新高。
嚴重影響了勞動力市場。

美國勞工部公佈了每週新申請失業救濟人數報告。
星期四上午8時30分....。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kx5z5x/jobless_claims_another_965000_americans_filed_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kx5z5x/jobless_claims_another_965000_americans_filed_new/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 15:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;New weekly unemployment claims spiked far more than expected last week to reach a five-month high, as the coronavirus pandemic and stay-in-place orders weighed heavily on the labor market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Department of Labor released its weekly report on new jobless claims Thursday morning at 8:30 a.m. ET. Here were the main results in the report, compared to consensus estimates compiled by Bloomberg:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initial jobless claims, week ended Jan. 9: 965,000 vs. 789,000 expected and a revised 784,000 during the prior week&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuing claims, week ended Jan. 2: 5.271 million vs. 5.000 million expected and 5.072 million during the prior week&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/initial-jobless-claims-week-ended-jan-9-2021-coronavirus-pandemic-191640522.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/initial-jobless-claims-week-ended-jan-9-2021-coronavirus-pandemic-191640522.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽車E /r/wallstreetbets vs Melvin Capital]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kx2elq/gme_rwallstreetbets_vs_melvin_capital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kx2elq/gme_rwallstreetbets_vs_melvin_capital/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 14:51:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TSLA能感覺到一個死人在走路。TSLA TO 1000 EOW 🚀🚀。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwy1j6/tsla_can_sense_a_dead_man_walking_tsla_to_1000_eow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwy1j6/tsla_can_sense_a_dead_man_walking_tsla_to_1000_eow/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[DD]12k關於NextEra Energy(NEE)LEAPs作爲清潔能源的玩法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我並不打算就此發帖，但我想說明一下情況
投資於一家專注於清潔能源的公用事業公司是明智之舉。
即將到來的刺激政策/轉向可再生能源。

那麼，什麼是NextEra能源？從維基百科上總結出來的。

 * 它是最大的電力...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwyduo/dd_12k_on_nextera_energy_nee_leaps_as_a_clean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwyduo/dd_12k_on_nextera_energy_nee_leaps_as_a_clean/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 13:00:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I  wasn&amp;#39;t really planning on making a post on this, but I&amp;#39;d like to make the case for investing in a utilities company focused on clean energy as a smart play for the upcoming stimulus/shift towards renewables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what&amp;#39;s NextEra Energy? Summarized from Wikipedia:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is the largest electric utility in the USA by market capitalization. (At 160B currently)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenues of over $19.20 billion in 2019. Operating income of $5.35 billion in 2019.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;About 14,000 employees throughout the US and Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The important subsidiaries include

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Utilities;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida Power &amp;amp; Light (FPL) - A Florida electric utility. Notable for having wider profit margins than usual.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gulf Power Company - Electric utility in the Alabama area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NextEra Energy Capital Holdings (NEECH)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NextEra  Energy Resources (NEER) - The largest operators of wind and solar  projects in the world. Importantly, expansive holdings in the Midwest.  Also has numerous energy storage projects under their belt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They also have a 35% stake in NextEra Energy Partners (NEP) with Jim Robo being the CEO of both companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.investor.nexteraenergy.com/fixed-income-investors/financial-policy&quot;&gt;In  fact, I&amp;#39;ll just direct you to NextEra&amp;#39;s IR page, because for some  reason they&amp;#39;ve placed a very solid series of pages outlining their  financial health where almost nobody will find them.&lt;/a&gt; You can flip  through the Policy, Strength, Funding/Capital Structure, Cash  Flow/Leverage, and Liquidity pages there at your leisure to understand  more about the company. But basically, they&amp;#39;re extremely healthy as a  company. Notably, they&amp;#39;ve been &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.investor.nexteraenergy.com/news-and-events/news-releases/2020/11-02-2020-222338600&quot;&gt;unwinding positions for cash&lt;/a&gt; recently despite their solid balance sheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now,  I&amp;#39;d like to point out their P/E: 41. Yup, this is a &amp;quot;boring&amp;quot; utility company trading at 41x P/E after running up 200% in 5 years and 80% in  2. For reference, Microsoft is trading at 34.90 P/E. As far as utilities  go, I think it&amp;#39;s fair to say these guys are as far from boring as it  gets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary of the fundamentals;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management is extremely reliable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They&amp;#39;re the market leader in renewables deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They&amp;#39;ve proven they know how to compete and edge out profits in cutthroat industries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High P/E, but in a stable industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have plenty of leverage available for massive capital expenditures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now  onto why I think they will collect more than their fair share of  Biden&amp;#39;s upcoming stimulus. Let&amp;#39;s start off by looking at what Biden has  been pushing in his announcements;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pushing the environmental costs onto polluters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pushing renewables directly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating long-term middle class union jobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among utilities, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.investor.nexteraenergy.com/news-and-events/news-releases/2020/12-11-2020-173514490&quot;&gt;NextEra stands out as an early and consistent investor in renewables&lt;/a&gt;. Straight from the link above:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According  to S&amp;amp;P Global Trucost, NextEra Energy ranked ahead of its peers on a  number of impressive reported performance metrics, among others,  including signed contracts to build approximately 12,000 megawatts of  additional wind, solar and battery storage projects as of the close of  2019, and NextEra Energy&amp;#39;s announced target of emissions reductions per  unit of generation by 67% by 2025 from a 2005 baseline, equivalent, to a  40% reduction in absolute emissions – and this, despite an expected  doubling of generation over the period. Already, NextEra Energy reports  more than 50% of its generation is from zero- and near-zero-emitting  sources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;#39;s fair to say that point 1 will hurt them much less than it will their less progressive competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally,  as a result of their investments so far, they&amp;#39;re not untested when it  comes to deployment: They know what to expect and we know they can  execute on larger CapEx programs with less risk than the competition. If  Biden is to throw the expected 40 billion a year into the industry,  it&amp;#39;s quite likely NextEra will be ready to scale up operations  sustainably and successfully to capitalize on the opportunity, clearing  point two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But point three is the  really interesting one. Let me start off with a question; If you were a  democratic president that wanted to create middle-class jobs in  renewables, how would you go about it? Would you invest in the companies  making the end product? Maybe a little for the companies that pull the  required resources out of the ground too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/khx7eb/stimulus_bill_includes_35_billion_for_clean/&quot;&gt;Let&amp;#39;s  take a look at what the clean energy portion stimulus bill a few weeks  ago contained and see how NextEra is positioned for each portion.&lt;/a&gt; Big thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/u/millerlit/&quot;&gt;/u/millerlit&lt;/a&gt; for summarizing. Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.investor.nexteraenergy.com/reports-and-filings/annual-reports&quot;&gt;I&amp;#39;ll be referencing the NextEra 2019 annual report from this point on&lt;/a&gt;. Please bring up a copy if you&amp;#39;d like to verify the numbers I claim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1.5 Billion for Solar - Will probably go to most industry players pretty  equally, NextEra will get a cut as a result of their investing through NEER. 12% of NEER&amp;#39;s generation is from solar power according to the 2019 annual report (p.13).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$2.6 Billion for Transport - NextEra probably won&amp;#39;t get much of this, but they have &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.investor.nexteraenergy.com/news-and-events/news-releases/2020/12-08-2020-123104618&quot;&gt;made an acquisition&lt;/a&gt; in the field within the last month. It would be a nice perk if they  announced major projects here, but let&amp;#39;s just leave this as a  hypothetical.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1.7 billion for a Weatherization Assistance Program - I&amp;#39;m not 100% sure how  they&amp;#39;ll break this down, but up here in Canada they do these programs  as rebates through utility providers. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fpl.com/save/programs.html&quot;&gt;NextEra is almost definitely going to get a cut of this as far as I can see.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1.08 billion for short-term, long-term, seasonal and transportation energy  storage technologies - NextEra is pretty big in the battery storage  field. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greentechmedia.com/articles/read/nextera-energy-to-spend-1b-on-energy-storage-projects-in-2021&quot;&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think they&amp;#39;ll be the ones developing a new battery chemistry, but they&amp;#39;re definitely a serious user.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$2.36 billion for smart utility and energy distribution technologies. -  They&amp;#39;re going to get a serious cut of this for obvious reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$625  million for new research, development and commercialization for both  onshore and offshore wind technologies - 65% of NEER&amp;#39;s renewables  generation is wind power according to the 2019 annual report. They&amp;#39;re  going to get a nice cut here too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$850 million for geothermal technology development - Nothing here will go to NextEra, as far as I&amp;#39;m aware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1093 million for marine energy and hydropower tech - Nothing here will go to NextEra, as far as I&amp;#39;m aware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$500 million pot for industry and transportation looking to decarbonize - 0 stake in this race&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$6.2  billion for carbon capture utilization and storage technologies - FPL  is investing quite heavily here, as 74% of their generation back in 2019  was from Natural Gas (p.9). They&amp;#39;re going to get a good portion of  this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$6.6  billion in funding for the modernization of existing nuclear power  plants and the development of advanced reactors - FPL generated 22% of  their power from Nuclear in 2019 (p.9). They&amp;#39;re probably going to get a  fair slice of this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$4.7 billion for fusion industry - NextEra isn&amp;#39;t spending money on fusion development, as far as I&amp;#39;m aware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Looser  regulations for using government land for renewables - A nice gesture  to drop land costs by increasing supply for sustainable uses. &lt;a href=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/0f/US_federal_land.agencies.svg/1280px-US_federal_land.agencies.svg.png&quot;&gt;Here&amp;#39;s a map of US public land so you can take a look.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you get the point by now - NextEra has a slice in a lot of these pies directly. On top of that, the renewables segment as a whole is going to hugely benefit from the stimulus driving down the capital expenditures required for panels and turbines. Frankly, there are very few people  better positioned than a well-run utility company with massive credit  available taking on the debt at great rates. When I put it like that, it&amp;#39;s no surprise that these folks managed to thrive under Trump&amp;#39;s policies - and that they&amp;#39;re extremely well positioned to grow aggressively under Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there&amp;#39;s even a fun political trap for the republicans here. Do you know  where the best place to place on-shore wind turbines is? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nist.gov/sites/default/files/images/itl/sed/gsg/mri50_2mph_inc_gumbel_v2.png&quot;&gt;The midwest&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nist.gov/programs-projects/maps-non-hurricane-non-tornadic-extreme-wind-speeds-contiguous-united-states&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;) - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?client=firefox-b-d&amp;amp;q=US+2020+election+results&quot;&gt;A notable republican stronghold area&lt;/a&gt;. NEER&amp;#39;s own wind turbine deployment map in the annual report (p.13) backs up that their expansion is largely in that area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn&amp;#39;t be surprised at all if the Democrats quietly slated a lot of  the renewables spending into the midwest in an attempt to entrench a pro-union and pro-clean energy vote there - forcing the republican platform into a weird spot in future elections. It helps that that&amp;#39;s pretty much the economical way to play it too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sum it up, I think NextEra&amp;#39;s going to be a serious beneficiary of the renewables bill however it ends up going down, even if only because of their financial resources, deployment experience, and contracts with  suppliers. A big portion of this is that I don&amp;#39;t believe the market has  priced in the amount they&amp;#39;re collecting directly and indirectly because  the response so far seems to have been &amp;quot;FAN/TAN/ICLN/QCLN goes brrrrr&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s talk about the competition; The other US utility companies that were  listed as leaders in the clean energy transition by Global Platts are  Dominion Energy, Sempra Energy, and Xcel Energy. From one look at them  it seems like they&amp;#39;re (1) much smaller and (2) at best half off on P/E  so I didn&amp;#39;t really look at them too hard if I&amp;#39;m being honest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for the bigger question; Do I grab NEE or [clean energy ETF of choice]?  Really, it&amp;#39;s up to you. I think that the clean energy ETFs are trading  at downright idiotic valuations now. That, and I&amp;#39;d much rather bet on  one or two known strong performers that I believe in than I would on a  bunch of companies picked by someone else. That being said, those ETFs  have much more hype behind them, which is an important consideration in  this market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short-term catalysts  are basically the stimulus bill and earnings on the 26th. I expect some  big announcements on how they plan to capitalize on the bill during the  earnings call, and a huge bump in interest if they announce that they&amp;#39;re  accelerating their renewables pipeline and focusing on that portion of  the company more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, onto positions and how I&amp;#39;d trade it;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If  you just want to buy and hold in an account for the extreme long-term  -&amp;gt; buy shares and hold, I think this is going to heavily outperform  the S&amp;amp;P 500 into the future.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If  you want to get some of the spicy synthetic leverage gains with me  -&amp;gt; Jan 20 2023 80c&amp;#39;s. They print if the stock goes up ~15% in the  next 2 years because IV is super low. I grabbed 10 at 12.10 at the start  of the week on the dip, but I think they&amp;#39;ll open 13.00+ tomorrow. Keep  in mind that you don&amp;#39;t need to hold till expiry, I&amp;#39;ll probably liquidate  these after a year because I want the tax benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s all from me today! This is my first DD post ever, so if you&amp;#39;ve got any suggestions/questions feel free to fire away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB奧斯特主義者在YOLOing GME後，一夜之間賺足了父母的工資]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwscdd/wsb_austists_after_yoloing_gme_and_making_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwscdd/wsb_austists_after_yoloing_gme_and_making_their/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 12:03:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[億萬富翁共和黨人肯-朗格恩感到 "被背叛"，敦促美國人團結起來支持喬-拜登https://t.co/pLR3OJcHk2。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349416369893347338</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349416369893347338</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 10:16:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Billionaire Republican Ken Langone feels ‘betrayed,’ urges Americans to unite behind Joe Biden https://t.co/pLR3OJcHk2</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CCIV在通往月球的道路上？]]></title><description><![CDATA[CCIV被傳將收購Lucid E/V。雖然Lucid剛剛獲得了其第一
廠家去，它的汽車實際上有一個非常酷的設計（產品看起來是一個很好的設計）。
合法的），其電池壽命比特斯拉多出近100miles，Lucid剛剛發佈了
在他們的網站上有投資者關係總監、SEC......的職位。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwxc9v/cciv_on_the_path_to_the_moon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwxc9v/cciv_on_the_path_to_the_moon/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 10:16:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CCIV has been rumored to be acquiring Lucid E/V. While lucid just got its first factory going, its cars actually have a really cool design (product looks legit), its battery lasts almost 100miles more than Tesla, and Lucid just posted jobs on their website for Director of Investor Relations, SEC reporting manager, and Investor Relations Analyst. It popped today, but if they announce they are taking Lucid public...expect NIO-level jump (4x-5x in a few days)  🚀🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/WSB到花旗。你覺得自己有責任嗎？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwu9hu/rwsb_to_citi_do_you_feel_in_charge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwu9hu/rwsb_to_citi_do_you_feel_in_charge/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 10:16:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[獅子電器。他們是誰，爲什麼你會對他們感興趣？長長的DD帖。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我警告你，這將是一個相當長的閱讀，但你會
希望能感謝我。

又是一天，又是一個EV的遊戲。TSLA和NIO都是電動汽車公司的例子。
利用早早參加聚會所帶來的收益，以獲取更多的利益。
電動汽車。

厲害啊 但有一個整體...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwghg9/lion_electric_who_they_are_and_why_they_should_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwghg9/lion_electric_who_they_are_and_why_they_should_be/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 09:16:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;I warn you that this will be quite the long read, but one that you will hopefully thank me for.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another day, another EV play. TSLA and NIO are both examples of EV companies that have capitalized on the gains resulting from being early to the party for electric cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Awesome. But there is a whole other dimension to the automobile industry other than cars that HAS NOT been electrified yet, and that this company has a first-mover advantage on (just like NIO and TSLA did): &lt;strong&gt;The medium-heavy duty vehicles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I present you with an opportunity to be early to this party featuring the sleeping giant that is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;LION ELECTRIC ($NGA)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is currently trading under the SPAC ticker $NGA with a merger completion set for the end of Q1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;That’s right, by buying 1 share of $NGA right now, you are effectively buying 1 share of Lion Electric. For anyone who wants to better understand SPACs, I highly recommend a quick search on Investopedia.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me preface this post by saying that &lt;a href=&quot;https://thelionelectric.com/en&quot;&gt;Lion Electric&lt;/a&gt; has been working on their vehicles, battery technology, and charging grids since 2010 and ALREADY HAS VEHICLES ON THE ROAD. So no, they are not some shambolic ponzi scheme of an EV company (looking at you NKLA). In fact, it literally has the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/largest-zero-emission-school-bus-fleet-in-north-america-bolstered-by-10-bus-delivery-from-lion-electric-301194935.html#:%7E:text=The%20Lion%20Electric%20Co.&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;text=With%20these%20new%20buses%2C%20Twin,school%20buses%20in%20its%20fleet.&quot;&gt;largest fleet of electified school buses&lt;/a&gt; on the road in North America as we speak. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.thelionelectric.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Investor-Presentation_20203011.pdf&quot;&gt;Here is the link to their investor presentation where they are already forecasting a positive EBITDA by the end of 2021. Highly recommend skimming over it, but I will highlight the main points later on in the post for yall anyways.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;So why haven&amp;#39;t I heard about this &amp;quot;Lion Electric&amp;quot; company?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple answer: it&amp;#39;s a Canadian company located in Quebec. No company outside of America or China can be of interest right? &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;RIGHT????&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Well, the EV credits and subsidies in Quebec are great, but other than that you are right. The good thing is that it ain&amp;#39;t gonna be Canadian-based much longer. Lion is going to reveal its new U.S. manufacturing facility any day now, rumored to be in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/the-lion-electric-co-to-deliver-michigans-first-11-electric-school-buses-as-part-of-the-volkswagen-mitigation-settlement-300917333.html&quot;&gt;Michigan&lt;/a&gt; where it delivered the state&amp;#39;s first ever 100% electric school buses. Lion Electric, in fact, are already &lt;a href=&quot;https://michigan-company.com/co/the-lion-electric-co-usa-inc&quot;&gt;registered as a business&lt;/a&gt; in Michigan. Oh, and it just so happens that the rumored factory location is right in between two Amazon factories, and is not a mere coincidence (see more below on why this is pertinent). Anyhow, their future clearly lies in the United States, and they are uplisting as LEV on the NYSE when the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210104005149/en/Northern-Genesis-Acquisition-Corp.-Announces-Filing-by-The-Lion-Electric-Company-of-a-Preliminary-Registration-Statement-on-SEC-Form-F-4-in-Connection-With-Their-Proposed-Business-Combination&quot;&gt;merger&lt;/a&gt; with NGA closes in March, as per the CEO. Seriously, look at how many job listings are posted across America by Lion Electric by clicking &lt;a href=&quot;https://emploislion.com/en/jobs&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;So, why should I care?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because Jeff Bezos and Joe Biden care.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;News silently broke last week that &lt;strong&gt;AMAZON&lt;/strong&gt; has come to an agreement to purchase up to 500 of Lions class-6 and class-8 delivery trucks per year from 2021-2025 (or up to 2500 over 5 years). Emphasis on &amp;#39;silently&amp;#39; because this company, unlike many, lets their results do the talking rather than a slimy PR team. Oh yeah, I almost forgot to mention that Amazon has the option to purchase at least &lt;strong&gt;2500 trucks per year (conservative number), or 1.1b worth&lt;/strong&gt; for the five years following 2025, with a possibility of acquiring up to &lt;a href=&quot;https://stnonline.com/news/school-bus-production-to-benefit-from-amazon-agreement-lion-electric/&quot;&gt;15.8% of the company&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yup. Amazon are in bed with Lion Electric, and you should be too.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, before anyone asks, the Tesla semi-truck serves entirely different purposes. No point in comparing apples to oranges. Tesla&amp;#39;s truck is specialized for a single purpose: long distance delivery from warehouse to retail. &lt;strong&gt;The Lion-8 and Lion-6 delivery trucks are much more versatile, will be used by Amazon to deliver between Amazon&amp;#39;s facilities, and most importantly they are ready for MASS SCALE PRODUCTION&lt;/strong&gt;. So, no, they are not competing against the Tesla semi and will fill different voids in the market. &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/nJiXzp8&quot;&gt;See here how diversified their truck lineup really is.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;And what about Joe Biden?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sleepy Joe and his Clean Energy Plan have vowed to &lt;a href=&quot;https://thenextweb.com/shift/2020/11/14/what-bidens-environmental-plans-mean-for-electric-vehicles-syndication/&quot;&gt;electrify 500,000 school buses&lt;/a&gt; over the next 4 years&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO COMPANY better positioned to take a huge piece of that pie than Lion Electric. If that seems like a stretch to you, consider this: the CEO of Lion, Marc Bedard, will be speaking at a virtual event on the future of E-mobility this Wednesday (Jan 13), &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.demio.com/ref/vFksZ11nZGvHsaxG&quot;&gt;where the Co-chair of Biden&amp;#39;s Infrastructure Committee will be in attendance&lt;/a&gt;. Their client from Twin Rivers Unified School District went as far as labelling Lion&amp;#39;s electric buses as the &lt;strong&gt;[Rolls Royce and Tesla of school buses]&lt;/strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=StpnGrItO4E&amp;amp;t=45s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=StpnGrItO4E&amp;amp;t=45s&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure many of you will be aware of the merger completed today with Proterra, another electric bus manufacturer. Awesome right? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1820630/000121390021001584/ea133141ex99-2_arclight.htm?fbclid=IwAR0X17En3iZX-fZhuNAneJG2lDvOX_pT-OcKlXVbKWmnAMFtuNbUsrqA4M0&quot;&gt;A real shame that, in their investors presentation, they did not compare their revenue projections to Lion&amp;#39;s past the year 2021, as they would&amp;#39;ve admitted to being second best.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proterra are also exclusively a bus play, while Lion expects nearly 90% of its revenue by 2024 to be from trucks. In fact, Lion&amp;#39;s revenue from their trucks ALONE in 2024 is projected to trump Proterra&amp;#39;s entire revenue in 2025.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, none of these companies have anywhere near the capacity to electrify 25% of the American school bus fleet by themselves in 4 years. So I assure you that Lion will be providing buses to Biden over the next 4 years, as will Proterra probably, since there are only 3 players that are READY in the industry to be in on this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why should I be buying NOW?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because today may very well be the last chance to get in $NGA under 30$.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Cramer is inviting Marc (the CEO) onto &lt;strong&gt;Mad Money&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/ucl54g5avaa61.jpg&quot;&gt;TODAY most likely&lt;/a&gt; after it was initially scheduled last week, but the events in Washington forced a postponement. A blessing in disguise for everyone really, and a final chance to get in before this it takes off. NGA is still trading at a measly 1B valuation, with Amazon ALONE forecasted to purchase more than 1b worth of trucks per year come 2025. Marc is going to pump Lion to the best of abilities on Mad Money, and Cramer is going to eat all of it up, as this company is the real deal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do I know $NGA will get pumped so hard?&lt;/strong&gt; The CEO of Lion featured on a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fm93.com/audio/361623/marc-bedard-pdg-de-lion-amazon-dispose-a-acheter-des-camions-du-producteur-quebecois?fbclid=IwAR1N4Kr0eX-nLjr2-VThUCUVcGIwRlL0ZpC7Abpic7fQY7In4BbJqz7Y7jE&quot;&gt;local news podcast&lt;/a&gt; last week and boasted about the Amazon deal as well as their advantage over competition in electrifying buses and trucks, &lt;strong&gt;comparing Lion to Tesla in the process&lt;/strong&gt;. Unfortunately, he said all of this in French, which I&amp;#39;m sure quite a few of you won&amp;#39;t understand. But once he regurgitates it all in English to Jim Cramer, the significant deal with Amazon and its similarities to Tesla in its infancy will wreak havoc in the market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oh yeah, and, by the way, the last time Cramer hosted a CEO from an up and coming EV merger acquisition (CIIC), that stock went from 21$-37$ in the two following trading sessions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;But why should I pick Lion Electric over all the other EV stocks that get spammed in here?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because Lion Electric offers much more than just prototypes, ideas, and false hopes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· There are currently 7 different &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/L1cu6oS&quot;&gt;trucks and buses&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;available for purchase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· They already have &lt;strong&gt;300+ vehicles on the road&lt;/strong&gt; today with over 
  6mil miles between them &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Multi-year deal agreement for &lt;strong&gt;Amazon&lt;/strong&gt; to purchase up to 
  2500 vehicles (Lion6 and Lion8) 2021-2025, with even bigger 
  and more lucrative opportunities afterwards&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;CN (huge Canadian transporter)&lt;/strong&gt; recently Purchased 50 
  trucks - with a chance to increase size of order later&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;Government-backed&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/xoJ9Kze&quot;&gt;Canada&amp;#39;s prime minister Justin 
  Trudeau supports the company&lt;/a&gt;, 
  while nationalized companies like Hydro Quebec and SAQ have 
  purchase agreements in place that provide a strong foundation 
  for Lion&amp;#39;s business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;Produce their own batteries:&lt;/strong&gt; on top of already having suppliers for their batteries, Lion is 
  building a facility to and immunize themselves against potential shortages as they upscale 
  production, set to be completed in 2022&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;V2G technology&lt;/strong&gt; ready for the batteries, and implemented 
  into their school buses&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Deals with &lt;strong&gt;BMW, ChargePoint, Nuvve, and Romeo Power&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/dFFTczt&quot;&gt;8 NEW vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to be produced between 2021-2022 
  including: Ambulance, bucket truck, Class 5 and Class 7 trucks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/wFbrle5&quot;&gt;USA expansion&lt;/a&gt; completed by 
  2022, will give them a &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;Made in America&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt; image&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· NKLA &lt;em&gt;obviously&lt;/em&gt; had to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2020/12/23/tech/nikola-garbage-truck-%20%0A%20%20canceled/index.html&quot;&gt;scrap their deal on the table with Republic Services&lt;/a&gt; to 
  provide them with up to &lt;strong&gt;5000 garbage disposal trucks&lt;/strong&gt; just a 
  few weeks ago. Who could possibly fill the void and has a ZERO EMISSION
  refuse truck ready for purchase? Lion Electric, that&amp;#39;s 
  who. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lAsNQwjXDP4&quot;&gt;See the truck in action here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;How about their financials??&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/uLp1pf3&quot;&gt;Well, here are their financials and revenue projections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Projected revenue of &lt;strong&gt;3.6 billion $&lt;/strong&gt; by 2024&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;Cash flow positive&lt;/strong&gt; in 2023&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· &lt;strong&gt;EBITDA positive by end of 2021&lt;/strong&gt;, with EBITDA growth of 
  approximately 16% YOY afterwards&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Cost reduction of 50% by 2024 &lt;strong&gt;(better profit margins)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Undervalued EV company tied to Amazon that has product labelled as the &amp;quot;Tesla of school buses&amp;quot;. CEO will appear on Mad Money today most likely, and $NGA will fly past 30$. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;POSITIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/L4gr51J&quot;&gt;Here.&lt;/a&gt; 700 $NGA shares and 1k warrants, with an extra 500 shares in a separate account. Would not recommend options on this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roblox什麼時候上市？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我認識的每一個孩子都會玩這個遊戲，然後求媽媽給他們的信用卡購買
他們寶貴的羅布泊。一旦這隻股票漲停，我就會把所有的錢都投入到這隻股票上
公開。這是我的問題，雖然，任何洞察力，他們將在何時上市？]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwlu3r/when_will_roblox_go_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwlu3r/when_will_roblox_go_public/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 09:16:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every child I know plays this game and begs mommy for their credit card to buy their precious robux. I’m dumping everything into this stock once it goes public. That’s my question though, any insight as to when they will go public ??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一個充滿Lisp的兔子洞]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25760381</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25760381</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 09:16:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽車E - 結束遊戲 🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwuc3a/gme_end_game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwuc3a/gme_end_game/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 07:41:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美聯儲要求特斯拉召回15.8萬輛汽車，原因是觸摸屏顯示屏失效]]></title><description><![CDATA[美國安全監管機構要求特斯拉召回15.8萬輛汽車，因媒體
控制單元故障，導致觸摸屏顯示停止工作。
在美國國家公路交通安全局進行了長達數月的調查後。
管理局。

廳缺陷調查組對我廳缺陷調查工作進行了...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kww5i6/feds_asks_tesla_to_recall_158000_vehicles_over/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kww5i6/feds_asks_tesla_to_recall_158000_vehicles_over/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 07:41:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. safety regulators have asked Tesla to recall 158,000 vehicles over media control unit failures that cause the touchscreen displays to stop working, following a months-long investigation by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Office of Defects Investigation unit of the agency determined that the failure of the media control unit is a safety issue since functions like the backup camera and defogging and defrosting setting controls stop working as well as audible chimes, which are used when the turn signal indicator is activated and to alert drivers while the vehicle&amp;#39;s Autopilot advanced driver assistance system is engaged. Reports of the MCUs suddenly failing have been a topic for years in Tesla forums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The failure is caused when the memory storage in a flash drive used in the used in these vehicles reaches capacity, investigators concluded. The only solution is to replace the physical piece of hardware. Vehicles affected include Model S sedans built between 2012 and 2018 as well as Model X SUVs in 2016 through 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla did not respond to a request for comment. However, the company did provide information to NHTSA, which is contained in the report. Tesla confirmed to NHTSA that all units will inevitably fail given the memory device’s finite storage capacity. Tesla provided its own statistical model showing the number of projected weekly MCU repairs from 2020 to 2028. The automaker estimated that replacement rates for MCU failures will peak in early 2022 and gradually decline until (near) full part turnover has been accomplished in 2028, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These vehicles are equipped with an NVIDIA Tegra 3 processor with an integrated 8GB eMMC NAND flash memory device. Part of this 8GB storage capacity is used each time the vehicle is started. The eMMC NAND cell hardware fails when the storage capacity is reached, resulting in failure of the MCU, the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eMMC NAND flash device&amp;#39;s lifespan based upon the number of program/erase cycles, after which the MCU fails due to memory wear-out. Investigators determined that the expected usage life rating for the 8GB eMMC NAND flash memory device is about 3,000 Program-Erase cycles, after which the eMMC NAND flash memory device would become fully consumed and no longer be operational. At a daily cycle usage rate of 1.4 per block, accumulation of 3,000 P/E cycles would take only 5 to 6 years, the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The agency has officially requested that Tesla initiate a recall to notify all owners, purchasers, and dealers of the subject vehicles of this safety defect and provide a remedy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/feds-asks-tesla-recall-158-000308276.html&quot;&gt;https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/feds-asks-tesla-recall-158-000308276.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[看來BABA又走上了中國政府 "批准 "的軌道了]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好!

大多數人可能還不知道，但精誠證券這是一家國家
價值1500億美元的投資公司，由中國人持有。
政府發表文章稱，他們對BABA的年度目標價。
是330美元，目前約爲237美元/股。

由...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwpjrk/seems_like_baba_is_on_track_again_with_chinese/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwpjrk/seems_like_baba_is_on_track_again_with_chinese/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 07:41:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of you might not be aware of that, but  &lt;strong&gt;Essence Securities&lt;/strong&gt; which is a state owned investment company value at &lt;strong&gt;150B$&lt;/strong&gt; that being held by the Chinese government  published  an article saying that their &lt;strong&gt;yearly&lt;/strong&gt; target price for &lt;strong&gt;BABA&lt;/strong&gt; is &lt;strong&gt;330$&lt;/strong&gt; which is currently at around &lt;strong&gt;237$&lt;/strong&gt; per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By them saying that is actually meaning that they do see these target price as realistic (kinda mean they won&amp;#39;t screw it again).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to remind you, BABA group is making a LOT of money over and is completely profitable, the only thing made their stock go down from 3XX to their current value is the issue with the Chinese government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From this point, &lt;strong&gt;BABA&lt;/strong&gt; stock seems like a completely &lt;strong&gt;GREAT&lt;/strong&gt; stock to place money at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**News&lt;/strong&gt;:** &lt;strong&gt;14/01/21  &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;U.S. Decides Against Investing Ban on Alibaba, Tencent and Baidu&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to the article in the comment section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HN提問：如何提高歐洲SWE的工資？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25766884</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25766884</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 07:41:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[泡沫。VSCode個人知識管理和共享系統]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25760066</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25760066</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:55:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[麥當勞關於如何最好地拯救對話的理論]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25767627</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25767627</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:55:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所有的人都上船了！]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwmn2h/all_aboard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwmn2h/all_aboard/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:01:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我他媽的愛你們]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwmobg/i_fucking_love_you_guys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwmobg/i_fucking_love_you_guys/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 05:02:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[KTOS及其光明的未來]]></title><description><![CDATA[你可能在WSB上看到過一篇與KTOS有關的帖子，來自於另一位
用戶。好了，再經過一番丈量，下面我可以爲KTOS說說。

首先我重複一下其他帖子說的話。最近ARK、黑石、萬科
和富達公司大量買入KTOS的股票，有...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwkztn/ktos_and_its_bright_future/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwkztn/ktos_and_its_bright_future/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 05:02:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might have seen a post the other day on WSB relating to KTOS from another user. Well, after a bit more DD, here is what I can say for KTOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First i&amp;#39;ll repeat what the other post said. Recently ARK, Blackrock, Vanguard and Fidelity have bought a huge number of shares in KTOS, and there is a good reason why. I&amp;#39;ll link to the original post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kvrv7b/cathie_arkbacked_tech_innovator_kratos_defense/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; as it will likely be a more interesting read and im not great at formatting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought i&amp;#39;d look into them and I was pretty pleased with what I saw.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I attended the presentation, and this is what I managed to jot down during the presentation. I&amp;#39;m sure it&amp;#39;ll look very boring, but maybe for you its worth reading. I was taking these down as I was listening, so there may be gaps or misquoted information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Significant invests and won a lot of contracts. Continued investment in 2021 and accelerate in 2022 as these mature to production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Primary Areas&lt;/strong&gt; - Target drones – very high in demand. Lots of contacts are for target drones. Leading high-performance jet target drones. Drones get shot down and then replaced, looking to expand domestically and internationally as new drone requirements are needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Skyborg contract awarded. LCAAT contract awarded, government announced the Valkyrie flew with the F22 and F35 showing they have drones performing missions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next gen engines for drones and cruise missiles – important announcement made to have another contract for Kratos next gen engine for cruise missiles and drones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unmanned drones&lt;/strong&gt; – Gremlin is reusable, only company with a family of these drones (low cost, 400k to 3m). Force multiplies and they’re the market leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Gremlin – govt announced they have multiple customers for the gremlin drones for when it transitions from research team at DARPA. Likely moved to 2022/2023 due to covid and earthquake. Nothing else in the Gremlin, Valkyrie class line aside from Kratos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Space and satellite communication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Biggest business in kratos, leading the industry, supporting ~80% space missions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Thousands of LEO and MEO satellites planned including HBTSS () and TITAN (Tactical Interface Tracking Application Node) program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Microsoft partnered with musk and starlink, AND kratos. Large, new 5G GSaaS beginning. Very low latency and very integral to this. Doing military and commercial, leveraging scale of having both military and commercial, making them competitive as they drive costs down. Very high expectations. High profitability 2022/2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microwave electronics&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Largest independent microwave companies internationally, in support of C5ISR programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Industry seeing increased funding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Kratos typically only provider&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic deterrence&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o GBSD 
 180m contract including significant development systems needed for customer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; New facility with new equipment for this program, production multiple times larger than dev piece, so expect massive investment. 2nd half of 2021, big step up in revenue in 2022. Big growth driver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turbine tech and engines&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Designed into a number of systems, only 2 publicly disclosed (Graywolf and speed racer).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Recently can announce additional funding at low cost cruise missiles and tactical drones. The engine is the largest bill (35%). Want to disrupt the engine market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Number of agencies looking to fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missile defense and hypersonic programs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o One of 2 primary providers for ballistic missile defenses. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Key supporter of the AEGIS programs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financial information&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Drone opportunity expected to transform company soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Space and satellite sector very well positioned and expecting lots of growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Won a number of classified contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o 2021 will be last year of increased internal investments. Heavy investment, but lots of growth after.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Ground based strategic deterrent – multi hundred million contract, significant expenditure on machinery, tools and equipment. In 2021, as they won the contract in 2020, it’ll be a significant CapEx.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Lots of IP movements on engines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o Not taking govt funding for the next gen engines, they’ll eat the costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Will need secure facility with classified environment. Most employees have very high security clearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o 2021 solid growth year, no questions about it. Primary dial on how good this will be is going to be a recompete. If not successful in the recompete, it’s a 35m hole to fill. VERY strong if they get it. If not, the growth won’t be as strong due to this hole. 2022 and 2023 look like step function growth years with lots of contracts maturing to production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o LEO constellations from SpaceX will benefit Kratos. CEO isn’t sure about STARSHIP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;o 70% federal/DoD contracts vs 30% private contracts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[蘋果在macOS 11.2 beta 2中取消了第一方防火牆的豁免。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25771022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25771022</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 05:02:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你總是聽說有人花了1萬比特幣買了幾個披薩。那交易的另一方的人呢？

這些幣現在價值近4億美元。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349512553060323328</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349512553060323328</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 04:07:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You always hear about the person who paid 10,000 Bitcoin for a couple of pizzas. What about the person on the other side of that transaction?

Those coins are now worth almost $400 million.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[插電--你相信它的燃料電池技術嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，根據我的理解--氫氣作爲一種燃料，效率一般較低。
氫燃料的生產和動力的釋放都是能源。
儘管成本較高，但固態電池的耐用性是個問題。
引起的廣泛採用。這有多合理...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwhxww/plug_power_do_you_trust_its_fuel_cell_technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwhxww/plug_power_do_you_trust_its_fuel_cell_technology/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 04:07:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all, based on what I understand - hydrogen is generally less efficient as an energy source - both on the production of hydrogen fuel and the release of power from solid state batteries and durability is an issue, notwithstanding the costs incurred to enable wide-range adoption. How plausible is Plug Power’s technology, when Nikola has shown to also fail in its pursuit of fuel-cell success? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Am hoping for a real answer from a technical person who knows the technology; ideally not looking for meme investors or those with pump and dump strategies. Thanks!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[海盜灣創始人認爲PARLER無法保持在線是 "尷尬的"。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25769730</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25769730</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 04:07:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[上週美國的Covid-19住院人數下降了2%，這是自去年9月以來首次出現周環比下降。https://t.co/HP6FAmLSpN。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349528886200119301</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1349528886200119301</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 03:00:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Covid-19 hospitalizations in the US fell 2% over the last week, the first week-over-week decline since last September.🙏 https://t.co/HP6FAmLSpN</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$URG Uranium play under 1$ before Biden's trillion dollar plan reveal tomorrow + 1/12 Executive Order just signed about nuclear reactors (1)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ur-Energy $URG是一家從事鈾礦開採和回收的礦業公司。
業務，其活動包括收購、勘探、開發和其他活動。
鈾礦財產的運營。近200萬的體量，1.51億的市值。
看看昨天簽署的最新行政命令，...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwm4h9/urg_uranium_play_under_1_before_bidens_trillion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kwm4h9/urg_uranium_play_under_1_before_bidens_trillion/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 03:00:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ur-Energy $URG is a mining company that engages in uranium mining and recovery operations, with activities including acquisition, exploration, development, and operation of uranium mineral properties. Almost 2m in volume, 151m market cap. Check out the latest Executive Order signed yesterday by the US GOV issued yesterday about promoting small Nuclear reactors for national defence &amp;amp; space exploration &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/executive-order-promoting-small-modular-reactors-national-defense-space-exploration/&quot;&gt;https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/executive-order-promoting-small-modular-reactors-national-defense-space-exploration/&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4mj3pqb8n2b61.png?width=2385&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=e3513595c7dd2d2a4ec2b7f9371653a5f1d3067b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/4mj3pqb8n2b61.png?width=2385&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=e3513595c7dd2d2a4ec2b7f9371653a5f1d3067b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s the link to check stats on Finviz:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;utm_source=twitterhttps://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=URG&amp;amp;ty=c&amp;amp;p=d&amp;amp;b=1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is currently listed amongst the top 5 energy plays in these chosen criteria (sorted by lowest price)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/nnwhiluon2b61.png?width=2528&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d6267f24dbe5a158b0f9153abeaac077af749662&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/nnwhiluon2b61.png?width=2528&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d6267f24dbe5a158b0f9153abeaac077af749662&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forecasts have a median estimate of 19% increase from current price, the highest is 1.30$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ev7hmnr9r2b61.png?width=1528&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ddc27a5f1b9b5ac61b09800b5632286c1cf072b2&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/ev7hmnr9r2b61.png?width=1528&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ddc27a5f1b9b5ac61b09800b5632286c1cf072b2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts coverage on CNN has 4 BUY 0 HOLD 0 SELL &lt;a href=&quot;https://money.cnn.com/quote/forecast/forecast.html?symb=URG&quot;&gt;https://money.cnn.com/quote/forecast/forecast.html?symb=URG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/64y7iz2wq2b61.png?width=2075&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bd23b5aa1dcd9640315ff4a87d36942e3e1732d3&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/64y7iz2wq2b61.png?width=2075&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bd23b5aa1dcd9640315ff4a87d36942e3e1732d3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nuclear power backers hopeful Biden&amp;#39;s climate focus will boost industry : &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nuclearpower-energy/nuclear-power-backers-hopeful-bidens-climate-focus-will-boost-industry-idUSKBN29G2AY&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nuclearpower-energy/nuclear-power-backers-hopeful-bidens-climate-focus-will-boost-industry-idUSKBN29G2AY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directly from Joe Biden&amp;#39;s website : &lt;a href=&quot;https://joebiden.com/clean-energy/&quot;&gt;https://joebiden.com/clean-energy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/negn19pro2b61.png?width=1871&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4004da3e6a914763f28ffbd97c30add03f8cb85f&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/negn19pro2b61.png?width=1871&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4004da3e6a914763f28ffbd97c30add03f8cb85f&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Added by the Global X Uranium ETF two weeks ago + BlackRock/Lazarus owning a percentage of the company &lt;a href=&quot;https://fintel.io/so/us/urg&quot;&gt;https://fintel.io/so/us/urg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vanguard bought in November (I know they buy everything but still)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good article on $URG &lt;a href=&quot;https://investorintel.com/sectors/uranium-energy/uranium-energy-intel/ready-for-the-inevitable-change-in-the-market-as-a-secure-domestic-uranium-industry-is-in-the-united-states-best-interest/&quot;&gt;https://investorintel.com/sectors/uranium-energy/uranium-energy-intel/ready-for-the-inevitable-change-in-the-market-as-a-secure-domestic-uranium-industry-is-in-the-united-states-best-interest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;price increase over 60% in Uranium since 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I&amp;#39;ll open up a position and see how it plays out for the next few weeks. Thursday Biden&amp;#39;s trillion dollar plan will be revealed I guess, so everyone is expecting a boost in clean energy related stocks. Need some more info, if you guys find anything negative I&amp;#39;d like to know, the more we research the better. Hope this post was helpful, since $URG has never been mentioned before. update: CEO buying shares last month &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.markets.co/h-c-wainwrights-take-on-this-canadian-energy-stock/288386/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對於那些懷疑通用汽車E。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在今天的整個過程中，你會看到很多增益色情。對於那些
你們誰的紙手，我很抱歉。雖然也許它打開了你的眼睛
意識到WSB運行市場。我們比投資公司更大 因此
還有一齣戲要做。

PLTR. 尚未爆發，卻又保持着...。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwjyhm/for_those_who_doubted_gme/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwjyhm/for_those_who_doubted_gme/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 03:00:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll be seeing a lot of gain porn throughout the entirety of today. For those of you who paper handed, I’m sorry. Although maybe it opened your eyes to realize that WSB runs the market. We’re bigger than investment firms, hence why there’s still a play to be made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLTR. Yet to explode, yet held on by all the same diamond hands of $GME. There’s a presentation at the end of this month for Palantir and it’s for showcasing their technology so shareholders and people who haven’t gotten in yet can better understand the product they’re providing. Although you don’t want to get in after the presentation, you need to get in before. If you think that $GME is exploding, just wait because $PLTR is known by everyone. I’ve even heard random idiots at bars talking about it. The amount of diamond 💎 hands 🖐 in PLTR is catastrophic, there’s no doubt that this company will succeed in the future. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lockup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lockup period is coming to an end, and shareholders will be selling of their stakes. It’s inevitable, but that’s why you make a play on PLTR now because the drive up before lockup will be something extraordinary since shareholders will try to maximize their gains upon lockup ending. Take those GME tendies and put them straight back into the market with good ol’ Palantir.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make some money now, sell before lockup and screw over the shareholders by forcing them to hold their shares once again. The amount of volume upon lockup ending will be tremendous and quite possibly the biggest shit show of 2021. I’m in for the ride and hope you guys are too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Presentation end of month = Drive up in stock price. Lockup in early February = Drive up for shareholders to capitalize their gains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Positions: 400 Shares @ 26.4, 1/15 27c , 1/22 28c&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: 🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我做了一個ETF篩選器]]></title><description><![CDATA[我做了一個ETF篩選器，以幫助我跟蹤哪些行業和產業是。
做得好。

近期表現最好的ETF包括

中消協

CIBR(網絡安全)

XRT(零售)

COPX(全球銅礦公司)

PSCM(小盤材料)

你可以看到完整的ETF列表，在...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwlqt2/i_made_an_etf_screener/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwlqt2/i_made_an_etf_screener/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 03:00:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I made an ETF screener to help me keep track of what sectors and industries are doing well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some recent top performing ETF include&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CHIQ (China Consumer Discretionary)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CIBR(Cybersecurity)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XRT(Retail)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COPX(Global Copper Miners)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PSCM(Small Cap Materials)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;you can see a full list of the ETFs at the following &lt;a href=&quot;https://etf-screener.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/sector.html&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not a web dev and there is probably a bit of jargon used for the noob investor so happy to answer any questions.  Its optimized for my mobile so apologies if it doesnt show up well on your screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a few other screens based on Country (EWY -Korea is at the top of the list ) and Thematic Funds which I consider funds like ARKK and others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If any react developers want to collaborate, please do send a PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[8.8萬的GME收益CANT STOP WONT STOP gamestop。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwijab/88k_in_gme_gains_cant_stop_wont_stop_gamestop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwijab/88k_in_gme_gains_cant_stop_wont_stop_gamestop/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 01:50:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴(BABA) 🚀 🚀]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴股民的好消息。

BABA可能會反彈幾天。

美國人不會被禁止投資阿里巴巴了。
[https://www.wsj.com/articles/americans-wont-be-banned-from-investing-in-alibaba-tencent-and-baidu-11610563890]和
百度]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwr4k5/alibaba_baba/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwr4k5/alibaba_baba/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 01:50:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good News for Alibaba stockholders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BABA will probably rally for a few days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/americans-wont-be-banned-from-investing-in-alibaba-tencent-and-baidu-11610563890&quot;&gt;Americans won&amp;#39;t be banned from investing in Alibaba&lt;/a&gt;and Baidu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME 🚀🚀🚀🚀，我不賣。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwhsto/gme_i_aint_sellin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwhsto/gme_i_aint_sellin/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 01:50:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我一定要讓他們知道現在誰是老大]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwpxn6/i_had_to_let_them_know_who_is_in_charge_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwpxn6/i_had_to_let_them_know_who_is_in_charge_now/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 01:50:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當我將100%的保證金轉入GME股票時，我的保證金是多少？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwjvbm/when_i_yolo_100_margin_into_gme_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwjvbm/when_i_yolo_100_margin_into_gme_shares/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 01:50:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HN提問：我們怎麼知道Signal或Telegram不在他們的服務器上存儲我們的數據？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25764142</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/25764142</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 01:50:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽車E幫 today]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwl4gd/gme_gang_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/kwl4gd/gme_gang_today/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:03:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ARKX太空探索ETF來襲]]></title><description><![CDATA[方舟投資計劃增加一隻 "太空探索ETF"，股票代碼爲ARKX。
根據週三的一份證券文件。

太空探索ETF將重點關注那些 "引領、扶持 "的公司。
或受益於技術功能產品和/或服務的發生。
表面上]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kws3g0/arkx_space_exploration_etf_incoming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/kws3g0/arkx_space_exploration_etf_incoming/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:03:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ark Invest plans to add a “Space Exploration ETF” under the ticker ARKX, according to a securities filing on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Space Exploration ETF would focus on companies that are “leading, enabling, or benefitting from technologically enabled products and/or services that occur beyond the surface of the Earth,” the filing said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/13/cathie-woods-ark-invest-plans-space-exploration-etf-arkx.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/13/cathie-woods-ark-invest-plans-space-exploration-etf-arkx.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1579982/000110465921003837/tm212832d1_485apos.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1579982/000110465921003837/tm212832d1_485apos.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ARKX。ARK投資太空探索ETF。證監會備案以下]]></title><description><![CDATA[剛在微博上看到這個。
https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1579982/000110465921003837/tm212832d1_485apos.htm

Cathie Woods和團隊正在申請太空探索ETF，ARKX。我認爲
顯然，斯普林特PCE將在其中，對其他任何想法？還在經歷
我自己也是醫生

還有任何人...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwr7ef/arkx_ark_invest_space_exploration_etf_sec_filiing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/kwr7ef/arkx_ark_invest_space_exploration_etf_sec_filiing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:03:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just saw this on twitter, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1579982/000110465921003837/tm212832d1_485apos.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1579982/000110465921003837/tm212832d1_485apos.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cathie Woods and team is filing for a Space Exploration ETF, ARKX. I think obvisouly $SPCE will be in it, thoughts on any other? Still going through the doc myself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And anyone jumping on?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>