<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reddit 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit热门内容]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 12:52:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Chewy Due Diligence - I am adding more!]]></title><description><![CDATA[咀嚼式消化器

____________________________________________________________________________________________________________

2020年收入，收入按年增長%。



2020年10月31日 1.78億元 44.9%+ 2020年7月31日 1.70億元 47.31%+ 2020年4月30日 1.62億元
46.17%+ 2020年1月31日 1.35億...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m89ans/chewy_due_diligence_i_am_adding_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m89ans/chewy_due_diligence_i_am_adding_more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 11:24:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;CHEWY DUE DILLIGENCE&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;____________________________________________________________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REVENUE for 2020 with YOY revenue growth %&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Oct. 31, 2020&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.78 bil&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;44.9%+&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;July 31, 2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.70 bil&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;47.31%+&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;April 30, 2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.62 bil&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;46.17%+&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jan 31, 2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.35 bil&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;24.54%+&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;____________________________________________________________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past year has been one hell of a year for this retailer. The pandemic was a driving factor for the growth we saw take place this year with Chewy adding over &lt;strong&gt;5 million new users&lt;/strong&gt;. They reported positive growth quarter after quarter leading up to the pandemic (they were poised for success and executed perfectly), in addition to a hopeful outlook on customer retention moving forward as a result of covid. Who wants to switch back to lugging bags of pet food around? They will also benefit from the generational &amp;quot;trendiness&amp;quot; of the company as they continue to grow and expand their services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Just order from Chewy&amp;quot;. I remember my dad always telling me to &amp;quot;just order from amazon&amp;quot; whenever I wanted something I could not find in stores. He would also advocate for using the service due to their unbeatable prices. The fast delivery was but a bonus as I would have preferred to go to the store and buy my item right away (if it was something I was excited about/wanted). I guess my point here is that pet food really is not all that exciting. It is more of a necessity than a want. If Chewy can compete with in store prices, who in their right mind would go out for pet food? Just order from Chewy and forget about it right? Amazon was but a book store....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;In the works....&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compounding -&lt;/strong&gt; this is service offered by Chewy&amp;#39;s pharmacy where they customize pet medications to meet specific needs of individual pets. Some animals can only take certain medications in a liquid form or require very specific doses or formulations of a particular drug. Their pharmacy will formulate these medications to meet a vets request for a pet and can deliver said formulation for consumption. They plan to eventually offer this service directly to vets so they can offer the service to their &amp;quot;in house&amp;quot; patients. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with a vet -&lt;/strong&gt; pretty self explanatory but has more implications than meets the eye....once they have the ability to consolidate their customers needs into one service, hopefully their own service, I believe the revenue jump will be huge. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Some key figures -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.8% in net sales increase per customer ($363/customer)&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 mil new users added in 2020 (40% increase YOY)&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;25.5 gross margin (increase by 180-basis points as they spend less on customer acquisition and see an increase in brand recognition)&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Cash Flow positive at 32.9 mil compared to -12.8 mil the year before&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Cash from operating activities up to 63.4 mil from only 1.6 mil the year before&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ownership is an interesting topic here. Back in 2019 Chewy was acquired by BC Partners who also owns PetSmart. They own approximately 63% of the company. BC Partners acquired Chewy as a strategic move after seeing revenues slip due to losing market share to the online retailer. Chewy is NOT a subsidiary of PetSmart or vice versa. BC Partners own each of them separately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Analysis - consolidation in the 50-60 price range was very strong...this is where i started my position and have been tracking support and resistance for some time now familiarizing myself with the stocks movements. The price peak back in September to around 75 created a strong level for us to monitor. The 75 resistance was broken, followed by strong price action to the upside. We are now coming back down to test the 75 level for new support before pushing higher. The weekly chart is in play, using the 180/200 ma as a buy level. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chewy was modelled with Amazon in mind. The CEO stated that he used the 1997 letter to shareholders by Jeff Bezos to model the building of his company. This has proven to be very true as they offer 1-2 day delivery for orders over $50, prices beat out brick and mortar stores, the bonuses and discounts for signing up and sticking with them, as well as their expansion into different fields of pet care. Chewy customer service is outstanding, something not even Amazon can compete with for the time being. The personalization is second to none. Chewy also has a 1 year return window vs Amazon&amp;#39;s 1 month window. Chewy&amp;#39;s pharmacy is something Amazon does not have. Amazon may sell flee or tick medications, but they do not fill scripts. With purchase experience varying with Amazon from one experience to the next due to different dealings with vendors and individual sellers, the experience for the customer at Chewy is one Amazon simply can not compete with. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may see some minor pull back in revenues as the 2020 surge may be hard to keep up with. Will this effect the stock price in a negative way? Possibly. But i doubt it. I believe this is being priced in as we speak. The long term outlook does not change. I believe this company will continue to grow over time and will continue to increase their margins and revenues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[蘸醬很好。還有嗎？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7zine/that_dip_was_nice_got_anymore/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7zine/that_dip_was_nice_got_anymore/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:38:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[明天可能會到500，700也許1000，無論如何都要繼續持有，壓榨會持續，至少2周，我們不會錯過那枚火箭]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m83hla/tomorrow_may_go_to_500_700_maybe_1000_keep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m83hla/tomorrow_may_go_to_500_700_maybe_1000_keep/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:38:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我的朋友被告知要買債券。順便說一下，他們20多歲]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的投資教育程度不高的朋友都跟着沃倫-巴菲特傻乎乎的。
建議，他們買債券作爲投資。他們甚至不買債券。
他們買的是BND。我告訴他們，他們的錢最好放在標準普爾指數上
或其他指數基金，但他們不想聽。他們21歲...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m7vh8p/why_the_fuck_are_my_friends_being_told_to_buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m7vh8p/why_the_fuck_are_my_friends_being_told_to_buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:16:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My less investment educated friends are all following warren buffets stupid advice and they are buying bonds as investments. They aren’t even buying bonds. Their buying BND. I’ve told them that their money would be better put in the s&amp;amp;p or another index fund but they don’t want to listen. They’re 21 years old and have no reason to buy bonds but they say that they bring “security” to their portfolio. Btw this is their retirement account that they plan on holding till they’re 60. Can someone talk some sense into them because they don’t want to listen to me even.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[顯示HN：電子遊戲中的字體]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26495059</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26495059</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 08:52:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[顯示HN：用於深度學習的雲GPU--成本只有AWS/GCP的1/3。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26492931</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26492931</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 08:32:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[更新之前關於紙手媽媽的帖子；她告訴我賣掉我的GME，當我漲了20萬美元，所以自然，我做了任何好的弱智會做的事情。我雙雙下跌，損失了95%的投資組合🦍💎🙌🏾🦍🙌🏾💎🥴。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m87vak/update_on_previous_post_about_paperhanded_mom_she/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m87vak/update_on_previous_post_about_paperhanded_mom_she/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 07:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們要先眨眼嗎？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m8248z/we_are_going_to_blink_first/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m8248z/we_are_going_to_blink_first/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 06:59:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在我把100%的投資組合都投入到看漲之後，終於看了公司的資產負債表，發現他們從來沒有盈利過]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m87hkv/finally_looking_at_the_company_balance_sheet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m87hkv/finally_looking_at_the_company_balance_sheet/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 06:28:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[過去25年美債最大修正...

https://t.co/mNNNRh7fEy

數據來源於@ycharts https://t.co/Y12P7QZMNA]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372679473418670087</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372679473418670087</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 05:46:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[問HN：在一天的工作結束後，如何找到精力去研究興趣愛好？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26500021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26500021</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 05:46:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME彭博終端更新 03/18/21 | 終極遊戲即將到來。]]></title><description><![CDATA[歡迎親愛的APES們來到我的最後一次BLOOMBERG更新03/18/21 !

我希望你們都做得很好，併爲明天準備好爆米花。

像上次一樣，我將向你解釋你可以看到的不同的
圖片一步一步的，或者說這裏的圖片一步一步的。

PICTURE...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7yw5z/gme_bloomberg_terminal_update_031821_the_endgame/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7yw5z/gme_bloomberg_terminal_update_031821_the_endgame/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 05:28:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WELCOME FELLOW APES TO MY LAST BLOOMBERG UPDATE ON 03/18/21 !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you&amp;#39;re all doing great and have popcorn nearby for tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like last time, I am going to explain you what you can see on the different pictures step by step, or picture by picture in this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PICTURE 1:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/wgfpkk1s4tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9bf17c0c0a7c6164dbd996fadbb783719340a079&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/wgfpkk1s4tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9bf17c0c0a7c6164dbd996fadbb783719340a079&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first picture, we don&amp;#39;t really see a difference compared to my last screenshots. We see a decline in sellers, which is obviously good, and a small increase of institutional involvement, also good. No negative data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PICTURE 2:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/hzvspcs66tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ed4244b5cd2bcc90c1140300a0a0b9de9d3ac0ef&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/hzvspcs66tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ed4244b5cd2bcc90c1140300a0a0b9de9d3ac0ef&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find it quite funny, that we can see a spanish asset manager buying call options which also expire tomorrow. Just like the idea, that some of the hedgies want other hedgies to be smashed. They don&amp;#39;t really have a huge position and won&amp;#39;t have any big impact on the price of GME. All other options you can see are outdated and the accuracy of these options cannot be granted. Don&amp;#39;t try to speculate, since you cannot tell whether they&amp;#39;re still in or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For all of you who don&amp;#39;t know what call options are, the spanish asset manager bets that the price of GME will be above 200$ tomorrow, which would definitely be amazing for us apes. I am explaining in the following pictures why exactly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PICTURE 3:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/opnh5k177tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bede88f52d218976b6f0cff114ba4ce8fa52d1b1&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/opnh5k177tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bede88f52d218976b6f0cff114ba4ce8fa52d1b1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay so, this is where the important stuff is displayed. We can see that 11,681 options are expiring tomorrow if the price hits 250$, which is currently not the case. (GME at 211$ while I&amp;#39;m writing this DD). This would mean at this point over 2509 call options COULD, not have to, execute tomorrow ~ 250k shares COULD be bought. Keep in mind, that most people don&amp;#39;t execute their calls, but rather just sell them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Important info: I am only taking into account call options from 160$ - 250$ as you can see, since I didnt want to add all the amounts from 100$ to idk where. So you can expect that there are at least over 1000 options expiring aswell at the strike price of 100$. But I know some would argue about this, and this is why I am just calculating with the options shown in the screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SO: If GME hits 250$ by tomorrow over 1,2 mio shares COULD be bought, assuming that all people execute the calls, but this doesn&amp;#39;t really has a huge importance since marketmakers begin to buy shares already in case of someone executes his options. 1,2 mio shares being bought at the same point, or even half of it -&amp;gt; huge price jump. But also 100k or 200k shares would create a price jump and therefore COULD lead to the so-called gamma squeeze (hitting higher stock prices, causing other options to be in the money, and so on). I don&amp;#39;t say that it for sure will cause a gamma squeeze. It just could end up in the situation we&amp;#39;re all striving for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PICTURE 4:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t7m7flh59tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f98da6a0969261cbe0dc220bc4a1ef24ffb4b21b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/t7m7flh59tn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f98da6a0969261cbe0dc220bc4a1ef24ffb4b21b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay so, now we come to the point where you can clearly see why it&amp;#39;s kind of important for GME to be over 200$ by tomorrow. If GME is UNDER 200$ TOMORROW, over 12k put options (1,2 mio shares) CAN be executed, which would cause a price drop. That doesn&amp;#39;t automatically mean that the gamma squeeze possibility is non-existent anymore, but it would definitely mean that we would have to wait for the next expiration date to let it happen. It also doesn&amp;#39;t mean that everyone really executes his options, since like I said, most of them never get executed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we come to the huge BUT part:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IF GME IS ABOVE 200$ TOMORROW, WE HAVE NEARLY NO PUT OPTIONS THAT ARE OF ANY IMPORTANCE ANYMORE. This means, that there would really be no huge downward pressure on the price, outgoing from options, if it starts to rise. You can check this by yourself on other platforms. There are not a lot put calls on GME over the strike price of 200$.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picture 5:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ofxur2biatn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=681866a6b46249f775ac5ddefd2c900cb4135d64&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/ofxur2biatn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=681866a6b46249f775ac5ddefd2c900cb4135d64&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is again very interesting imo, since we can clearly see, that the ETF objectives increased their positions by over 10%. OVER 10% !!! Since Blackrock owns almost 10mio shares which are mostly in ETFs (I KNOW THIS FROM MY OWN BLOOMBERG RESEARCH BUT YOU CAN OFC JUST DONT TRUST ME. THEN IGNORE THE FOLLOWING SENTENCE) , I ASSUME that BLACKROCK (LARGEST ASSET MANAGER IN THE WORLD) is on our side and wants GME to skyrocket. Very good information, so do I think. We also see an overall increase in positions, except from one fund objective, the value fund objective (betting on stocks that are in their opinion undervalued). I know there were a lot of posts about Blackrock being on Citadels site. Which is just as likely. I don&amp;#39;t have more information than you have. But Blackrock is the biggest shareholder of GME and has most of its stocks in ETFS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ETF increase could also just mean that another Hedgefund, not called Blackrock, increased their position in ETFs. Everything is possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last picture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/7mlji2q9btn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=947b90a1993cf426da98ee679e8732a10dfd82e7&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/7mlji2q9btn61.jpg?width=4032&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=947b90a1993cf426da98ee679e8732a10dfd82e7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This really contains no helpful information, but I just want to show you that all short sellers stopped reporting short interest since the 02/26/2021 (When GME started to rise from 40$ on february 22nd to 265$ on march 10th.). Although short interest usually got reported on the 15th each month, we still have no recent reports. Seems a bit sketchy, imo. But this could also just mean nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t want to get anybody buy GME due to my posts, since I am mostly making assumptions here and personally just find it really suspicious. I know we all find the situation really suspicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I THANK EVERYBODY FOR READING THIS AND WHICH ALL OF US GOOD LUCK IN THE WAR! I AM HYPED FOR POWER HOUR AND IF GME IS ABLE TO STAY ABOVE 200$. but keep in mind, we have many evidences, that other HFs are on our side, besides from my assumptions that Blackrock wants GME to skyrocket. Please read other DD&amp;#39;s if you want to have more info about this topic particularly. I can recommend DD&amp;#39;s by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/HeyItsPixel&quot;&gt;u/HeyItsPixel&lt;/a&gt; about this topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HAVE A NICE EVENING EVERYBODY. I LOVE YOU ALL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: Holy shit this really took me an hour to make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: GME DOES NOT HAVE TO CLOSE ABOVE 200$ TOMORROW! THIS ALSO DOESNT MEAN THAT &amp;quot;GME IS OVER&amp;quot; OR SOME SH** IF IT CLOSES UNDER 200. I WILL HOLD MY SHARES UNTIL GME HITS 1 MIL. I DONT CARE IF IT IS TOMORROW, NEXT WEEK, NEXT MONTH OR NEXT YEAR. PLEASE DONT GET THE IMPRESSION THAT I SAID THAT GME HAS TO CLOSE ABOVE A SPECIFIC RANGE&lt;strong&gt;. I WANTED TO SAY THE GAMMA SQUEEZE IS MOST LIKELY TO EXPECT TOMORROW OR MONDAY WHEN GME IS ABOVE 200$ TOMORROW SINCE MOST OPTIONS EXPIRE ON MARCH 19th which is information we already had a long time ago. I held my shares while being at -90% and I will hold them until they&amp;#39;re at +69,420%. My personal opinion.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 2 : My main goal is not to motivate you, promise you anything or predict anything. My intention of my every two-day Bloomberg updates are to show you how the market does and if retail is selling or anything. That’s all. If you’re not interested in my text, don’t read it and just look at the screenshots and make your own opinions. I know, that not all options have to be executed and most of them probably are not being executed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 3: I also did not say that Blackrock IS FOR SURE ON OUR SIDE, but Blackrock is the one having most shares embedded in ETFs. And as you can see, the positions in ETFs increased by 10%. This also COULD MEAN THAT ANOTHER HEDGEFUND OR ASSET MANAGER JUST INCREASED THEIR POSITION!! Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, PLEASE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For real, it just makes me sad that so many people misunderstand me and think &amp;quot;I am one of them&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;trying to say that GME HAS TO CLOSE ABOVE 200$ tomorrow or it crashes&amp;quot; or say that I said &amp;quot;all options are for sure being exectued&amp;quot;. I never said such things and that was never my intention. I am not going to make any more updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IF GME ABOVE 200$ PREPARE FOR LIFTOFF. IF UNDER: GET YOUR MONEY TOGETHER CUZ ITS A FIRE SALE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the credit goes to &lt;a href=&quot;/u/Bullmarket_chaser&quot;&gt;u/Bullmarket_chaser&lt;/a&gt; who couldn&amp;#39;t post the original DD on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/wallstreebets&quot;&gt;r/wallstreebets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check the original DD here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/GME/comments/m7usgx/final_bloomberg_update_on_031821_the_endgame_is/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/GME/comments/m7usgx/final_bloomberg_update_on_031821_the_endgame_is/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資於非上市公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，我有一些親密的朋友誰創辦了這個相當成功的公司幾
幾年前。經過媒體的一番熱議，一些相當重量級的玩家投資我。
我想我也會伸出手，看看我是否能加入。因爲我不是什麼百萬富翁
這將是我爲數不多的幾次能參與的機會。I…]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m85fyo/investing_in_nontraded_company/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m85fyo/investing_in_nontraded_company/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 05:28:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I have a some close friends who started this quite successful company a few years ago. After some buzz in media with some quite heavy players investing I thought I&amp;#39;d reach out too see if I could join in. Seeing as I&amp;#39;m no millionaire this will be one of the few times I&amp;#39;m able to particiapte. I belive in their business model bigly and honestly think they have a very good chance of succeeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now I&amp;#39;ve only invested in stocks and mutual funds so when it comes to investing in privately-held companies what pitfalls and financial key metrics should I look at / ask them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company today:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current outstanding shares: 6m&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implied equity value: 23m USD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are about to initiate another round of funding, this will be a large round where they are trying to raise 440m USD since they are scaling up substatntionally from local to national distribution and sales in order to supply demand , if sucessfull it will change the numbers to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding shares: 15.5m&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Estimated valuation: 440m USD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Estimated earnings/projections look good but what specific answers should I ask them before jumping the gun and what key metrics should I try and calculate?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[構建Async Rust的共同願景]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26503809</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26503809</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:46:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何設計程序]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26493990</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26493990</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:46:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[她只帶着300美元來美國留學--現在她是NASA局長了]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26509062</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26509062</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:46:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[4100張PUT合約，很笨，但我相信我把下一次市場暴跌的範圍縮小到本週。明天就是我虧損1萬的日子，否則我就會隨着暴跌變成百萬富翁，把所有的東西都捲進GME。🚀 💥]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m862k3/4100_put_contracts_pretty_dumb_but_i_believe_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m862k3/4100_put_contracts_pretty_dumb_but_i_believe_i/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:22:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我認爲$GME依然牛氣沖天，走向月球？]]></title><description><![CDATA[同胞們，我知道你們中的許多人，包括我在內，都經歷過一些艱難的日子。
和小時。你們中的許多人甚至可能已經停止了喫蠟筆，或者更糟糕的是：賣了
你的$GME股票損失慘重。

我想利用這個機會告訴大家，並不是所有的事情都會失去。沒有什麼是失去的
直到你賣掉！）。的...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7ya85/why_i_think_gme_is_still_bullish_and_going_to_moon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7ya85/why_i_think_gme_is_still_bullish_and_going_to_moon/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:22:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fellow apes, I know many of you, me included, have been through some tough days and hours. Many of you might even have stopped eating crayons or worse: sold your $GME stocks with huge losses. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to use this chance to tell you that not all is lost. Nothing is lost (until you sell in fact!). Of course I have no idea what I&amp;#39;m talking about - I&amp;#39;m really no one to trust in financial advice, so be aware. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But still I am using all these fancy indicators and am wondering why everyone is complaining. Trends in stocks need corrections, that&amp;#39;s basic DOW-theory. And how much do they correct in general? A 0.5 Fib-retracement correction is very usual in almost all trends. They even sometimes correct a fib-retracement below. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when you&amp;#39;re looking at my chart now (very fancy, colors!, buy!) you will see that we&amp;#39;re pretty exact around that retracement now. Furthermore price tried to go under EMA50 but directly went up again to the exact position of EMA50. Where are we now?  Correct, almost at EMA50 but NOT below. This is a hell of a resistance and we&amp;#39;re not letting it fall below my fellow apes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore EMA100 and EMA200 are still showing upward movement, which is also good. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not least MACD aims for its zero-line and might turn positive. You ask when? Hm, if you look at the MACD trend it might be tomorrow, Friday 03/19 (and we are all hoping for a beginning squeeze on that day, don&amp;#39;t we?!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, from my perspective everything is still fine. For disclosure, I&amp;#39;m stuck in the upper 300s in GME, and I won&amp;#39;t sell before we reach at least four digits! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL:DR: Trend is still fine, EMA50 is holding like a son of a bitch and we should see some upward movement tomorrow, Friday 03/19 or coming Monday. I like the stock and you should like it too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/rwn267m02un61.png?width=2091&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=09182b5399332de89d5a0db97254e1762fad8278&quot;&gt;My technical analysis on $GME&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新不倫瑞克省監測到40多例不明神經系統疾病。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26503284</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26503284</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:22:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[稅額和如何使用稅額，更好的解釋... ...]]></title><description><![CDATA[> FIFO(先進先出) ----> 先賣出您最老的股票。
> 
> LIFO（後進先出）----> 先賣出您最近買入的股票。
> 
> 最高成本 ----> 先賣出成本最高的股票。
> 
> 低成本----> 以最低的平均價格先賣出你的股票。

美元...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m86yjx/tax_lots_and_how_to_use_them_better_explained/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/m86yjx/tax_lots_and_how_to_use_them_better_explained/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 03:57:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FIFO (first in first out)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;----&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Sells your oldest shares first  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LIFO (last in first out)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;----&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Sells your most recently purchased shares first  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highest Cost&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;----&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Sells your shares with the highest cost basis first  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low Cost ----&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Sells your shares with the lowest average first &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dollar cost averaging is key when accumulating shares of a particular company. This process becomes completely thrown off the moment we start to sell at a profit IF we are limited to FIFO only. Below I will illustrate the necessity of utilizing alternative tax lots.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy 100 DKNG at 35&lt;/strong&gt; on 11/02 (loading up on a long term position) $3500  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy 100 DKNG at 45&lt;/strong&gt; on 1/05 (adding to long term position) $4500  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total - $8000&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy 100 DKNG at 55&lt;/strong&gt; on 2/23 (adding for swing trade) $5500  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy 100 DKNG at 60&lt;/strong&gt; on 3/05 (adding for swing trade) $6000  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total - $11,500&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First thing to note is we currently would have an average price of 48.75. Lets say DKNG runs to 80 for the sake of our example. The price is now $80 and we would like to begin taking profits. Note that we are trading around a core long-term position. By unloading shares, we are also unloading risk. We want to unload the riskiest shares first. By doing this, we are able to hold on to our oldest and also our cheapest shares (the lot purchased at 35 and 45). We will sell 200 shares at 80 using the Highest Cost method. This will sell all 200 shares purchased at 55 and 60. We would lock in $4500 in profit and would see our average lower to 40 as we no longer own shares at 55 or 60. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With $4500 locked in profit, we have effectively lowered our cost for the remaining shares from 8k to 3500. We can do this over and over until the position is free. Obviously if you blow the profits on another ticker it will not work this way. I like to roll the profits back in to the same ticker on a nice dip and repeat the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had we been using the FIFO tax lot method, we would have been forced to sell our shares averaged at 35 and 45 first. Sure this would lock in a slightly larger gain, but it would also inch up your cost basis to 57.50. Every time you do this, you raise your average and your risk becomes greater. For a long term hold you want to keep the best average possible. This keeps your risk low. By selling your most expensive shares first, you will always be passing that risk along to someone else at a profit and will remain exposed to the asset you wish to own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[顯示HN：LitiHolo--桌面3D全息圖打印機，可以製作真正的全息圖。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26503715</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26503715</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 03:56:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2008年 "股災 "時的那些人在哪裏，你還記得復甦的情緒嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不聲稱自己是這個市場的熊或牛。我只是隨波逐流
但我從媒體和公衆那裏得到的一些感覺，讓我想起了很多。
2008年的危機。好吧，更多的是危機後的復甦。我可能是
今天交易的reddit用戶平均年齡，當它發生....。]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m81rlu/where_are_those_who_were_around_for_the_2008/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m81rlu/where_are_those_who_were_around_for_the_2008/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 03:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do not claim to be a bear or a bull in this market. I am just along for the ride but some of the feel I get from the media and the public remind me a lot of the 2008 crisis. Well more so the recovery from the crisis. I was probably the age of the average reddit user trading today when it happened. FYI it was much harder to get into trading (and expensive) back then... make sure to appreciate the time you are living in! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I remember was that when the fed stepped in and started handing out money everyone was dropping the word &amp;quot;hyperinflation.&amp;quot; It was the first time I had heard of it and I had to figure out what it meant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also cut interest rates in half and the theme was &amp;quot;it is only a matter of time before they came back.&amp;quot; I bought a house in 2011 and my loan officer was pushing me to hurry before interest rates went higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They started this &amp;quot;quantitative easing&amp;quot; for the stock market where the government dumped money in so it would move up &amp;quot;artificially.&amp;quot; This is how it was explained to me at the time and why people started talking about the bubble building that was going to &amp;quot;pop&amp;quot; in the stock market as it recovered to it&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;pre-crisis&amp;quot; levels. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I think back to the &amp;quot;sentiment&amp;quot; of the financial crisis I see a lot of the same things today but it is all compressed into a much shorter time frame now. It also has this &amp;quot;double down&amp;quot; feel. Interest rates didn&amp;#39;t ever recover and were cut in half yet again during the covid crisis. The fed is printing far more money then they did back then (though the bail outs were huge). I don&amp;#39;t think they ever really stopped (someone else can clarify) injecting money into the economy. I also would like to note that inflation didn&amp;#39;t &amp;quot;get out of control&amp;quot; but it sure seems things are much more expensive even though the numbers they follow don&amp;#39;t show that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR These are the things that come to my mind from watching CNBC everyday after work during the financial crisis. The worries of then seem to be similar to the worries of today but they didn&amp;#39;t actually play out back then. At the same time it seems we never got &amp;quot;back to where we were&amp;quot; when you consider the fed&amp;#39;s involvement after 2009. They seem to be perpetually stuck injecting money and keeping rates low. Whenever they try to step away the market throws a tantrum and they come back. Can anyone else make some comparisons as to how this time is different or possibly the same? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus Question: Are any signs of a weak economy always going to be the responsibility of the fed to fix it? (More in reference to 2018-2019 than the covid crash.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這些新的非開源許可證是怎麼回事？]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26504021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26504021</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 02:59:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大猩猩捐款現已超過35萬美元]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7y89q/gorilla_donations_have_now_exceeded_350000/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7y89q/gorilla_donations_have_now_exceeded_350000/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 02:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是多麼整潔的。他們非常喜歡我們對大猩猩的支持，爲了感謝我們，他們給我們做了一件💎🙌🦍襯衫。我也爲自己訂了一件]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m82cvd/how_neat_is_this_they_loved_our_support_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m82cvd/how_neat_is_this_they_loved_our_support_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 02:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[列表中的書籍閱讀，如果你想真正成爲知識的股票，而不是停留在一個常態，不知道他們在做什麼的人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我要給大家打一些知識，所以要穿好你的大童褲! 你
應該按順序閱讀這些書，因爲它們堆積在一起。
的頂層，而要了解其中的經驗教訓，就必須要瞭解
在下的教訓。

聲明：本人不是理財顧問...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m85sp6/list_of_books_to_read_if_you_want_to_actually/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m85sp6/list_of_books_to_read_if_you_want_to_actually/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 02:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m about to hit you all with some knowledge, so get your big kid pants on! You should read these books in the order they are listed, because they stack up on top of each other and the lessons learned in one are needed to understand the lessons in the next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor or registered securities analyst.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let&amp;#39;s begin:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Little Book of Common Sense Investing by John Bogle&lt;/strong&gt; - For those of you who don&amp;#39;t know, John Bogle is one of the most important people to ever walk this planet when it comes to stocks and investing for the average person. He founded a little company called Vanguard (ever heard of it?) and he also invented the first index fund. In this book, Bogle gives us a primer on the classical approach to passive, conservative and long-haul investing. He goes into the statistics on how around 90% of mutual funds and most people can not beat the market. He makes it clear and simple that if you want to benefit from stock yields over time, you should deploy your money into index funds and sit back while earnings and dividends carry you to wealth. Many people (probably most people to be honest) can stop here and honestly do perfectly fine. The info in this book is all you need to build serious wealth. You will also understand the theory that picking individual stocks is usually a &lt;em&gt;losers game&lt;/em&gt;. If you aren&amp;#39;t content with boring old index fund investing though, read on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One Up On Wall Street by Peter Lynch&lt;/strong&gt; - This book is dated but the principles written in its pages ring true to this day. Peter Lynch is considered one of the most successful mutual fund managers of all time. He achieved returns that beat the S&amp;amp;P 500 for over a decade straight for his investors in the Fidelity Magellan Fund in the 70&amp;#39;s and 80&amp;#39;s. Yes I know I said most people can&amp;#39;t beat the market by picking stocks, which is why those who can do it consistently are very special. In this book he teaches you about the tools and strategies he used to achieve those results. It&amp;#39;s a great book because it doesn&amp;#39;t get too crazy in terms of math and logic, and it&amp;#39;s easy to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thinking, Fast and Slow by Daniel Kahneman -&lt;/strong&gt; Now it&amp;#39;s time to take a break and get into the &lt;em&gt;psychology&lt;/em&gt; behind stock investing. Let&amp;#39;s be honest, we&amp;#39;re all pretty stupid and we all have internal biases. These two facts can be serious roadblocks to investing success. The sooner you admit that the better off you&amp;#39;ll be. This book will help you understand how to separate your irrational mind from your rational mind when investing and it will make you better at objective decision making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, now at this point you have two paths you can take. After these three books you&amp;#39;ll have a good grasp on the &lt;em&gt;theory&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;mindset&lt;/em&gt; to making money in stocks, but you will be lacking the knowledge to actually &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;pick individual stocks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. I mean how are you supposed to do that? Just buy whatever is trending on Reddit or what that idiot Jim Cramer on CNBC is talking about? Well as long as you still understand (from book #1) that the odds are against you when picking stocks, you can continue on one of two paths:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- The Value Investing Path&lt;/strong&gt; (Finding, analyzing and buying stocks that are &amp;quot;undervalued&amp;quot; and waiting for them to rise back to their fair market value, thus making a ton of money. This is what Warren Buffett does. It&amp;#39;s also extremely difficult, boring and requires &lt;em&gt;rock-solid&lt;/em&gt; emotional stability to ignore the ups and downs of the market.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-OR-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- The Traders Path&lt;/strong&gt; (Following market trends and sentiment to find opportunities that can make you money. I personally would not consider this path to be an &amp;quot;investors&amp;quot; path. This is a &amp;quot;speculators&amp;quot; path, and they are very different. However, you can make money speculating. This could involve shorting stocks or doing a bit of technical analysis, or maybe even playing with some derivatives like options. This path is also extremely difficult and will cause most people to lose &lt;em&gt;hours&lt;/em&gt; of sleep each night sweating as they panic about their positions)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you chose &lt;strong&gt;The Value Investing Path&lt;/strong&gt;, continue here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All of the accounting books you can find&lt;/strong&gt; - You NEED to understand the fundamentals of accounting in order to value businesses. There is no getting around it. Yes, it&amp;#39;s boring but if you find yourself enjoying it, you may have an inclination for this. Read everything you can on accounting. Learn to read balance sheets, income statements and cash flow statements. Learn about assets and liabilities. Do the practice assignments in the books and all of that!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Intelligent Investor by Benjamin Graham -&lt;/strong&gt; This is probably the most famous book on this list, and guess what, you&amp;#39;re not going to understand ANY of it. This is the book that Warren Buffett swears by. In fact, Buffett studied with the author of this book when he was a lad. This book is the bible of value investing. Every successful investor knows this book. Within its pages you will learn about what to look for in the stock market, how to understand market behavior, what a good business looks like, how to find the &lt;em&gt;intrinsic value&lt;/em&gt; of a company, and much much more. I recommend reading this book at least twice and researching everything inside it that you don&amp;#39;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Margin of Safety by Seth Klarman -&lt;/strong&gt; Physical copies of this book are extremely expensive, so you&amp;#39;re better off finding an online copy (shh don&amp;#39;t tell). It&amp;#39;s a bit more modern than the title above and it was written by a very successful value investor!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Dhando Investor by Mohnish Pabrai&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;-&lt;/strong&gt; Fantastic value investing book that offers some fresh ideas and new things to think about that are built on top of the previous books. Also written by a very successful investor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you chose &lt;strong&gt;The Traders Path&lt;/strong&gt;, continue here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reminiscences of a Stock Operator by Edwin Lefèvre&lt;/strong&gt; - A classic that most traders are told to read at some point in their lives. It teaches so many valuable lessons of reflecting on your wins/losses, psychology of trading, knowing yourself and your weaknesses and more fun stuff. It&amp;#39;s an old book but definitely worth reading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting Started in Technical Analysis by Jack Schwager&lt;/strong&gt;  - If you don&amp;#39;t know, technical analysis (TA) is the process of finding opportunity by analyzing the market indicators such as price, volume and trends. It ignores company fundamentals and is often seen as a type of voodoo that you either believe in or you don&amp;#39;t. I personally am not a fan, however I do recognize the importance TA plays in understanding some stocks at certain times. I do believe that in combination with other metrics, TA can provide valuable insight. This book will teach you the basics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fooled by Randomness by Nassim Nicholas Taleb -&lt;/strong&gt; It is not possible to predict the stock market. This book will help you reconcile with that. It will help with understanding how randomness and a bit of luck ties into not only your trading, but your whole life. You will learn about risks and the consequences of taking them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market Wizards by Jack Schwager&lt;/strong&gt; - Another great book by the same author as #2 above. This is written in a sort of conversation-like format where the author interviews some of the most successfully traders of the time. There is tons of information in this book on all of the topics we&amp;#39;ve discussed since it&amp;#39;s like you&amp;#39;re reading a conversation between two people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this post will help some of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Honorable mentions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The Snowball - Alice Schroeder&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Security Analysis - Benjamin Graham and David Dodd&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- A Random Walk Down Wall Street - Burton Malkiel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The Alchemy of Finance - George Soros&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The Big Short - Michael Lewis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits - Philip Fisher&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Value Investing: From Graham to Buffett and Beyond - Bruce Greenwald&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[可視化地表現了我買任何股票時的情況。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m82xo7/visual_representation_of_what_happens_when_i_buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m82xo7/visual_representation_of_what_happens_when_i_buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 02:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["等全家人都睡了，我再做2個小時的捲曲開發。"]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26505303</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26505303</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 02:39:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有時候很容易理解爲什麼很多普通人會被市場所迷惑。

你覺得現在最大的風險是什麼？

嗯，我們擔心經濟會過於強勁

你是說太弱了吧？

不，不是太強。相信我，這是一個東西]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372590634733858816</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372590634733858816</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 01:59:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天2021年3月18日星期四的市場回顧。]]></title><description><![CDATA[股市週四下跌，此前一天創下紀錄高位，因爲財政部。
收益率再次上升，點燃了科技股的再次重挫。此外，一
新報告還顯示，美國去年首次申請失業救濟金人數意外上升。
本週。標普500指數（SPY）收跌1.44%，科技重...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m80afu/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_march/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m80afu/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_march/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 01:59:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stocks fell Thursday after reaching record highs a day earlier as the Treasury yields rose again, igniting another heavy pullback in tech stocks. Moreover, a new report also showed US first-time unemployment claims unexpectedly rose last week. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) closed 1.44% lower, the tech-heavy Nasdaq&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rising Treasury yields hurt high-growth companies, like tech stocks, the most because these companies require a large amount of capital to fund their growth and usually generate most of their earnings years down the line. Higher Treasury yields make it more expensive to borrow capital decreases the value of future cash in today&amp;#39;s dollars as rates increase partly because investors have more opportunity to earn bigger returns from assets paying higher interest and dividends right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Federal Reserve reiterated its commitment to maintaining interest rates near zero and asset purchase program at a pace of $120 billion per month in place for the foreseeable future, even as the US economy shows signs of gaining momentum thanks to an increase in the pace of vaccination and the recently passed stimulus package. FOMC members now expect the unemployment rate to dip to 4.5% by the end of this year with an inflation rate of 2.4%. Three months earlier, the Fed expected an unemployment rate to improve to only 5.0% with core personal consumption expenditures rising by just 1.8% by year-end. Real GDP growth will likely come in at 6.5% this year, the Fed projected, up sharply from its previous 4.2% growth forecast. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell reiterated that the central bank would tolerate some overshooting of its inflation and employment targets as the economy makes strides in recovering, and would keep monetary policy loose until more data confirms the economy is back on track.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Federal Reserve’s assessment of the economy helped allay concerns of a rapid rise in inflationary pressures forcing the Central Bank to tighten restrictions sooner-than-expected. Seema Shah, Chief Strategist at Principal Global Investors, wrote in an email to Yahoo Finance, “The Fed certainly gave the market some meat to chew on, raising its economic growth forecast for 2021 significantly to 6.5%. The implication of this projection is that, at some point in 2022, U.S. GDP will exceed its pre-pandemic path. Despite this very strong outlook, the Fed played down the risk from inflation, with their projections showing a very modest and, importantly, only temporary overshoot of their 2% target – certainly a more subdued inflation outlook than many investors were fearing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of March 17, 73.7 million Americans—22.2% of the total population, and 28.5% of those 18 and older—had received at least one dose of a COVID vaccine, according &lt;a href=&quot;https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#vaccinations&quot;&gt;to data&lt;/a&gt; from the Centers for Disease Control. That’s up from 62.5 million a week ago. 40 million Americans, or 15.5% of the total adult population has been fully vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Labor released their weekly unemployment report.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial jobless claims, week ended March 13:&lt;/strong&gt; 770,000 vs. 700,000 expected and an upwardly revised 725,000 during the prior week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuing claims, week ended March 6:&lt;/strong&gt; 4.124 million vs. 4.034 million expected and 4.144 million during the prior week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs on Thursday raised its forecast for the adoption of battery electric vehicles in the U.S saying, “We now expect battery electric vehicles to comprise 20% of U.S. sales in 2025, 40% in 2030, 60% in 2035, and 75% in 2040.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. crude oil prices dropped for a fifth straight session on Thursday, giving back recent gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Motion Picture Association, the number of subs to video streaming services grew to 1.1 billion in 2021. In that time, box office revenues were down $30 billion in the year to $12 billion as movie theaters were shut down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, the U.S. Department of Commerce is hosting a closed-door virtual meeting with miners and battery manufacturers to discuss ways to boost Canadian production of EV materials, according to documents seen by Reuters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written in the morning and does not reflect intraday movement*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accolade (ACCD) target raised by Canaccord Genuity from $59 to $62 at Buy. Stock currently around $47&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alliance Data Systems (ADS) target raised by Oppenheimer from $85 to $130 at Outperform. Stock currently around $117&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ascendis Pharma (ASND) target raised by Canaccord Genuity from $172 to $190 at Buy. Stock currently around $144&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Docusign $DOCU target raised by Morgan Stanley $MS from $280 to $290 at Overweight. Stock currently around $213&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOMO with two target raises. Stock currently around $65  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Morgan Stanley (MS) from $70 to $76 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needham &amp;amp; Co from $85 to $91 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fate Therapeutics (FATE) target raised by SVB Leerink from $88 to $121 at Outperform. Stock currently around $92&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;JD.com&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24JD&amp;amp;src=cashtag_click&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;(JD)target raised by HSBC from $103 to $108 at Buy. Stock currently around $85&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kohl&amp;#39;s (KSS) target raised by Jefferies Financial Group from $66 to $71 at Buy. Stock currently around $61&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lennar (LEN) with two target raises. Stock currently around $101  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BTIG Research from $104 to $117 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JMP Securities from $90 to $120 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Novavax (NVAX) target raised by HC Wainwright from $207 to $317 at Buy. Stock currently around $225&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pinduoduo&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PDD&amp;amp;src=cashtag_click&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;(PDD) target raised by Benchmark from $150 to $176 at Buy. Stock currently around $150&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Royal Caribbean (RCL) target raised by UBS Group from $79 to $116 at Buy. Stock currently around $91&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teleflex (TFX) target raised by Raymond James from $460 to $480 at Strong-Buy. Stock currently around $416&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;ULTA Beauty (ULTA) with three target raises. Stock currently around $319  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barclays from $298 to $361&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wells Fargo from $330 to $356&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Suisse from $208 to $350&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In my view, the biggest investment risk is not the volatility of prices, but whether you will suffer a permanent loss of capital. Not only is the mere drop in stock prices not risk, but it is an opportunity. Where else do you look for cheap stocks?” - Li Lu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME供應不足...]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m81b2a/gme_supply_running_low/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m81b2a/gme_supply_running_low/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 01:01:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球央行最新消息。
-巴西2015年以來首次加息，加息75個基點至2.75%。
-土耳其自去年9月以來第4次加息，加息200個基點至19.0%。https://t.co/LuSQqy1slo。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372603492695748608</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372603492695748608</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 23:35:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你在賣出，別人在買入--股市真傻]]></title><description><![CDATA[是什麼讓我有點笑的是在紅色的日子裏，當人們賣掉在說的。
納斯達克，並將他們的資金轉移到週期性股票，因爲一些壞消息和。
然後在第二天把它搬回納斯達克！

我一直不明白這是怎麼回事。所以今天的失業申請是
高過]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m806na/youre_selling_and_someone_else_is_buying_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m806na/youre_selling_and_someone_else_is_buying_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 23:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes me sort of chuckle is on red days when people sell off in say the Nasdaq and move their money into cyclical stocks because of some bad news and then on the next day move it back to the Nasdaq!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could never understand what&amp;#39;s going on here.  So today jobless claims were higher than expected, so the Nasdaq sells off and people put their money in the &amp;#39;re-opening&amp;quot; stocks.  WHY?!  Then the next day or two or week everything reverses!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s like musical chairs or something.  What the hecks the point?!  Also what makes it really stupid is that when someone is selling because of bad news someone else is buying the same bad news!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So people are selling because they think BECAUSE of bad news their stocks will go down and so consequently those same sellers are all driving the price down by selling!  Makes a lot of sense! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So everyone panics and sells because they think everyone else is going to panic and sell and so everyone sells.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the funniest part is that a few days later everyone buys right back in again!  Talk about dumb!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以205元的價格購買100股的FIGHT $GME。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://preview.redd.it/xm7ryrunqtn61.png?width=808&format=png&auto=webp&s=c4fb38ef9bcfc8d65f1ee9c64964b97b5c45f186]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7wh16/100_shares_for_the_fight_gme_at_205/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7wh16/100_shares_for_the_fight_gme_at_205/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 23:15:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/xm7ryrunqtn61.png?width=808&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c4fb38ef9bcfc8d65f1ee9c64964b97b5c45f186&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/xm7ryrunqtn61.png?width=808&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c4fb38ef9bcfc8d65f1ee9c64964b97b5c45f186&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當你的鑽石手擔心Cramer對GME的看法可能是對的，請看一下這個視頻。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7q85a/when_your_diamond_hands_fear_cramer_could_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7q85a/when_your_diamond_hands_fear_cramer_could_be/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 23:15:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場休市。
 
✧ S&amp;P 500 △ 0.29%。                  
✧ Nasdaq △ 0.40%。             
✧羅素2K △ 0.73%                   
✧ 道瓊斯 △ 0.58% https://t.co/DUERY5yJvD。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372276968205512706</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/tweet/1372276968205512706</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:41:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在我們的環節處理中，我們發現並解決了一個罕見的比賽狀況。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26506920</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26506920</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:41:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[猩猩一起強🚀🚀。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7zgff/apes_together_strong/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7zgff/apes_together_strong/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[看來我們有一個好的老式盯着我們了]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7ybhx/looks_like_we_have_ourselves_a_good_old_fashioned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7ybhx/looks_like_we_have_ourselves_a_good_old_fashioned/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼人們似乎總是說市場很快就會崩潰？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道現在市場被高度高估的論調，而且有。
很多 "容易 "的錢進入股票。但似乎總有一些人
爲可能即將發生的車禍敲響警鐘。回溯到2016年，我
記得很多人都說房地產有泡沫。但是...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m7yebl/why_do_people_always_seem_to_be_saying_the_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/m7yebl/why_do_people_always_seem_to_be_saying_the_market/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know the arguments that the market is highly overvalued right now and there is a lot of &amp;quot;easy&amp;quot; money going into stocks. But it seems there are always people sounding off alarms about possible imminent crashes. Going back to 2016, I remember many people saying that real estate was in a bubble. But housing prices have kept going up relentlessly. But now I see a lot of big names in investing saying the market will crash, from Charlie Munger, Ray Dalio, Warren Buffet, etc. are all saying markets are unreasonably high. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it normal for there to be so many doom preachers or is there really something to worry about for the near future?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[諷刺的是，我的個人博客使用Kubernetes。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26502900</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26502900</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:21:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所有《未來之城》開篇語錄]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26506447</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/hn/26506447</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 22:21:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME: 冷靜點！價格一直在盤整! 在月初的暴漲之後，價格從黃金比率（61.8%）反彈，在向上突破之前，在110-130美元之間盤整。現在，(歷史重演)看起來是在200-220美元之間盤整，然後向上。不是理財建議!]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7v0qy/gme_chill_prices_consolidate_all_the_time_after/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7v0qy/gme_chill_prices_consolidate_all_the_time_after/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[而DFV讓更多的人買... 🚀。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7cn3z/and_dfv_made_more_buying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7cn3z/and_dfv_made_more_buying/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GUH。100萬美元的電話更新。白癡繼續讓看θ怪獸破壞看漲期權價值。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7cu2w/guh_1m_in_calls_update_idiot_continues_to_let/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7cu2w/guh_1m_in_calls_update_idiot_continues_to_let/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg利用Robinhood無限槓桿的缺陷，對AAPL財報進行OTM看跌，GUH。]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7py5v/snoop_dogg_using_robinhood_infinite_leverage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7py5v/snoop_dogg_using_robinhood_infinite_leverage/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DFV的例子的重要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[u/DeepFuckingValue[https://www.reddit.com/u/DeepFuckingValue/]收穫頗豐
的人氣，因爲他今年驚人的投資回報率。

很多人都在等待他那著名的 "YOLO UPDATE"，他每隔一段時間就會發布一次。

我們都看在眼裏，我們做夢都想擁有這樣的回報，擁有這麼多的
錢，...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7tp5e/the_importance_of_dfvs_example/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7tp5e/the_importance_of_dfvs_example/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/u/DeepFuckingValue/&quot;&gt;u/DeepFuckingValue&lt;/a&gt; has gained a lot of popularity for his incredible ROI this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people wait for his famous &amp;quot;YOLO UPDATE&amp;quot; that he posts every now and then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all look at them and we can only dream of having such returns, having so much money, who wouldn&amp;#39;t?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all look and wonder if we&amp;#39;ll ever make so much money in our lives, probably not, we think to ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But DFV was just a regular user of Reddit two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was convinced of his ideas, had some cash, and fell in love with this company, as we all have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, he bought in at a much lower price, but that&amp;#39;s not really what sets this man apart from most of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the secrets to his success was... his diamond hands and balls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was ridiculed for such a &amp;quot;stupid&amp;quot; investment - who would yolo his money in a &amp;quot;failing brick and mortar company&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was subjected to FUD daily, he lived through some horrible earnings reports, and yet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;he &lt;strong&gt;held.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He held because when a strong man/woman is convinced of his ideas nothing can distract him  - nothing can destroy him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is what I also want to be. That is what I am going to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe in my ideas. I believe in myself. I know why I&amp;#39;m here today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t let myself down just because I see some red days (or green days!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how things will turn out to be. No matter how red a day / week / month will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will &lt;strong&gt;hold.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit: This is not just about GME, this is a general discussion&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit II: Guys I&amp;#39;m not saying that diamond handing was all there is to DFV&amp;#39;s success. Of course his extraordinary DD and his education did most of the work, but that doesn&amp;#39;t mean that it was easy to hold through the tough times. What I&amp;#39;m trying to tell you is that his conviction and determination should be taken as an example&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit II: Wow thank you guys for all the awards, glad you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UWMC火箭]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我 我非常看好GME，我不會爲了這個賣掉任何一份股票
戲。然而，我有一些現金 躺在我的經紀賬戶，我欠了
稅。而我不想感到任何壓力，關於壓榨不得不。
發生在X或Y之前，所以這些錢不會進入GME。這...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7plal/the_uwmc_rocket/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7plal/the_uwmc_rocket/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First off: I&amp;#39;m very bullish on GME, and I won&amp;#39;t sell a single share for this play. However, I had some cash laying around in my brokerage account that I owe in taxes. And I don&amp;#39;t want to feel any pressure about the squeeze having to happen before X or Y, so that money won&amp;#39;t be going into GME. The squeeze will happen when it happens, and I can confidently say I can hold my shares for however long I need to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So during the last couple of weeks, I’ve seen UWMC being mentioned here. From what I understand, the company has pretty good fundamentals. They’re profitable, yada yada yada. However, I’m not looking for boomer stocks that give me a few percent of profit a year. I like rockets.But among the posts about UWMC, people were mentioning that there were a lot of options expiring on Mar 19. This piqued my interest. And I decided to take a look at the options chain myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ran a script to collect the data from the Yahoo options chain on Mar 7th, and quickly realized that there are indeed a shit ton of calls. This is not a boomer stock. This is a rocket, primed for launch. I figured someone else was going to post about the options chain in a more exhaustive manner, but this never happened. However, the last date for optimal launch conditions is drawing close, and the stock price is finally seeing some nice upwards action. So I figured I&amp;#39;d take it upon myself to tell you all about the beautiful options chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, before we start, I should mention that my understanding of options is rather limited. Prior to the whole GME thing, “options” primarily made me think about the menu where you can change the graphics fidelity and your controls in a videogame. So keep that in mind as you read this. I’m not the ideal person to be posting this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UWMC options chain had (as of Mar 7th - sorry about the outdated data, didn’t run the script since then, and the Yahoo IV seems to be scuffed right now) a total of 501,471 calls, with strike prices ranging from $1 to $25. As we all probably know by now, each call contract is worth 100 shares. This means that there were call contracts out there worth 50,147,100 shares.For a stock which has a public float of only ~90 million. Let that sink in. There are calls for literally 55% of the float.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also went ahead and calculated approximate deltas for the various calls in order to calculate to which extent these calls are likely hedged. With the price at the time ($8.68), roughly 11.3 million shares would have been held by call writers, assuming all of them hedge according to delta, and calls worth 38.9 million shares would have been unhedged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a price of $10, the number of hedged shares should go up to roughly 16 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At $12, that number would be ~23 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At $14, ~28.9 million. At this point, there are still ~21.2 million shares that are unhedged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this just keeps going as the price reaches new heights. Basically RKT all over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, the deltas would be slightly different today seeing as the delta calculation takes time until expiry into account, and a lot of the calls expire tomorrow, but the situation should still be &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; similar. Also, all of the calls aren’t written by market makers or by people who delta-hedge, but from what I understand, Market Makers do write the majority of call options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR:There are call options out there worth roughly 55% of the public float of UWMC. Potential for a massive gamma squeeze starting if the price goes up just a couple of dollars. EZ 2-bagger &lt;em&gt;with shares&lt;/em&gt; before the week is over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the price doesn&amp;#39;t go up soon enough, UWMC is apparently still a solid company, according to other posts on this sub. Boomer profits, maybe a 2-bagger with shares before the year is over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Positions: 150 shares @ $9.06. No options because I’m not rich enough to set up an account at an american broker, and I can’t find any european brokers that offer options for american stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is obviously not investing advice. I barely understand how options work, and eat crayons for breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Market is open, yahoo IV is unscuffed. So I could get some fresh data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total open interest  is 543,817 for calls across all strike prices and dates. Table below is assuming 100% of calls are hedged according to delta. This is obviously not the case in reality, but I&amp;#39;m not sure what percentage would be a reasonable assumption, so just posting the raw results from my script here. Also, keep in mind my deltas aren&amp;#39;t 100% correct, but rather just approximations. I&amp;#39;m too smoothbrained for using the real black-scholes algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Price of underlying&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Shs hedged&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Shs unhedged&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$9.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;12,837,474.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;41,544,225.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;15,287,918.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;39,093,781.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;19,884,009.9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;34,497,690.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;23,913,412.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;30,468,287.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$13&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;28,048,652.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;26,333,047.9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$14&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;32,059,778.8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;22,321,921.2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;35,577,854.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;18,803,845.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$17.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;41,868,771.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;12,512,928.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;45,074,617.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;9,307,082.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;49,206,602.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5,175,097.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;51,505,219.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2,876,480.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit2:&lt;br/&gt;
Shitadel and Susquehanna both seem to be UWMC stakeholders. Just a heads up. If this prints, it likely also prints for the bad guys.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼$GME在週三的刺激下只走了+0.79%？]]></title><description><![CDATA[繪本DD自🦍🦍🦍沒有喜歡的讀物。

本週至今在800C 3/19上花費了20MM美元。

https://preview.redd.it/aso8z03pepn61.jpg?width=750&format=pjpg&auto=webp&s=f8314dd277b4ada03e5484caa8da4271cdf4bd8e

這導致MM們的delta對沖非常少，下週The Calls OI
將...]]></description><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7i1yk/why_gme_only_moved_079_on_stimmy_wednesday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7i1yk/why_gme_only_moved_079_on_stimmy_wednesday/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Picture book DD since 🦍🦍🦍 no like read&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20 MM USD was spent on the 800C 3/19 so far this week&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/aso8z03pepn61.jpg?width=750&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f8314dd277b4ada03e5484caa8da4271cdf4bd8e&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/aso8z03pepn61.jpg?width=750&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f8314dd277b4ada03e5484caa8da4271cdf4bd8e&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which resulted in very minimum delta hedging by the MMs, next week The Calls OI will be taking a dive after 3/19&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/kzvzg8hsepn61.jpg?width=755&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c07ee2c44efa7a657792327d26fb1eb6bd6f8428&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/kzvzg8hsepn61.jpg?width=755&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c07ee2c44efa7a657792327d26fb1eb6bd6f8428&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;800C buyers, Meet one of your trade counterparty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/y0x9fwc0fpn61.jpg?width=750&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0bb9d47bf73f67b0cb604b6413d5aa7c17c8097c&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/y0x9fwc0fpn61.jpg?width=750&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0bb9d47bf73f67b0cb604b6413d5aa7c17c8097c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some ITM puts will trigger net buying by MM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/tvl838g7fpn61.jpg?width=1104&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d05a15bd436b145b4151f843c3767e048890a6d1&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/tvl838g7fpn61.jpg?width=1104&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d05a15bd436b145b4151f843c3767e048890a6d1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But near expiry far OTM calls will also trigger selling&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/p9uy4fmcfpn61.jpg?width=997&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b0b1608b03616a8dc296c58e6022ec6de3f0a9a7&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/p9uy4fmcfpn61.jpg?width=997&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b0b1608b03616a8dc296c58e6022ec6de3f0a9a7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resulting in a net selling of shares if price sits around this price level&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/hpsmq4jgfpn61.jpg?width=1138&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4e10f108353131da63de0abbae867602d9fd775a&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/hpsmq4jgfpn61.jpg?width=1138&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4e10f108353131da63de0abbae867602d9fd775a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the current structure of the OI strikes, expiries and underlying price, $GME will be bleeding shares, dumped by MM because delta is decreasing due to theta. This phenomenon is particular in high IV stocks with a concentration of OI strikes above the underlying nearing expiry, ie like $GME.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get back to Monday&amp;#39;s price level, you guys need to either NET BUY 400MM USD(400 thousand &lt;strong&gt;🦍🦍🦍&lt;/strong&gt; with 1k 🍌🍌🍌 each)  worth of shares (not on RH since they may not be actually buying it but just give you an IOU instead), or Gamma up the ATM and near OTM options for 3/19 and 3/26. No, I&amp;#39;m not a HF shill or  a thetagang vampire, I&amp;#39;m being real, your stimmy won&amp;#39;t be enough to move the market  by only  buying shares at this price point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms Alexis Goldstein agrees that options probably contributed most of the volatility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7h6uv/what_was_the_footprint_of_institutional_trading/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7h6uv/what_was_the_footprint_of_institutional_trading/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;TL;DR Gamma it back up you tards&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在另一個14K]]></title><link>https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7vhtg/in_for_another_14k/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reddit.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/m7vhtg/in_for_another_14k/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 21:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>