<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你可以改变我的想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览Reddit-Change My View的热帖]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 15:50:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: It should be illegal for health insurance providers to have access to discounts that the average consumer does not]]></title><description><![CDATA[US based obviously. In my opinion it should be illegal for an insurance provider
to have access to 'plan discounts' that the average consumer cannot have access
to. An example, I have needed some blood work and imaging recently. Quest
diagnostics billed nearly $800 total for 2 round of blood work.…]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oew0yl/cmv_it_should_be_illegal_for_health_insurance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oew0yl/cmv_it_should_be_illegal_for_health_insurance/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 15:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;US based obviously. In my opinion it should be illegal for an insurance provider to have access to &amp;#39;plan discounts&amp;#39; that the average consumer cannot have access to. An example, I have needed some blood work and imaging recently. Quest diagnostics billed nearly $800 total for 2 round of blood work. The insurance company paid approximately $80 of it, due to the plan discount. This is the case across the board. Needed an MRI, cost was $2200, the plan discount brought it down to $950. To be clear, they reduced the total amount to those values via plan discounts, I&amp;#39;m not complaining that they didn&amp;#39;t cover the remainder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US has a major issue with their cost of Healthcare. Can someone change my view and explain to me what the benefit of allowing this is, versus the MRI just costing $950 and the blood work just costing $40 and forcing the insurance company to pay the 100% (assuming the plan states they need to cover 100%).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 狗的品種，如巴哥犬、臘腸犬和鬥牛犬，應被歸類爲虐待動物。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如標題所說，某些品種的狗（也包括其他動物），只是
爲了動物的福利，它們不應該存在。
巴哥犬的人都需要帶它們去看獸醫，以解決它們的呼吸問題
因爲它們的臉部結構絕對是被破壞的......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oem7nf/cmv_dog_breeds_such_as_pugs_dachshunds_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oem7nf/cmv_dog_breeds_such_as_pugs_dachshunds_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 07:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the heading says, certain breeds of dogs (and other animals too), just shouldn’t exist for the animal’s welfare, I know so many people that have owned a pug that have needed to take them to the vets just to fix their breathing because their face structures are just absolutely destroyed through breeding, same with the English Bulldogs, faces absolutely destroyed with a overbite that can’t be healthy for any living thing but who cares? Its cute thats all that matters!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People may say I’m over exaggerating the fact of calling it animal cruelty but thats honestly my view of the issue, effecting the animals health or body structure for the worse to make the animal seem cuter isn’t good for anyone but the owners view on the dog.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list goes on and on of dog breeds with health issues due to breeding: Basset hound, Lhasa Apso, Chihuahua, Bulldogs, Shih tzu, Boston Terriers. And thats just some of the dogs with high chances of breathing issues, ear/eye infections and joint issues, whats the point of continuing to breed animals like this? The demand? Money? Doesn’t matter, why should these come before the welfare of a living thing?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly just don’t get it so if you guys could try and change my view on this issue it would be an interesting topic to talk about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：對不能區分外語的人來說，這不是種族主義。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我坦率地說，這是對這個的迴應
[https://www.reddit.com/r/WhitePeopleTwitter/comments/odaxhu/they_can_barely_manage_english/?utm_medium=android_app&utm_source=share]
幾天前在r/whitepeopletwitter [/r/whitepeopletwitter]上的帖子炸開了鍋。
聲稱你是種族主義者，如果你...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oejsee/cmv_its_not_racist_to_not_being_able_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oejsee/cmv_its_not_racist_to_not_being_able_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 07:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll be honest that this is a response to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/WhitePeopleTwitter/comments/odaxhu/they_can_barely_manage_english/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;amp;utm_source=share&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/whitepeopletwitter&quot;&gt;r/whitepeopletwitter&lt;/a&gt; that blew up a few days ago that asserts that you&amp;#39;re racist if you can&amp;#39;t tell the difference between Thai and Mandarin. And yes, I am from the US if that matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure if I was exposed to either language on a regular basis, I could probably tell you the difference between them because they seem to be fairly dissimilar despite both being tonal languages, but I don&amp;#39;t. I don&amp;#39;t live in an area with a lot of mandarin or Thai speakers that I know of and I don&amp;#39;t have any of those heritages in my immediate family. So, if I heard it in passing, I don&amp;#39;t think I&amp;#39;d know the difference off the top of my head. Does that make me racist? I don&amp;#39;t think so. I think it&amp;#39;s simply a difference of what I&amp;#39;ve been exposed to in my everyday life, but I&amp;#39;d love to hear everyone&amp;#39;s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：繼續把出櫃的同性戀者放在新聞中，並把他們作爲英雄來推崇，只會讓人覺得作爲同性戀仍然不正常。]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎每次有名人出櫃是同性戀，就會在社交媒體上大肆宣傳，稱他們是出櫃的英雄和強者。
媒體稱他們是英雄，是出櫃的強者。如果這是20多年前的事
前，我完全同意。但如今，隨着自豪月的到來，相當多的人開始接受同性戀。
現在有了驕傲月，而且相當多的人都接受了同性戀，我...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oehe3h/cmv_continuing_to_put_people_coming_out_as_gay_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oehe3h/cmv_continuing_to_put_people_coming_out_as_gay_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 23:38:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems everytime a celebrity comes out is gay it is plastered all over social media calling them a hero and strong for coming out. Now if this was 20+ years ago I&amp;#39;d totally agree. Nowadays though, with there being a pride month and a considerable amount of the population being accepting of gays I feel like pushing this narrative isnt going in the right direction. If a male celebrity came out and said he has sex with women we all wouldnt care and say that&amp;#39;s not news, in my opinion that&amp;#39;s how we should treat people coming out as gay. If the whole point of putting it in the news is the get more people to be accepting of it then it&amp;#39;s not gonna work. If someone doesn&amp;#39;t like people for being gay, putting it in their face that someone is gay isn&amp;#39;t gonna change how they see gay people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：有些父母真的應該讓他們的孩子拋棄他們。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不只是指虐待性的父母，只是指任何一種過分的父母。
自戀的、固執的、狹隘的、自以爲是的，以及其他所有你能想到的描述可怕父母的詞彙。
你能想到的描述可怕父母的詞彙。有毒的父母。

如果他們是有毒的，爲什麼任何孩子要留下來照顧他們的父母......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oeak4c/cmv_some_parents_genuinely_deserve_to_have_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oeak4c/cmv_some_parents_genuinely_deserve_to_have_their/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 22:36:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not just referring to abusive parents, just any kind of overboard parents. Narcissistic, stubborn, narrow minded and self righteous, and all the other terms you can think about to describe horrible parents. Toxic parents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why should any kid stay to take care of their parents if they were toxic to them? In fact, &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; parents have children because they’re afraid of dying alone and expects their children to take care of them. (a good number of old asian parents do that btw, source: am Asian) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By these type of parents I mean, parents who can’t accept their children’s sexuality or religion. Like when religious parents find out their kid is gay or is atheist and they completely lose their shit. Like as if being gay is wrong or a crime, or if not believing in god is a sin. Clearly some parents live in the Stone Age when it’s fucking 2021 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parents constantly trying to control them / controlling them when they were young, constantly arguing with them and manipulate them. Gaslighting them and guilt tripping them.  Or having insane expectations that their kids need to get all A’s or they are a disgarce to the family, or that their kids need to do a high end job / prestigious job like a doctor, etc (asian parent mindset) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t owe shit to our parents, they decided to bring us to the world. If they were good parents, then in return, they deserve to be taken care of. If you had a shitty childhood / majority of your life was shit when you lived with them, then they deserve to die alone and deserve to be abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我已經厭倦了這種不斷嘗試將毒品使用正常化的做法，最輕的毒品仍然可以將你的生活搞得一團糟。]]></title><description><![CDATA[讓我們把話說清楚。在毒品問題上，我幾乎是一個自由主義者。I
我認爲它們應該被合法化、徵稅和規範化，因爲在我看來，這樣做的好處明顯大於壞處。
在我看來，這樣做的好處顯然大於壞處。我是一個乾淨的人，我不喝酒
也不抽菸。我對大麻和迷幻藥很好奇，但在...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe4p16/cmv_im_tired_of_this_constant_attempt_at/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe4p16/cmv_im_tired_of_this_constant_attempt_at/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 17:32:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s get this out of the way: I&amp;#39;m pretty much a liberal regarding drugs. I think they should be legalized, taxed and regularized as it looks to me that the pros of doing that clearly outweight the cons. I am a &lt;em&gt;clean&lt;/em&gt; guy, I don&amp;#39;t drink and I don&amp;#39;t smoke. I am curious of weed and psychedelics, but at the moment I have no intention of experimenting with that because I don&amp;#39;t want to finance organized crime (all drugs are illegal where I live): there&amp;#39;s people who are literally enslaved, abused and extorted to get the traffic going, and I don&amp;#39;t really think a transient moment of hedonism warrants feeding into this cycle. I don&amp;#39;t have alternative access. And even if I had, I can&amp;#39;t trust the way it&amp;#39;s produced and the substances it is mixed with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided that I want to be more informed about drugs in general, so I started reading more on the topic. I&amp;#39;m getting more confused and lowkey furious as the only kinds of opinion I find are 2: drugs are immoral and dangerous and you should NEVER use them, or drugs do no harm at all and you should just be a little cautious. Bear in mind that I&amp;#39;m generalizing a big deal. What I&amp;#39;m saying is that I can&amp;#39;t seem to find balanced opinions on the matter, and each position has its degree of conspiratorial thinking backed into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate the position that all drugs are harmful under any circumstances because it&amp;#39;s a stance that has never produced the desired effects. People won&amp;#39;t stop using drugs, and if they don&amp;#39;t abuse illegal ones they will very likely abuse legal ones. Alcohol is one of the most dangerous drugs legally available on the market and it can have devastating effects on its users. Although rare, people can use paint and glue as means to get high, you simply can&amp;#39;t stop it. Weed, among all illegal drugs, is probably one of the most harmless to exist in nature, definitely less dangerous than alcohol for both the consumers and those around them. Psychedelics have also been shown to help both in the treatment and rehab of most psychological conditions and of addiction itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So... why the title you may ask? Well... because drugs ARE fucking dangerous, that&amp;#39;s why!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m growing increasingly impatient with scientists, activists and fake-gurus who talk about how everyone should take psychedelics, that there&amp;#39;s no such a thing as &amp;quot;too much weed&amp;quot;, and that using heavy drugs just every now and then doesn&amp;#39;t hurt. That&amp;#39;s irresponsible, misguided and dangerous, particularly for minors. In my experience, and that of the people I&amp;#39;m most intimate with, that&amp;#39;s a load of bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s been a steep increase in drug use in recent years. Every social circle I&amp;#39;ve been in has loads of people smoking weed. There&amp;#39;s basically no socialization if weed is missing.. And inevitably those who consume the most of it also consume other drugs and are involved in questionable pursuits. The more I see drugs circulating in a certain group, the more I see a great acceptance of antisocial behavior and a seriously impaired sense of judgment. Pure collectivized denial. Some of them are in an extremely sad state, clearly dissociated and incapable of thinking straight, but nobody seems to notice or care rationalizing with &amp;quot;but that&amp;#39;s just the way they are&amp;quot;. My brother is diagnosed with BD type 1 and his psychotic episodes were most likely triggered by his consistent weed use. He cut the weed, and while the psychosis was less intense his mood remained impaired until he found the right medication. You might argue that he only had adverse reactions because he was already prone to it, but does that change anything at all? Do you think that the widespread message that weed doesn&amp;#39;t really hurt helps anyone with the knowledge that adverse reactions aren&amp;#39;t at all uncommon?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I encounter an otherwise interesting source speaking about drugs there&amp;#39;s always a moment in which they will say something cospiratorial in nature, such as the idea that all the drugs being banned are the ones that make you question the government and stuff like that. You literally CAN&amp;#39;T PROVE THAT. There&amp;#39;s never real meat behind that, but even if that was the case then I think you need to talk to those who say that the 60s activist movements were deliberately dismantled by the CIA by introducing drugs in the picture. Like... get the story straight, maybe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;#39;s as if it wasn&amp;#39;t blatant how there&amp;#39;s a whole circus of enterpreneurs that are just waiting to capitalize on the weed market and use all the bullshit spewed by these activists for their marketing campaigns. The speculation is already blatant. I keep seeing bullshit like &amp;quot;cannabis smoke doesn&amp;#39;t cause cancer&amp;quot;, as if it wasn&amp;#39;t known that consistent inhalation of hot smoke is detrimental to anyone&amp;#39;s health. Anyway, most people I know mix weed with tobacco so that&amp;#39;s a pointless objection really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if we really want to politicize things, we should also remember that when 19th century China tried to become independent from colonizers Britain and other countries actively worked to hook the chinese population on opium in an attempt to make them become more compliant and less willing to rebel against european influences, sparking an addiction epidemic that lasted decades. Look that up: the opium wars. &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/37G0JmU6NwM?t=1134&quot;&gt;I find this interview with John McAfee and his opinions on weed quite interesting.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My rant is incomplete, but I guess you got the gist of it. I&amp;#39;m for the legalization of drugs for the possible applications in healthcare and to starve off organized crime, and why not, for occasional recreational use (meaning not every day, possibly not even every week). But I still think it&amp;#39;s dangerous and can very easily become a pernicious vice that can destroy your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：加密貨幣在邏輯上是不可行的，因此是美化了的賭博，而不是一種投資]]></title><description><![CDATA[我還沒有看到一個令人信服的答案，爲什麼比特幣和其他貨幣是
實際上是金融的未來。有幾個非常基本的缺陷是
對我來說很明顯。

 * 法幣的貶值。法幣在許多地方已經不是很好了，因爲
   荒唐的印鈔機爲緩解COVID而印鈔......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odx41x/cmv_crypto_is_logistically_unworkable_and_is_thus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odx41x/cmv_crypto_is_logistically_unworkable_and_is_thus/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 15:43:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have yet to see a convincing answer for why Bitcoin and other currencies are actually the future of finance. There are a few very basic flaws that are obvious to me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Devaluation of fiat. Fiat is already not in a great spot in many places due to the absurd money printing for COVID relief spending.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Following that, a government is not going to allow something that further devalues their currency and then cuts into tax revenue on top of that, since Bitcoin is untaxable. I&amp;#39;m fiscally conservative, but tax revenue is certainly necessary. Governments could fine companies who take Bitcoin, essentially taxing them and removing the incentive to use it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The fragmentation of the economy. You can&amp;#39;t run a modern economy with multiple currencies, all holding different values that fluctuate wildly. If I go to the store with one dollar, I can be confident that the purchasing power of that dollar will be the same next week. Yes, inflation happens, but it is usually gradual and measured. My dollar will be able to buy me a candy bar next month the same as it can this month. Bitcoin (and other currencies that follow its lead) has wild swings of 10% within days, sometimes hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elon Musk has singlehandedly sent Bitcoin crashing with one tweet. You can&amp;#39;t do that to fiat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t seen any good rebuttals to these very simple arguments. I see crypto as a gamble, not an investment. There is no thesis required, and the vast majority of crypto fans seem to do their DD by reading tweets from big holders that want to pump the price. There aren&amp;#39;t earnings, balance sheets, SEC filings to look at for Bitcoin. The stock market can be irrational, yes, but crypto seems like it&amp;#39;s very obviously doomed to fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：Gmail在日常可用性方面領先於Outlook的街道]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾在同時使用Outlook和Gmail的企業環境中工作過（Google
爲特定的企業定製了品牌等，但它是Gmail的一部分。
但它是Gmail的一部分）。) 在同一類型的工作環境中使用這兩種軟件後，我認爲
我的看法是，Gmail不僅僅是略勝一籌，而是遠勝於它。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe4y7v/cmv_gmail_is_streets_ahead_of_outlook_in_everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe4y7v/cmv_gmail_is_streets_ahead_of_outlook_in_everyday/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 13:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have worked in corporate environments that use both Outlook and Gmail (Google tailors it to the specific corporate with branding etc, but it’s Gmail through and through). Having used both in the same type of working environment, my take is that Gmail is not just marginally better, but far better. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a non-technical user, so I’m not going to rattle off a feature list from some IT website. My needs are speed, user friendliness, integration with other applications (Gmail - google drive, Outlook - Office 365) and obviously a good calendar interface. Outlook might tick the boxes for these items, but Gmail just does it far better. Am I missing something here? CMV. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(And no, I don’t work for a tech company or have some underlying marketing agenda.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：所有的社交媒體平臺都在試圖複製tiktok，我討厭這樣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[所有的社交媒體平臺都在試圖整合全屏視頻，"只需要
刷 "的平臺，我討厭這樣。Reddit剛剛這樣做了，我討厭它。我不希望
你的低劣算法試圖在我瀏覽視頻時向我提供舊內容。
我討厭新的 "聊天 "評論佈局....。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe1apm/cmv_all_social_media_platforms_are_trying_to_copy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe1apm/cmv_all_social_media_platforms_are_trying_to_copy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 11:31:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;All social media platforms are trying to integrate the full screen video, “just swipe”, platform and I hate it. Reddit just did it and I hate it. I don’t want your shitty algorithm to try to feed me old content when I swipe on a video from my home page, and I hate the new “chat” comment layout. Instagram has done the same thing which was expected but Reddit has been my salvation. Your search bar barely fucking works why would your algorithm be any better. Why is this any better? Are there any perks to it? Make me hate this bullshit less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：如果沒有空間讓白人男子感到被重視和讚賞，那麼新納粹主義和白人鎮壓主義將繼續增長。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我認爲最近白人至上主義的增長與少數族裔和婦女的日益被接受和重視直接相關。
越來越多的人接受和重視少數民族羣體和婦女。在
邊緣化的白人男子看到這些羣體因其膚色、性別等而得到認可，他們也想得到同樣的認可，但只有這樣他們才能感覺到自己是其中的一員。
性別等，他們也想得到同樣的認可，但唯一的辦法是他們能感覺到自己是屬於
的唯一方法...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe0e2l/cmv_if_there_isnt_space_for_white_men_to_feel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oe0e2l/cmv_if_there_isnt_space_for_white_men_to_feel/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 11:31:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the recent growth of white supremisim is directly tied with the increasing acceptance and valuing of minority groups and women. Where marginalized white men see these groups be recognized for their skin color, gender, etc and they want the same except the only way they can feel like part of a group is to be a white nationalist and they get more and more radicalized. Instead there needs to be a space where white men can come together and feel proud of who they are. Instead the media does everything it can to ignore the average white man, outside of sports, politics and business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I thought this sub was supposed to change my view, not prove my point&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：美國輸掉了阿富汗戰爭]]></title><description><![CDATA[本週，大多數美國士兵離開了阿富汗。和越南一樣，這也是一場
昂貴的災難。對美國來說，阿富汗遠征是一次失敗。

 * 他們沒有打敗塔利班。
 * 他們沒有贏得阿富汗人民的心。
 * 他們沒有改善阿富汗人民的生活。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odgp3z/cmv_the_usa_lost_the_afghan_war/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odgp3z/cmv_the_usa_lost_the_afghan_war/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 04:36:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week most US soldiers left Afghanistan. And like Vietnam it has been a costly disaster. The Afghan expedition was a failure by most metrics for the US:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They did not defeat the Taliban.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They did not win the hearts and minds of the Afghan population.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They did not improve the lot of average Afghans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They did not implement a stable democracy, or shown the benefit of democracy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;America&amp;#39;s standing did not improve&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;America&amp;#39;s army has been shown to be a joke that could not defeat stone age people with AK47s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Afghan war atrocities and abuses (and the +100 000 dead Afghan civilians) will be another wip to beat the USA with in the future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thousands of dead and maimed US veterans also do not benefit the USA. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I would say that the only people who benefited would be the billionaires who run Arms corporations in the US.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：許多美國人對生活在美國感到不滿意]]></title><description><![CDATA[每到7月4日，我都會看到許多不同的人在抱怨我們正在慶祝獨立這一事實。
我們正在慶祝我們的獨立。他們這樣做的依據通常是，我們
在這個國家有問題，無論是現在還是過去。

生活在美國是一種特權，否認它是，就是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odrdvw/cmv_many_americans_are_ungrateful_for_living_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odrdvw/cmv_many_americans_are_ungrateful_for_living_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 03:33:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every 4th of July I see so many different people complaining about the fact that we are celebrating our independence. Their basis for this is generally that we have problems in the country, both in the present, and in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Living in the United States is a privilege and denying it is, is ridiculous. I work in a warehouse with many people who immigrated to the United States and through asking them what they think about the US, 100% of them could not be more happy with how their lives have improved after moving here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, one of the arguments I have heard is that our Founding Fathers were slave owners and did atrocious things in the past, so why would I want to celebrate that. Yes they were, and there is no denying that, but why is this alone a justification for not celebrating our freedom and ideas that were created by the same Founding Fathers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：人們對Sha'Carri被禁止參加奧運會的憤怒是荒謬的，禁令絕對不是試圖壓制或壓迫任何人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎很多人都對藥檢不合格感到非常不安。這真是
人們希望她在藥檢中被抓到時沒有任何後果，這很瘋狂。
藥檢中被發現的後果。我甚至不認爲他們對大麻進行藥檢是正確的，但
但標準已經存在了。她的母親去世了，這是不是很可怕？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odavbx/cmv_peoples_outrage_over_shacarri_being_banned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odavbx/cmv_peoples_outrage_over_shacarri_being_banned/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 20:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like a lot of people are really upset over the failed drug test. It’s crazy that people want there to be no consequences to her getting caught on a drug test. I don’t even think it’s right that they drug test for cannabis, but the standard is already there. Is it awful her mother died and she had to cope? Absolutely! But let’s not pretend like she’s super oppressed because of a failed drug test for the olympics. It’s an unfortunate situation but people are really making a mountain out of a mole hill. Also, how is it fair to the athletes that didn’t smoke and get to move up to her spot? Some people wouldn’t go to the olympics otherwise so are supposed to forget about rules cause Sha’Carri can run fast?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：《每日秀》和類似節目弊大於利]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直喜歡看喬恩-斯圖爾特，然後是特雷弗-諾亞，因爲他們的幽默感。在
偶爾，他們會透露一些有價值的見解，吸引人的採訪，或令人印象深刻的新聞。
令人印象深刻的新聞工作。不過，通常情況下，大部分的樂趣來自於
看他們抨擊保守派的虛僞行爲。

然而... 他們是否...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od8qx8/cmv_the_daily_show_and_similar_shows_do_more_harm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od8qx8/cmv_the_daily_show_and_similar_shows_do_more_harm/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 17:36:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I always enjoyed watching Jon Stewart, then Trevor Noah, for their humor. On occasion, they would reveal some valuable insight, engaging interviews, or impressive journalism. Normally, though, most of the enjoyment came from watching them lambast conservative hypocrisies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However... Are they actually doing more harm than good to society?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thinking:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humans often hold beliefs that they don&amp;#39;t really identify with and don&amp;#39;t hold strongly. However, once they&amp;#39;re mocked for those beliefs, they&amp;#39;ll dig their heels in and believe it 10x as strongly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s my understanding that many conservatives feel they are constantly being mocked by elitist, privileged, Leftists very often for superficial reasons or insulting stereotypes (e.g., &amp;quot;You&amp;#39;re dumb because you have a country accent.&amp;quot;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Daily Show is a constant source of mockery, which could trigger (2) above, and by extension (1).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Furthermore, it&amp;#39;s rare to see The Daily Show use in-depth arguments to defend liberal stances. Usually, it just goes for the simple arguments (which sometimes don&amp;#39;t stand up to scrutiny, even when I agree with the conclusion!) and easy jokes. So there&amp;#39;s not much good being done here to balance out the potential harm of (3).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Some more background: I went from seldom watching Trevor Noah to never watching him again after Trump was elected president; the jokes just didn&amp;#39;t seem funny anymore. The stakes were too high, the situation too severe with someone like Trump in office. What&amp;#39;s the point of laughing at Trump&amp;#39;s tiny hands when his actions have such terribly large effect?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：每天吸食大麻並不是一個健康的習慣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道我會因此受到很多批評，但我不認爲每天抽大麻是健康的。
但我不認爲每天吸食大麻是健康的，我願意改變我的觀點，因爲這是我的關係中一個有爭議的問題。
在我的關係中，這是一個有爭議的問題。我的伴侶認爲每天吸食大麻
是可以的，但我認爲大麻和酒精是類似的。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odjq8u/cmv_smoking_weed_everyday_is_not_a_healthy_habit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odjq8u/cmv_smoking_weed_everyday_is_not_a_healthy_habit/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:36:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know I&amp;#39;m gonna get a lot of flack for this but I don&amp;#39;t believe it&amp;#39;s healthy to smoke weed everyday and would be open to changing my opinion on that as it is a contentious issue in my relationship. My partner believes smoking weed everyday is okay but I think marijuana and alcohol are similar in that, you shouldn&amp;#39;t over use any substance, because at some point you begin using it to cope with life&amp;#39;s daily challenges instead of learning to face your issues. I think if you&amp;#39;re healthy and have no medical reason to smoke every day, that it&amp;#39;s probably not a good habit. If anyone could provide research to the contrary that would help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：MLK的《伯明翰監獄來信》是一份非常被低估的文件，其信息對當今世界非常重要。]]></title><description><![CDATA[MLK對那些希望擁有虛假的和平的自由主義者的批評，讓人感覺到
與我們今天所處的世界如此相關。即使是我這個黑人
也落入了他在這封信中所說的陷阱。

如此多的少數民族面臨如此多的壓迫，而他們的一個默認反應是
總是 "如果...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od6h1i/cmv_mlks_a_letter_from_a_birmingham_jail_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od6h1i/cmv_mlks_a_letter_from_a_birmingham_jail_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 09:34:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MLK&amp;#39;s criticism of liberals who wish to have a false since of peace just feels so relevant to the world we live in today. To the point where even I a black man fell for the exact trap he speaks of in this letter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So many minorities face so much oppression and one the default responses is always &amp;quot;if only they didn&amp;#39;t make it their personality&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;if only they were just quieter about it. I just love the way he slam dunks on those idiotic takes on civil rights movements. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also believe it should be more relevant because it challenges the watered down version of MLK a lot of people get feed. They ignored the fact that his tactics were specifically created to make tensions rise and to make people upset for this watered down idea that he did everything perfectly peacefully. It&amp;#39;s an amazing document that deserves to be as well known as the I Have a Dream Speech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：一個教師因以前或現在的性工作生活而被解僱的世界是錯誤的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我認爲沒有理由解僱他們，我認爲這是不道德的。我所說的不道德並不是指
僱主不能合法地這樣做，我的意思是如果他們這樣做，我就不喜歡他們。
我的觀點是來自公立學校。在這裏，政府是僱主，他們
僱用教師。

教師的能力並不會因爲...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odeibr/cmv_a_world_where_teachers_are_fired_for_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odeibr/cmv_a_world_where_teachers_are_fired_for_their/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 08:40:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see no reason to fire them and I think its immoral. By immoral I don&amp;#39;t mean the employer can&amp;#39;t do it legally, I mean I will not like them if they do so. and my view is coming from public schools. Here the government is the employer who hires teachers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A teachers ability isn&amp;#39;t diminished because they once was a can girl. 
I know people will say that a teachers job is also about interacting with parents. 
But I think patents are in the wrong. It isn&amp;#39;t reasonable in the first place to care if the teacher was once a stripper. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess this is a complex issue with multiple layers but I think the entire process and the view that its OK to fire is all wrong. If its about how the kids will react if they find out their teacher is a sex worker, I think keeping the teacher and fostering a society that is sex positive will change exactly the problem people think will happen. Obviously its easier said then done. I would like to live in a world where kids just shrug and say, oh my teacher was a sex worker? Whatever. Children shouldn&amp;#39;t be watching porn anyways so if they do find out that&amp;#39;s on the parents who gave them access. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, my view is a world where teachers aren&amp;#39;t fired for their sex work is better than a world where they do&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：作爲一個有兩個年幼孩子的已婚父親，如果我開始騎摩托車，那就太自私了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我需要每個人今天都處於最佳狀態，因爲我真的希望你們
來改變我的看法。

我從十幾歲起就想買一輛摩托車，但我沒有錢。
錢。現在我買得起了，但我已經結婚了，有兩個孩子，我不能不說
認爲這是一個不必要的風險......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odausa/cmv_as_a_married_father_of_two_young_children_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/odausa/cmv_as_a_married_father_of_two_young_children_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 04:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I need everyone to be at the top of their game today because I really want you to change my view here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have wanted to get a motorcycle since I was a teenager but I didn&amp;#39;t have the money. Now I can afford one but I am married with two kids and I cannot help but think that it is an unnecessary risk that will make me much more likely to leave my children fatherless.  If I didn&amp;#39;t have a wife and kids I would definitely have one at this point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depending on the source, I have seen estimates that you are 27 to 35 times more likely to die per mile traveled on a motorcycle than in a car.  To me this seems unacceptably risky. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do realize that this is probably a self fulfilling issue to some degree. Motorcycles are seen as risky, therefore people who take more risks ride them, therefore more risks are taken on motorcycles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do believe that as a risk adverse person with a lot to live for I could probably be safer than the average would suggest, but how much?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could be swayed by statistics showing, for example, how much less likely you are to die if you wear all the gear all the time, or showing that the vast majority of fatalities are during specific road conditions that could be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately an anecdote that you have rode for 40 years and never had an accident will not change my view, though I would be happy to hear what habits you think have lead to your excellent record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would be happy to hear from other parents about how they justify the risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我認爲以約會爲目的在現實生活中接近某人會比網上約會（包括Tinder和Bumble等約會專用應用程序以及Instagram和Twitter DMs等社交媒體應用程序）得到更好的結果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1. 即時反饋。你不必懷疑你是否被拒絕了
    或者她對你有興趣，但要花很長時間來回應，因爲你會得到一個答案。
    因爲你當時就能得到答案。
 2. 2.在你接近她的時候，你不會和世界上所有好看的人競爭。
    2.在你接近的那一刻，你不會和世界上所有好看的人競爭。你...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od8z8z/cmv_i_think_that_approaching_someone_in_real_life/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od8z8z/cmv_i_think_that_approaching_someone_in_real_life/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 04:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Immediate feedback. You don’t have to wonder about if you’re being rejected or if she’s interested but taking forever to respond because you will get an answer right then and there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’re not competing with all the good looking people in the world at the moment you approach. You get their singular attention or at least more of it than on an app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a guy, as long as you don’t corner a girl in a situation where she feels threatened like a dark parking lot, a lot of girls will at least speak a little to you before it gets awkward or you successfully hold a conversation and get them to want to keep talking to you&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: defining results which in this case I mean results as in where you stand with the other person. There’s no delay. Tbh, I actually think that you get more positive outcomes too because of that immediate contact and not having to sustain a conversation in a back and forth with 1-5 hour long delays between responses&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: 對在現代軍隊服役的人說 "感謝你的服務 "是一件非常、非常奇怪的事情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我知道如果他們是被迫參加戰爭的，說 "謝謝 "是有道理的。
被徵召參加戰爭，以保護他們的國家（比如說一戰或類似的戰爭，那是很殘酷的
那是很殘酷的），但過了這個階段，每次都讓我很困惑。有時，在某人被徵召後，會有
有時在某人被感謝後會有起立鼓掌......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od34fv/cmv_saying_thank_you_for_your_service_to_someone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/od34fv/cmv_saying_thank_you_for_your_service_to_someone/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 22:30:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First off I understand it makes sense to say &amp;quot;thank you&amp;quot; if they were FORCED to be drafted into the war, to protect their country (say for WW1 or similar, that was brutal), but past that it baffles me every single time. Sometimes there are literally standing ovations after someone is thanked for serving in the military.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mainly see and hear this coming from people in the USA, but I see it in Canada too: I can&amp;#39;t wrap my head around thanking someone for a service/job that they signed up for. Most of the military will never see combat in their life, and if they do it is because they signed up knowing that they could die on the job due to the position they signed up for. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pay and perks are generally pretty good if you are in combat, and this reflects the danger that you are signing up for. It&amp;#39;s not like it&amp;#39;s a surprise! So why do we still do this seemingly mandatory congratulatory back rub in North America? Especially when all the combative wars we are currently involved in are unnecessary for the safety of our continent and countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open to discussion why this is still an important thing to do. To me it seems grandfathered in from wars gone by and doesn&amp;#39;t truly reflect what is going in modern North America&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit to add:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of downvoting me, leave a comment to help change my view! Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：因政治問題而結束關係/友誼是可以的]]></title><description><![CDATA[與流行觀點相反，政治不僅僅是在如何處理稅收方面的分歧。
稅收方面的分歧。它也不是一些無害的、中性的屬性，類似於
族裔、性別或性取向。你的政治歸屬是你的核心價值觀的反映
反映了你的核心價值觀，而你的核心價值觀就是你的內容...。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocyx3j/cmv_its_okay_to_end_relationships_friendships/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocyx3j/cmv_its_okay_to_end_relationships_friendships/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 19:32:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular opinion, politics is more than just a difference in what to do with taxes. It&amp;#39;s also NOT some innocuous, neutral attribute akin to ethnicity, gender, or sexual orientation. Your political affiliation is a reflection of your core values, and your core values IS the content of your character; and isn&amp;#39;t the content of your character the only reasonable thing that is up for judgement? Not only that, who you decide to vote for has REAL implications on the rest of us, should that person be elected into power. In the course of your political expression, people are allowed to reassess their friendship / relationship with you when they realize your core values are not compatible with theirs. In fact, it&amp;#39;s GOOD that people are choosing to end friendships / relationships rather than stew in a passive-aggressive, resentful dynamic with people whom they no longer like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：Instagram已經失去了它的優勢，最終會消亡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Instagram正在衰落，並將在未來幾年內繼續這樣做
直到他們最終消亡。以下是我認爲的理由。

一--Instagram正在失去其利基

作爲一個照片分享平臺，Instagram有一個成功的利基，而且這仍然是
最終是大多數創作者和用戶的目標。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocvz3l/cmv_instagram_has_lost_its_edge_and_will_die_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocvz3l/cmv_instagram_has_lost_its_edge_and_will_die_out/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 12:56:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram is on the decline, and will continue to do so for the next few years until they finally die out. Here are my reasons for believing that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One - Instagram is losing its niche&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram had a successful niche as a photo-sharing platform, and that is still ultimately what most creators and users use it for. Users use it because they want to see photos and engage with them. However, Instagram is now moving to attempt to compete with YouTube and TikTok, which will ultimately fail because those platforms are already occupying their respective niches, and doing a good job at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two - Instagram isn&amp;#39;t showing people what they want to see&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe that most casual users of Instagram are like myself - we follow pages that we want to use, which usually includes our friends and pages of interest that we are interested in. Instagram&amp;#39;s attempt to push people to look at pages that they don&amp;#39;t even follow at the expense of pages that they do is driving users away and lowering users&amp;#39; interest in the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these reasons, I think that Instagram will eventually die out, and pretty soon at that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我們應該對成本的 "外部化 "徵稅，而且稅率應該高到足以讓它首先不值得。]]></title><description><![CDATA[例如，將雞肉從美國運到中國比較便宜，在那裏進行加工（由於工資低和其他原因，比較便宜）。
在那裏，雞肉將被加工（由於工資較低和其他原因，它更便宜）並運回美國。
運回美國。這是一種畸形的做法，它創造了更多的
由於跨洋運輸造成了更多的污染，並使資本流失......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocw144/cmv_we_should_tax_the_externalization_of_a_cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocw144/cmv_we_should_tax_the_externalization_of_a_cost/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 12:56:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, it&amp;#39;s cheaper to transport chicken from the USA to China, where it will be processed (it&amp;#39;s cheaper due to lower wages and other reasons) and shipped back to the USA. This is a monstrous practice, that creates a lot more pollution due to trans-oceanic transportation and takes capital out of a nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end product is cheaper to manufacture so the corporation can increase its profits, and the costs are externalized: someone else will have to clean the oceans in the future, and someone else misses out on a job that&amp;#39;s outsourced to another nation. Net gain for the corporation, net loss for everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need taxes in place so that this practice is a net loss for the corporation. It&amp;#39;s ruining the country and the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：臥底警察和 "滲透者和誘捕 "聽起來非常違憲，因爲他們相當於在沒有搜查證或可能的理由的情況下進行搜查。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果警察把一卡車的鞋子擺出來，目的是爲了讓它們被偷，從邏輯上講
這意味着他們是在向公衆贈送東西，因爲這是用納稅人的錢購買的
用納稅人的錢購買的。

此外，臥底警察、麪包車、巡洋艦被用於日常交通執法
似乎公然違憲......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocsila/cmv_undercover_police_and_infiltrators_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocsila/cmv_undercover_police_and_infiltrators_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 08:41:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If police set out a truck of shoes with the intent of it being stolen, logically that means they were giving things away to the public because it was purchased with taxpayer dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also undercover cops, vans, cruisers being used for routine traffic enforcement seem blatantly unconstitutional because they amount to a search of the public without warrant or probable cause. Crime can happen anywhere, behind closed doors or on the streets and nothing is preventing police from enforcing traffic laws in plainly marked vehicles. Using unmarked vehicles is the same thing as policing an area without a warrant to search &amp;#39;looking for probable cause&amp;#39;. The warrant is already there, police have some function to protect the public, but hiding that warrant, which is the police presence, goes beyond legal limits placed on government by the bill of rights. Police in an area already amounts to a search, you cant hide the fact you are there and still call yourself law enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same goes for undercover police infiltrating freely associated groups, as they have no probable cause and the state cannot sanction the search of a group of people. People also cannot &amp;#39;surrender&amp;#39; that right or any other right, depending on which platform is used. I believe that act is also unconstitutional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：與女足（足球）有關的同酬是不現實的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[不要斷章取義。其他方面的同工同酬是合理的，比如
做同樣的辦公室工作。但在體育方面，我不認爲同工同酬在
在目前的女性市場上，我認爲女性足球的同工同酬是不現實的。

從我對體育的一般知識來看。球員的工資通常是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc567x/cmv_equal_pay_pertaining_to_womens_football/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc567x/cmv_equal_pay_pertaining_to_womens_football/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 01:41:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t take this out of context. Equal pay in other stuff is reasonable like doing the same office job. But in the context of sports, I dont see equal pay in women&amp;#39;s football being realistic in the current women&amp;#39;s market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my general knowledge of sports. Salary for players are usually determined by the total revenue of the league divided between the player&amp;#39;s salary, the owners, and the league&amp;#39;s administration. As an example, the NFL distributes is revenue by giving 49% to the profits for player&amp;#39;s salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I believe the real reason women don&amp;#39;t get equally paid in football is mainly due to the lack of revenue in women&amp;#39;s soccer. The best women&amp;#39;s soccer player wants to be paid the same as Messi or ronaldo. But the question is do they generate as much money as those two soccer giants? I believe the lack of revenue generated in women&amp;#39;s football leagues will limit their salaries. They need more demand where people want to pay just as much as mens league to watch and of course have the same amount of people willing to pay the same price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the whole movement seems weak because by paying the same wage as men they are bankrupting their own league. Where is the money coming from? Because they don&amp;#39;t generate enough revenue for equal pay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an example, women&amp;#39;s tennis generates high revenue. There is a reason they are the highest paid female athletes. They bring in fans and money. Not quite equal to the male tennis wage, but the gap is much smaller compared to other sports. Hence, revenue generated = higher salaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this entire movement was based on unfair percentage split then I am supporting them. But the issue is the absolute revenue is just so low compared to men. Sports is essentially entertainment. You get paid by the demand of people wanting to spend to watch you. Women&amp;#39;s football league just doesn&amp;#39;t have the demand comparable to the men&amp;#39;s league. They should focus on increasing that demand and revenue rather than asking for something that is not even available. Cause there is not enough money available to pay all the women football players the same as men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：現場清醒測試不應僅僅由官員的意見來決定]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道有人可能因爲酒精以外的東西而醉倒，所以
我知道爲什麼會有這樣的規定。然而，我不喜歡一個沒有經過培訓的官員決定對你的罪行進行指控。
我不喜歡一個沒有經過培訓的官員來決定對你的犯罪行爲進行指控，我認爲最多隻能
司機應該被帶到醉酒罐，然後被釋放......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocacpo/cmv_field_sobriety_tests_should_not_be_up_to_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ocacpo/cmv_field_sobriety_tests_should_not_be_up_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 18:34:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I understand that someone can be intoxicated on something other than alcohol, so I know why they&amp;#39;re in place. However I do not like that an officer with no training gets to decide to actually charge you with the crime, I believe at most a driver should be taken to the drunk tank and then released (WITH vehicle) and if the blood tests come back negative, then they can charge them and set up a court date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw this because years ago I was pulled over and apparently failed a field sobriety test. I was not on anything, my car was impounded for 30 days, and I had to miss work sometimes due to lack of ride, as well as going to multiple court dates because they kept scheduling them before they had the results, so I would wait all day in court only to be called up and rescheduled because they don&amp;#39;t have the blood work back. Finally I go and they say &amp;quot;oh your blood work was negative, you&amp;#39;re free to leave&amp;quot; but of course no refund for paying close to $2000 to get my car out of impound or anything. I&amp;#39;m not sure what should be the exact solution to this, but I do know that something needs to change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：預防自殺的集會/社交媒體帖子/5公里之類的東西完全是廢話，讓活人感覺更好]]></title><description><![CDATA[完全公開，我有幾個朋友死於自殺，其中一個至今仍深深地刺痛我。
痛苦......這也是我的觀點背後的驅動力。人們製作了
T恤衫，舉行5公里長跑，在社交媒體上發佈關於預防自殺的帖子和
諸如此類的東西。這到底是在幫助誰？如果有人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc4vkm/cmv_suicide_prevention_ralliessocial_media/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc4vkm/cmv_suicide_prevention_ralliessocial_media/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 13:30:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full disclosure, have lost a few friends to suicide, one of which still cuts me deep to this day... it is the driving force behind my view. People made T-shirts, had a 5k run, put up social media posts about suicide prevention and stuff like that. Who the hell is this helping? If someone is suicidal, none of this will help them. Yes, raising money for suicide hotlines is a noble cause, but guess what- the people that off themselves DO NOT CALL THEM! I know how bitter I sound, I still have a lot of residual anger over my friend&amp;#39;s death, but it just stinks like desperate bullshit people tell themselves to make them feel better. And full disclosure, I have been down some pretty dark roads and no one reaches out to you, nobody cares until it is too late. It is sometimes an impossible thing to see coming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：人們不應該在大流行期間沒有參加路考就拿到駕照。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這在美國正在發生。我知道有很多人在沒有參加路考的情況下獲得了他們的
不參加路考就拿到了駕照。這是一個可笑的選擇
政府在大流行期間做出的荒謬選擇。是的，這對人們來說很糟糕
不能馬上拿到駕照的人來說是很糟糕的，但爲了安全，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1guc/cmv_people_should_not_have_received_their_drivers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1guc/cmv_people_should_not_have_received_their_drivers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 07:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is happening in the United States. I know multiple people who got their driver&amp;#39;s licenses without taking their road test. This was a ridiculous choice the government made during the pandemic. Yes, it would have sucked for people who couldn&amp;#39;t get their licenses right away, but for the safety of the public this shouldn&amp;#39;t have been allowed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people getting these licenses are not good drivers. I know a few who simply couldn&amp;#39;t pass their road test in the past (SpongeBobs) and the pandemic gave them their license despite their lack of skills, all they had to do was fill out some paper work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know three people who got their licenses and got into accidents less than two months after getting them. Our governments are failing us right now in this way and causing more accidents by allowing these licenses to be handed out without road test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMV: People should not have received their driver&amp;#39;s licenses during the pandemic without taking their road tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：某些髮型不屬於某些文化]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在youtube/tiktok上看到有的人因爲一個白人戴着一個他們認爲只有他們的文化才應該戴的髮型而感到不安。
他們認爲只有他們的文化才應該留這種髮型，我不太理解。
真的很理解。

我在看一個歐洲婦女的YouTube視頻，她展示瞭如何做一個北歐/維京風格的辮子。
北歐/維京風格的辮子。她編了兩條玉米辮...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obywd5/cmv_certain_hairstyles_do_not_belong_to_certain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obywd5/cmv_certain_hairstyles_do_not_belong_to_certain/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:50:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen POC getting upset on youtube/tiktok for a white person wearing a hairstyle that they believe should only be worn by their culture and I dont really understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was watching a YouTube video of a European women showing how to do a Nordic/Viking style braid. She braided two cornrows (she called them cornrows but I think they were really Dutch braids) on both sides of her head, and then did a big braid on top, gathered all the braids together into a pony in the back. Some people were upset in the comments though, saying that she is appropriating black culture by doing these small Dutch braids, even though this hairstyle was done by vikings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another example, I saw a tiktok of these white girls at a pool, and they all were wearing a silk scarf on their head. People in the comments were upset by this, and claimed they were appropriating black culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just dont understand how a culture can own a certain style of braid or a certain way to tie a scarf to your head. If someone is wearing their hair like that, and they aren&amp;#39;t doing it to be racist, I dont see the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone please explain this to me. I hope this doesn&amp;#39;t come off as racist or ignorant, I&amp;#39;m not trying to be I just dont understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：一個人不應該被指控爲酒駕或醉駕，除非你真的在開車。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我上大學的時候，一個室友有一天晚上出去喝酒，在酒吧裏和別人發生了爭執。
在酒吧裏與人爭吵，然後決定離開。他意識到他已經
他意識到他喝得太多了，所以他叫了一輛車。當時是八月中旬，外面超級熱
所以當他在等待他的車時，他坐在他的卡車裏，並...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1c0n/cmv_a_person_should_not_be_able_to_be_charged/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oc1c0n/cmv_a_person_should_not_be_able_to_be_charged/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 05:32:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was in college a roommate went out drinking one night, got in an arguement with someone in the bar, and decided to leave.  He realized that he had had too much to drink, so he called a ride.  It was mid August and super hot outside, so while he was waiting on his ride he sat in in his truck and ran the A/C.  A police officer saw him and took him in for a DWI and he was convicted.  It effected his employment and schooling for the next couple of years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never liked the guy much, but I always thought he got a raw deal. He was doing the right thing and got the same penalty as if he decided to drive home.  You should be able to sleep it off in your car without fear of consequence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have heard the argument that if the officer saw a drunk sitting in their car and just walked away from it, the person could start driving at any moment.  I argue that it would be just as easy to take the person home as it would be to take them to jail, and it doesnt ruin their life. The police could even take them to the jail to dry out for the night just to be sure, but there is no reason to suspend their license, fine, and imprison a person for simply sitting in their car with the keys in their possession, or even sitting in a running vehicle. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To head off the first argument I see coming, this doesn&amp;#39;t apply to a vehicle in a lane of traffic, obviously if you are passed out at a stop sign or something you deserve a DWI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在《霹靂遊俠》中，沃爾特和傑西爲古斯工作的3個月有一些嚴重的甲基數學問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[1.) 他們在3個月內每週製作200磅的冰毒。(來源：The show)

2.) 冰毒的售價爲每盎司40美元。(來源：節目組)

傑西一直說："他以40美元一磅的價格出售"。我認爲有三種可能
這一點。

A.) 他的意思是40美元一磅。對於他們爲賺取Meth而承擔的所有風險，這
似乎是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obt46b/cmv_in_breaking_bad_there_are_some_serious_meth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obt46b/cmv_in_breaking_bad_there_are_some_serious_meth/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 01:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.) They are making 200 pounds of meth a week for 3 months.  (source: The show)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) The meth sells at $40 an ounce. (Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessie keeps saying, &amp;quot;He&amp;#39;s selling at 40 a pound&amp;quot;.  I see 3 possibilities for this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A.) He mean $40 a pound.  For all the risk they are taking to make Meth, that seems like too small of revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B.) Me meant $40,000 a pound.  This sounds like astronomically too high.  How could Meth junkies ever afford their meth if 1 pound sells for 1 years minimum wage salary?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;C.) He mis-poke, and meant $40 an ounce.  This sounds most plausible to me, as it means they are making some decent money from their risk and Meth junkies can still afford to buy their meth.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.) There are 16 ounces in a pound. (Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?client=firefox-b-1-d&amp;amp;q=ounces+in+a+pound&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.) They are working for 13 weeks.  (Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assuming ~31 days in a month, ~31 x 3 = ~93 days in 3 months.  ~93/7 = ~13 weeks in 3 months)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5.)  Conclusion: The meth they make for Gus during the 3 months can sell for ~1.5 million dollars.  (Source:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$40 (per ounce) x 16 (ounces per pound) x 200 (pounds per week) x 13 (weeks in the job) = $1,664,000, or ~1.5 million dollars)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now lets get down to the problems here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gus is losing money&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gus is paying 3 million dollars for these two guys to make product that he will sell for 1.5 million dollars.  That&amp;#39;s 1.5 million dollars down the drain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walter and Jessie are bad at Math&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessie and Walter both come to the conclusion that Gus is making 93 million off their 3 month job.  Given all the information we have, they should have come to 1.5 million.  Jessie I could understand making a mistake somewhere in this math.  But Walter is supposed to be the smart guy.  How could he also make this mistake?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would change my view&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.) Show me a way to interpret the information in the show in such a way that the job is profitable for Gus while still being based in reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) Explain why both Walter and Jessie made such bad math mistakes in their calculations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus points if you can do both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What wouldn&amp;#39;t change my view&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This was a mistake the show-writers made.&lt;/em&gt;  If this is the case I apologize since it means there isn&amp;#39;t really a view to be changed here.  However, I have hope that there is something I am missing that explains this mess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edits/deltas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gus is doing this venture as a long term plan.  Once he has Walt&amp;#39;s formula, he can start making money again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The math at $40k a pound checks out for Walter and Jessie&amp;#39;s calculation if you assume 12 weeks instead of 13 weeks.  12 instead of 13 weeks seems like a simple enough mistake if you assume the 4 weeks per month as many people do.  $40k a pound for meth seems unrealistic to me, but at least that is a flaw in the world building rather than Walter or Jessie&amp;#39;s character.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Junkies buy in teenths (1/16 of an ounce), which makes selling Meth at $40k a pound more reasonable.  Also, $40k a pound checks out with how much money Walter and Jessie were making when they cooked in their RV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Real Meth sells at about the $40k per pound value.  Looks like the show was actually being very realistic after all!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: 應該在他們/他們之間劃線。]]></title><description><![CDATA[有一天，我正在看Instagram，我關注的一個人在他們的故事上發佈了一個帖子，其中有多張幻燈片，其中有我從未聽說過的代詞。
他們的故事，其中有多張幻燈片上有我從未聽說過的代詞。
的，我發誓其中一個是viv/vov，一個是xe/xer。我認爲沒有理由
爲什麼我們需要在我們的社會中使用這些代詞，它們有什麼好處？]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwzwl/cmv_the_line_should_be_drawn_at_theythem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwzwl/cmv_the_line_should_be_drawn_at_theythem/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 01:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I Was looking at Instagram the other day and someone im following posted on their story a post containing multiple slides with pronouns I have never heard of before, I swear one of them was viv/vov and one was xe/xer. I see 0 reason why we need to have these in our society and what benefit they have: Maybe their is people who actually suffer from gender dysphoria and theirs people who don&amp;#39;t feel like they identify with the gender binary. But why would anyone need to use these pronouns for any reason other than to feel special? this seems to me like nothing more than progression for the sake of progression, call me homophobic all you want but I refuse to call anyone by any pronouns other than him, they or her. Its not like viv/vov people have been oppressed for hundreds of years like gay people. The sad thing is, is most people who share this an opinion with me get &amp;quot;canceled&amp;quot; because criticizing lgbt is some godforsaken sin now a days. I hope this subreddit will understand my POV and give me genuine reasons for why &amp;quot;neopronouns&amp;quot; need to exist and not accuse me of being homophobic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：成人節目和歌曲不應受到審查，因爲它們是爲成人準備的]]></title><description><![CDATA[公司不應該養育你的孩子。你是他們的父母，養育他們是
你有責任撫養他們。如果你不希望你的孩子看到或聽到一個
節目，那麼這應該是你的責任。當我在廣播中聽到一首歌有50個不同的小扭曲部分時
不同的小失真部分時，我就會笑。如果它是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwn05/cmv_adult_programs_and_songs_shouldnt_be_censored/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obwn05/cmv_adult_programs_and_songs_shouldnt_be_censored/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corporations shouldn&amp;#39;t have to parent your child. You are their parent and it is your responsibility to raise them. If you don&amp;#39;t want your kids to see or hear a programming then that should be on you. When I hear a song on the radio with 50 different little distorted parts it makes me laugh. If it&amp;#39;s so inappropriate why is it on a channel meant for all audiences? If it&amp;#39;s so inappropriate why let your child listen to begin with? Do you really think the swear words are the only controversial thing in these songs? Why not simply parent your child and make sure they aren&amp;#39;t consuming content you don&amp;#39;t see fit for your child?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also ruins songs and programs for us adults. There have been parts that are so heavily censored that the joke is basically how censored it is cause you&amp;#39;ll never hear the actual words. You just hear bleep bleep bleeeep bleep bleep bleep and some bleep bleep and then everyone around the character is just shocked and I&amp;#39;m just pissed. Why can I see a character get brutally killed in the most horrific way possible but not hear fuck? Why can I watch a character get sexually assaulted or even raped but as long as I don&amp;#39;t see a dick or a nipple then I&amp;#39;m good? I can watch mass genocide or listen to hate speech but can&amp;#39;t hear cunt?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dumbest part of all of this is 99% of us know exactly what is being censored. It doesn&amp;#39;t actually work as censoring if your mind fills in the blanks. Sure if the screen went completely black whenever nudity or sexual content came on or you censored the whole sentence instead of just the &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; word then yeah it&amp;#39;d work but we don&amp;#39;t do that. It feels like we simply do the level of censoring we do to make the 0.001% of the population who would be lose their shit happy but why the fuck do we care what they think? They aren&amp;#39;t watching the fucking shows! No way you are a stick up the butt prude and like watching South Park and rick and morty and you draw the line at nipples and fucks. Why do we pander to the extreme minority? We could uncensore every adult program and nothing would happen and everyone who watches these programs or listens to these songs would still listen and watch and the only mad ones would be people who don&amp;#39;t even consume that media&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: 既要求平等又要求騎士精神的女人是僞君子]]></title><description><![CDATA[現在對明星來說，我想澄清我所說的騎士精神是什麼意思。我並不是說要以尊重的態度對待
尊重別人或爲別人開門，這些只是一個體麪人的特徵。
人的特徵。我的意思是，男人約女人出來，必須計劃好約會。
支付費用和任何其他費用（因爲她會反對）。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obp7da/cmv_woman_who_demand_both_equality_and_chivalry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obp7da/cmv_woman_who_demand_both_equality_and_chivalry/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 20:43:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now to star I want to clarify what I mean by chivalry. I dont mean treating people with respect or holding the door open, those are just traits of a decent human. What I mean is the man asking the woman out , having to plan the date, pay for it and any further other(since she will hold it againts him if he dosnt) and generally having to ,, woo her,, while she stays passive. The main reason for this post is a coment I read on one of the dating subs(looking trought the controversial section on them is a guilty pleasure when I&amp;#39;m bored). It was a woman comenthing how when a guy dosnt pay for the date he shows that he is cheap and lazy and yet saying that she never pays for a date. This really annoyed me because it really reminds me of ,, modern day femenist,,. I belive that if a woman want equality ( which everyone should want) then she must accept both the benefits and the responsibility that come with it. You cant just say well I reject the gender norms in this and this area since they hinder me but I want to keep them in this and this are since I benefit from them. If you want to be intellectually honest you either chose equality,  both the good and the bad, or choose old school. Meaning that you demand that the guys is the archetype of the old school gentleman, but you also have to be the archetype of the old school woman(staying in the house, cooking, cleaning and taking care of his sexual needs whenever he wants). Now there isnt anything wrong with either of the options( different tastes for different people) but anything in between and your just a hypocrite who wants to have their cake and eat it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：拜登聲稱你需要F15戰鬥機和核彈來對抗政府是不正確的]]></title><description><![CDATA[查看與此有關的聲明。

https://youtu.be/SHLHkmWoYDU

理論依據。

美國在伊拉克戰爭中幾乎是輸了。當然，他們擺脫了薩達姆，但他們
但他們根本沒有制服伊斯蘭激進分子和前伊拉克軍隊的民兵。一旦他們
他們一離開，伊希斯就有了力量，不僅征服了大片的土地。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/objxpa/cmv_bidens_claim_that_you_would_need_f15s_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/objxpa/cmv_bidens_claim_that_you_would_need_f15s_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:48:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View is related to this statement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/SHLHkmWoYDU&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/SHLHkmWoYDU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rationale:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America pretty much lost the Iraq war. Sure they got rid of Saddam, but they didnt subdue the militant Islamists and ex-Iraqi army militias at all. Once they left Isis had the strength to not only conquer large swathes of Iraq, but the middle east proper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America has 7x the population of Iraq and something like 10x the guns, plus a populace with a ludicrously high rate of firearm profficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add to that the radically different levels of desertion, and more importantly sabotage. You think fragging was bad in Nam, see what happens when you invade Texas lmfao.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add to that the logistical nightmare that is protecting US infrastructure, literally 10s of millions of unguardable targets, and the whole thing starts looking unwinnable for the government very fucking fast.  US geography is also an extremely daunting challenge with regards to suppressing rebellion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there is the foreign actor concern. Allies would put pressure on to stop the killing of civilians (which would be a necessary collateral outcome of fighting your own people). Enemies would gleefully support the rebels in any way they could as hard as they could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government would never fucking glass its own territory and people with nukes, its fucking ridiculous to suggest such a thing. Even conventional bombing would be asking to feed into desertion and further rebellion. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not wanting to invade due to a rifle behind every blade of grass isnt just something for foreign armies to ponder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American citizens should be sickened by his words here, they are deeply unAmerican and downright terrifying to be coming from the top executive in the land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus CMV:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden is straight up lying about the &amp;#39;types of weapons&amp;#39; claim, you could absolutely own cannons as a private citizen. Privateers used them all the time and 2A allowed for their legal ownership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tl:dr&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2A practically ensures the US populace a reasonable if not favored chance against their own government. Not many countries can say that, and none of them have a military as daunting as the yanks. Biden&amp;#39;s cute little comment was pure unadulterated bluff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 1:&lt;/strong&gt; gee whiz its hard to run so many arguments at once. I should have done this with access to my pc instead of just my shitty phone with a cracked screen. I apologise to anybody left waiting, im trying to answer as quickly as possible, im literally sweating!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 2:&lt;/strong&gt; use of the Iraq war as example was just that. Whether that war counted as victory or defeat is not all that relevant to my opinion here, my point was just that the insurgent population was never subdued despite the overwhelming technological advantage wielded by the US military. The Taliban or viet kong might have been better to go with, but thats not exactly comparable because they are militaries themselves at the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 3:&lt;/strong&gt; I will add one argument. The top US military brass have said on many occassions that they are beholden to the constitution first and foremost. I tend to take them at their word, they generally seem like very principled and proud individuals willing to do anything necessary to uphold their oath. That means the President cant just decide to glass entire cities or States that contain innocent civilians in amongst an insurgency or guerilla network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit 4:&lt;/strong&gt; I think many here are failing to appreciate the ticking clock the government would be put under during a popular uprising, especially if many people stopped working and paying taxes. The US military is insanely expensive, an insurgency is very cheap. As the Taliban say: &amp;#39;you have the watches, we have the time&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：在門外漢的對話中，對措辭吹毛求疵的人很少在一個領域有真正深刻的知識或專業知識，而且沒有什麼有用的作用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[無論你的專長是什麼，我相信你都有過這樣的經歷。有人糾正
心理學家對 "戀物癖 "這種術語的不準確使用。糾正人們
糾正經濟學博士關於 "你不能說免費，因爲沒有什麼是免費的"。A
物理學家對 "重量 "的使用，等等。或者是一位個人...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obldx3/cmv_in_a_layman_conversation_nitpicking_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obldx3/cmv_in_a_layman_conversation_nitpicking_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:48:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your expertise, I&amp;#39;m sure you&amp;#39;ve had this experience. Someone correcting a psychologist on an inaccurate use of a term like &amp;quot;fetish&amp;quot;. Correcting people doing an economics PhD on &amp;quot;you can&amp;#39;t say free because nothing is free&amp;quot;. A physicist on the usage of &amp;quot;weight&amp;quot;, and so on. Or a personal favorite, focusing on a pronunciation mistake as a way to dismiss the knowledge (translated personal experience: &amp;quot;if you can&amp;#39;t say &lt;em&gt;gratuit&lt;/em&gt; correctly surely you can&amp;#39;t know that much about finance&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My view is that we should strive, in the context of a normal conversation or discussion, to be understandable by the lay public&lt;/strong&gt;, as experts in their fields should strive for us to understand. But to just &amp;quot;nitpick&amp;quot; on the fact that an expert or trained professional uses a more understandable, not perfectly accurate term, is pointless. The chances they know what they are saying are high, and that they know more than whoever is commenting even higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think there is a point in such a context to do this? As it&amp;#39;s something I hear almost daily about many fields and with many colleagues from various backgrounds complaining about this, I figured I should ask myself if maybe it actually could be useful. Am I wrong in preferring more approachable terms?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV: 你越是不關注你無法控制的事情，你就會越快樂。]]></title><description><![CDATA[對有些人來說，他們擔心的是體育或浪漫的關係。人們浪費
人們浪費了很多精力，希望他們喜歡的運動隊贏得大冠軍，或希望可愛的人喜歡他們。
可愛的人喜歡他們，而這幾乎總是在他們的控制之外。
會發生什麼。

對我來說，是股票市場、政治、...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obe27y/cmv_the_less_you_focus_on_things_out_of_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obe27y/cmv_the_less_you_focus_on_things_out_of_your/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some people they worry about sports or romantic relationships. People waste a lot of energy hoping their favorite sports teams win the big title or that cute someone likes them back when it is almost always outside of their control of what happens there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, it&amp;#39;s the stock market, politics, religion and cars. Thankfully, I&amp;#39;ve learned to accept the ebbs and flows of the bear and bull days. At this rate I&amp;#39;m going probably going to be in a middle class job where it would be a pipe dream for me to own a Ferrari or Lamborghini so I&amp;#39;ve stopped caring about what the newest hypercar will be like because I might only drive it in a Las Vegas supercar experience once every few years when I can afford it. With politics, I as a single person have little influence on who becomes president or who controls congress yet I still find myself reading political news everyday as if I am addicted to political news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cmv: 盜版行爲可以是合理的]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，是的，我認爲盜版可以因爲各種原因而變得合理。

首先，如果一個人有錢，可以合法地支付一項服務（電影、動漫、遊戲等），但他們不這樣做，因爲他們認爲娛樂活動應該是合法的。
而他們不這樣做是因爲他們認爲娛樂應該是免費的。
是的，那麼盜版就沒有正當理由。

此外，我認爲盜版服務...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obh4kl/cmv_piracy_can_be_justified/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obh4kl/cmv_piracy_can_be_justified/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, yes i think piracy can be justified for various reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, if a person has the money to legally pay for a service (movies, animes, games etc) and they don&amp;#39;t do it because they think entertainment should be free, yes, then piracy can&amp;#39;t be justified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also i think pirating services such as games that are made by indie companies and are available to buy for a cheap price, also can&amp;#39;t be justified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that out of the way, let me tell you my reasons :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reston number one: some people are poor. I have heard people say &amp;quot; WeLl iF yOu ArE pOor ThAT doEsNt jUStify sTeAling&amp;quot;, and i consider that bullshit cause, being really poor can also justify stealing in some conditions, if a homeless child steals one apple to steal alive, that isn&amp;#39;t wrong, human life values a lot more than an apple, if a person steals a loaf of bread to feed his family, it&amp;#39;s not something wrong, because again, human life values a lot more than a loaf of bread. So yes, i think stealing can be justified if the person they&amp;#39;re stealing from isn&amp;#39;t poor himself, also don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, i don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s a good thing to steal but if someone&amp;#39;s life depends on it, it can be justified. And for piracy, of course someone&amp;#39;s life doesn&amp;#39;t depend on watching movies, but i think if a poor person pirates some movie, it can lead to that person support the industry when he&amp;#39;s able to, that can also lead to free marketing some people are not able to pay for entertainment and i think it&amp;#39;s OK to pirate as long as it&amp;#39;s not possible to pay, of course as long as they choose to pay when they have the ability to. And also I&amp;#39;ve heard people say &amp;quot; eNtertAinMEnt iS a LuXurY&amp;quot;, and my answer to that is, what does a rich kid do to deserve to have that luxury that a poor broke kid doesn&amp;#39;t? The answer is, nothing, it just depended on their luck. So yes i think pirating can be justified as long as the person pays for it when they can&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2- legally paying for entertainment doesn&amp;#39;t always support the creators. Half the time that you buy something, the money doesn&amp;#39;t actually really go to the actual creators, usually the big company receives the money and not the actual creators. And that happens a lot especially in the Anime/manga industry. The industry has been growing, and that growth leads to more money for the creators, so why are animators still underpaid af? I think when a big company doesn&amp;#39;t pay their employees enough, they deserve their products pirated, at least until they decide to change&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3- it may be impossible to pay for entertainment. You might be confused, this is more of a personal reason but it&amp;#39;s literally impossible for people such as me to pay for entertainment legally. So let me explain, i live in Iran, and in Iran, international banking doesn&amp;#39;t exist, it&amp;#39;s not possible for an iranian person to pay for any service that&amp;#39;s outside of iran, and there&amp;#39;s no service that legally sells entertainment products like movies and animes, even the big streaming services pirate their stuff, so yeah it&amp;#39;s impossible for me to pay for something like Netflix. Also most of the entertainment services have banned iran, so doesn&amp;#39;t that mean they don&amp;#39;t want our money? And also it is possible to buy games, but they are so expensive that it&amp;#39;s possible to pay the rent with the money &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s all I&amp;#39;m going to say, i might be a bit biased, keep in mind that these are my opinions and i don&amp;#39;t count them as objective facts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：社交媒體對社會是有毒的]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在一個社交媒體網站上譴責社交媒體，這可能看起來很諷刺，但我認爲這是很恰當的。
但我認爲這是很恰當的 --

在我看來，社交媒體已經成爲人類最糟糕的傾向的可怕加速器，並且正在毒害我們的社會。
在我看來，社交媒體已經成爲人類最壞傾向的可怕加速器，並且正在毒害我們的社會。

慢性判斷、膚淺的謊言和錯誤信息的迴音室......]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obfpgz/cmv_social_media_is_toxic_to_society/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obfpgz/cmv_social_media_is_toxic_to_society/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may seem ironic for me to decry social media on a social media site, but I think it&amp;#39;s appropriate --&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, social media has been a horrific accelerator of humankind&amp;#39;s worst tendecies, and is toxifying our society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chronic judgments, superficial lies, and echo chambers of misinformation have amplified our negativity, as well as distracted many Americans and other members of industrial societies from real crises like Climate Change, World Hunger, Global Peace, or Social Justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean is, people online are nasty &amp;amp; carry that nastiness into real life. If you aren&amp;#39;t pretty, funny, or witty, no one values you in the digital world &amp;amp; the culture of people who learn this way likewise treat you cruelly in real life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even more scary, actual life-or-death needs are tragically ignored by bad info on FaceBook, InstaGram, Twitter, or even Reddit etc. We see vaccine lies lead to people dying ; we also see violent white supremacists organize domestic terror ; and we see junk science like alternate &amp;quot;climate&amp;quot; hypotheses spread as though they&amp;#39;re scientific theories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So with so much global ugliness emanating from online, what good is there to the tech of social media?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv：取笑白人以及美國人是社會可以接受的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[標題可以用更好的措辭。我不是說它 "應該 "被社會接受，我是說我認爲它目前（潛意識）是被接受的。
接受，我是說我相信它目前（在潛意識中）被接受。
而它不應該是。我要求你說服我，它不是社會上的
接受的。

在任何人誤解之前，這並不意味着...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obbfc0/cmv_it_is_socially_acceptable_to_make_fun_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obbfc0/cmv_it_is_socially_acceptable_to_make_fun_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 09:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title could have been worded better. I’m not saying it ‘should’ be socially acceptable, I’m saying that I believe it is currently (subconsciously) accepted, and it shouldn’t be. I’m asking you to convince me that it is not socially accepted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before anyone misinterprets this, this does not mean that other races and nationalities do not face racism and discrimination. I know that they face it much worse than whites and Americans, and I understand systematic racism and white privilege.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My point is that if you were to make a negative remark about a white person, it is not socially frowned upon. And that same remark made by a white person towards any person who isn’t white would have you labeled a racist. I’ll give an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;White person recommends going to a bar that is predominantly white. Response is “I don’t really want to be around that many white people haha”. Socially acceptable, even possibly a joke. No outrage. If it’s reversed and the comment is “I don’t really want to be around that many black people haha”. You are a racist, and a comment like that would destroy relationships. Replace black with literally any other race, and the comment is equally as racist, but made towards a white it’s like whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen the term “wypipo” for white people. No one says it’s racist, it just is what it is. If white people had a nickname for black people that black people did not like, you would be shunned for using it. Something like “they don’t like being called that, so stop”. But if white people don’t like being called wypipo? Doesn’t seem like it matters…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example about Americans. (Living as an American in another country has made me realise this over and over again, it never ends). A comment overheard in public “Americans are so annoying”. Everyone supports it (except for Americans of course), but the response is not “Wow that was actually racist”. Everyone openly agrees, it’s socially acceptable. Even if they don’t agree, you aren’t shunned for it. Same comment but replace Americans with literally any other nationality. “Japanese people are so annoying”, heads would turn and you’d be labeled a racist instantly, and rightfully so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: previous examples are xenophobic , not racist, but same idea of the discrimination. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been afraid to discuss this sentiment among peers, so before you change my view, can you please also let me know if I’m way out of line, or if it has some merit of truth, but the discussion itself may not even be socially acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: also to be clear, I don’t think that people are ‘intentionally’ accepting of this, it seems like more of a subconscious thing, not realising that there is anything wrong with being said&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: 在基於歐洲古老文化或神話的故事中插入非白人角色，無助於促進多樣性，不應鼓勵。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近看了《冰封2》的一個片段，注意到有相當數量的非白人角色。
非白人角色，令我感到驚訝。我不明白這些邏輯
補充。冰雪奇緣》的背景是幾百年前的斯堪的納維亞半島。難道這只是
膚淺的多樣性嘗試？

我最喜歡的節目是《阿凡達》：...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obdava/cmv_inserting_nonwhite_characters_into_stories/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/obdava/cmv_inserting_nonwhite_characters_into_stories/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 07:33:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw a clip from frozen 2 recently and noticed a pretty significant number of non white characters, to my surprise. I don’t understand the logic these additions. Frozen is set hundreds of years ago In Scandinavia. Is it just shallow attempts at diversity?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite show of all time is Avatar: the Last Airbender. It’s world is based on old Asian and Inuit culture and mythology. There are no white people in it and there shouldn’t be. I don’t see why the same logic shouldn’t apply to other stories like Frozen, Lord of the Rings, the Witcher, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only do these insertions seem forced and awkward, they take away from what could be. How many great mainstream fantasy stories are there based on old African mythology and culture? I can’t really think of any.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：聖何塞的新 "槍支所有者爲槍支暴力買單 "政策是錯誤的]]></title><description><![CDATA[聖何塞頒佈了一項新政策，將迫使所有希望行使第二修正案權利的人
迫使每個希望行使第二修正案權利的人購買保險，以用於
用於支付槍支暴力的受害者。

我認爲這是不對的。想象一下這個類似的場景，就能理解爲什麼我有這種感覺
這種方式。

"每一個行使其...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob61pw/cmv_san_joses_new_gunowners_pay_for_gun_violence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob61pw/cmv_san_joses_new_gunowners_pay_for_gun_violence/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 02:39:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Jose has enacted a new policy that will force everybody who wishes to exercise their 2nd amendment right to purchase insurance that will be used to pay victims of gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;#39;s wrong. Imagine this equivalent scenario to understand why I feel this way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Everyone who exercises their first amendment rights by speaking or writing should be required to pay libel/slander insurance to the government to pay damages for all the victims of illegal speech.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should rub you the wrong way... Or at least it does me. But I would like to hear from people who support this policy, since it is popular in many online circles, to see what I&amp;#39;m missing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：像英國這樣擁有埃及文物的國家沒有義務歸還這些文物，埃及政府對這些文物的所有權沒有比地球上任何其他政府更多的要求。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我經常聽到有人說，各國如何從埃及 "掠奪 "這些文物，而他們無權擁有這些文物。
他們無權擁有，這是不對的，他們應該歸還這些文物。
但我不同意這種說法，原因有幾個。雖然我可以理解
對於許多現有的文化，我可以理解這種推理。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaybaw/cmv_countries_such_as_the_uk_that_have_egyptian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaybaw/cmv_countries_such_as_the_uk_that_have_egyptian/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:38:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often hear about how countries &amp;quot;plundered&amp;quot; these artifacts from Egypt that they have no right to have, and that this is wrong and they should return these artifacts, but I disagree with this for several reasons. While I can understand this reasoning for many of the existing cultures that had their artifacts taken in recent memory, my primary contention with this for Egypt specifically is that they&amp;#39;re incredibly old. The Egyptians that created these artifacts and all their ancestors are long dead, and the people and government that currently live in Egypt are just the conquerors of the conquerors of the conquerors of the people who did create this artifacts. The British and others took these artifacts from the people who took them from the people who took them from the people who lived there thousands of years ago, their claim doesn&amp;#39;t really seem any less reasonable than those of the current Egyptian people or government. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I don&amp;#39;t really believe these artifacts should sit concentrated at a few European museums either, I believe when it comes to things this old they should be considered to be part of our shared heritage as a species and should be equally distributed around the world to all stable countries that could reasonable house them (I could make another argument about how Egypt is not the best place for these artifacts on the basis of the instability of the government alone), so that as many people as possible could see them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So CMV, why should these artifacts return to Egypt?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：我不認爲自由主義是那麼瘋狂或不合理的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[自然，個體自由主義者也可能是不合理的。而任何政治
任何政治觀點如果走到邏輯上的極端，都會顯得很瘋狂。

就其最基本的形式而言，自由主義者認爲，一個人或一羣人
在政府中沒有能力知道什麼是對我這個人最好的，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob1x57/cmv_i_dont_find_libertarianism_to_be_all_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/ob1x57/cmv_i_dont_find_libertarianism_to_be_all_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:38:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, an individual libertarian can be unreasonable. And any political viewpoint will look insane when taken to its logical extremes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At it&amp;#39;s most basic form, a libertarian believes that a person or group of people in government are not capable of knowing what&amp;#39;s best for me as an individual, or you as an individual. This is at it&amp;#39;s worse at the federal level, and gets slightly better as government gets more local.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, a libertarian wants to reduce the power of government to &lt;strong&gt;only what&amp;#39;s necessary.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is where individual libertarians would have discussions and debate, around what is necessary and what is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, a libertarian could absolutely be for universal healthcare. They might compare what we pay right now on average to the NHS, and see that we actually pay more than they do. Then there could be a discussion that the free market isn&amp;#39;t working right with healthcare because people don&amp;#39;t know what they will pay for the service, and the service is often times non-optional. Thus, it is necessary for the government to fund healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think where leftists and libertarians most often disagree is actually around the framing of the discussion. If the subject is social safety nets for example, the leftist will enter the conversation on the assumption that government is the one and only option for providing help to those that need it. The libertarian does not enter the conversation with this assumption. So the conversation is doomed from the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They aren&amp;#39;t disagreeing about helping people, they are disagreeing about the method of doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my view is that libertarianism isn&amp;#39;t any more or less crazy than conservatism or liberalism. Both of the latter philosophies wish to use the government to enforce their views, while libertarianism does not. I don&amp;#39;t find that to be an unreasonable political philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：作爲一個通常被認定爲相當左的人，我實際上很難看到跨種族和跨性別有什麼根本的不同。]]></title><description><![CDATA[拋磚引玉，因爲我注意到這可能是一個相當具有煽動性的話題，但
我正在努力保持好奇、誠實、開放和認真的態度。這就是說，我有一個相當
我的背景非常優越，這些問題都沒有直接影響到我的生活。
因此，我肯定會有相當大的差距在我的...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay9ks/cmv_as_someone_who_generally_identifies_as_pretty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay9ks/cmv_as_someone_who_generally_identifies_as_pretty/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:32:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throwaway because I&amp;#39;ve noticed that this can be a pretty inflammatory topic, but I am trying to be curious, honest, open, and earnest. That said, I have a pretty privileged background and none of these issues have impacted my life directly, so I will definitely have pretty big gaps in my understanding. I have made what I think is an honest effort to understand both sides of this debate (which seems to have been set off by a couple recent reddit/twitter posts and the Oli London video), and I feel like I&amp;#39;m reaching a completely different conclusion to the people close to me (and online) that I tend to agree with, so I want to challenge my thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general I am 100% fine with people being cisgender, transgender, non-binary, gender-fluid, transsexual, or whatever else as long as they are doing it in good faith.* Not everybody thinks this way, obviously, so we have this big cultural change underway as people come to grips with gender identity.  Big cultural shifts tend to create really challenging social/cultural knock-on effects. In my mind, this question about racial identity and being transracial is one of them. I don&amp;#39;t think there are easy answers for a lot of these questions, but I think we owe it to eachother to listen, explore, communicate, and compromise. The conversations that I&amp;#39;ve seen so far on the topic of racial identity are far from honest, with arguments like: &amp;quot;Gender dysphoria is a part of psychology [and racial dysphoria isn&amp;#39;t]&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ToiletPaperUSA/comments/o9svvj/called_it/h3daui1?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;0&lt;/a&gt; (Gender dysphoria wasn&amp;#39;t either, 50 years ago); &amp;quot;Culture and heritage however is lived through communities. It can be  appropriated and abused. A white British person claiming to be  trans-Korean diminishes the experiences and burdens of actual Korean people and communities.&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ToiletPaperUSA/comments/o9svvj/called_it/h3dc4wt?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt; (Gender has a massive cultural component), &amp;quot;Race and Ethnicity is Rooted in Ancestry… You Can’t Just Pick and Choose&amp;quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/verve-up/transracial-is-not-the-new-transgender-why-race-and-gender-are-not-synonymous-b2c688ef0fae&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt; (sounds a lot like the &amp;#39;gender is rooted in biology&amp;#39; argument to me) and &amp;quot;We also think that, as a result of this asymmetry, transgender identities deserve social uptake and so-called “transracial”  identifications as Black almost always do not. (We leave space for  unique circumstances in which someone who has deeply invested in a Black community and been forthcoming about their racial history is nevertheless accepted within that community as Black.)&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bostonreview.net/race-philosophy-religion-gender-sexuality/robin-dembroff-dee-payton-why-we-shouldnt-compare&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2015/jun/16/transracial-definition-destructive-rachel-dolezal-spokane-naacp&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt; (there&amp;#39;s obviously massive differences, but this argument isn&amp;#39;t fundamentally different to arguing that trans women aren&amp;#39;t women because they haven&amp;#39;t grown up having periods, experiencing sexism, etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting aside (for now) the existing use of &amp;#39;transracial&amp;#39; used in the context of adopted children raised outside of their biological parents&amp;#39; ethnic/racial cultures, I think that being transracial is similar in a lot of ways to being transgender or transexual, and I don&amp;#39;t see how that de-legitimizes either of those things. I think there&amp;#39;s a lot of fear on the left that this comparison makes the transgender/transsexual struggle look somehow ridiculous or absurd by association &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ToiletPaperUSA/comments/o9svvj/called_it/&quot;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt; and I guess I can see why people might think that, but it feels like either an unhelpful gut reaction, or (being a bit pessimistic) an overly political/strategic reaction which looks a lot like &lt;a href=&quot;https://thomasnastcartoons.com/2015/01/06/throwing-down-the-ladder-by-which-they-rose-23-july-1870/&quot;&gt;throwing the ladder down&lt;/a&gt;. Every new cultural idea is uncomfortable at first, but we don&amp;#39;t know if it has any merit if we don&amp;#39;t explore it in good faith. I think it&amp;#39;s also a missed opportunity to better understand trans/identity in general&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the other (original) definition of transracial -- adopted children raised outside their biological parents&amp;#39; culture/race -- I think it&amp;#39;s a really interesting bridge between transsexual identity politics and transracial (the other/new definition) identity politics, because there are hundreds of thousands of cases of transracial adoption, and I&amp;#39;m sure we could learn a lot about culture and identity if we asked them about it.  I expect some of these children experience very real, very complicated dysphoria [citation needed, obviously].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know if the likes of Rachel Dolezal, Oli London, Ja Du, Ekundayo, etc are charlatans or people in genuine turmoil deserving of, if not our sympathy, at least our patience. What I do know is that this kind of tectonic cultural shift has happened enough times throughout history that I think I want to hedge my bets and at least be kind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Quick aside:  I don&amp;#39;t say &amp;quot;as long as it isn&amp;#39;t hurting anyone&amp;quot; because I&amp;#39;ve observed that change hurts, and a lot of people are experiencing real pain caused by this big cultural shift in favor of trans rights and that&amp;#39;s unavoidable. However, I think there will always be charlatans out there who take advantage of the opportunity that any big disruption creates, so that&amp;#39;s why I say &amp;#39;in good faith&amp;#39;. You can pick your example of this, from people &amp;#39;playing the race card&amp;#39; to children setting their screen names to &amp;#39;Connecting...&amp;#39; to get out of zoom/skype classes during a pandemic. Big changes create opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：存在一個封鎖期（也許是2年，也許是5年，也許是75年，但有一定的期限），超過這個期限，即使是爲了拯救生命也沒有理由。]]></title><description><![CDATA[三角形變體的崛起讓我思考。

讓我們從一個極端的案例開始：封鎖今天出生的人的整個自然生命。
今天出生的人。

有誰會不同意這段時間的禁閉是不合理的，即使在科學上是爲了拯救生命？
即使在科學上是爲了拯救生命？

我想不會。

那麼，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oag13m/cmv_there_exists_a_period_of_lockdown_perhaps_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oag13m/cmv_there_exists_a_period_of_lockdown_perhaps_2/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:32:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of the delta variant has got me thinking:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s start with an extreme case: lockdown for the entire natural lives of people born today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would anyone disagree that this period of lockdown would not be justified even if scientifically established to save lives? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think not. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So then the question becomes what IS the maximum duration of lockdown that is justified even if scientifically established to save lives?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there a meaningful difference between &amp;quot;permanent&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;indefinite&amp;quot;? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that some maximal threshold should be debated and agreed upon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: 政治辯論應該現代化，要求提供來源和數字，以迫使對主張負責。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美國目前進行政治辯論的方式有點像一團亂麻。
政客們左右逢源，把數字拋來拋去。辯論結束後
你還有30-45分鐘的節目專門用來檢查他們所說的事實。
他們說的話，同樣沒有任何來源。

作爲政治辯論的一部分，...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay3cb/cmv_political_debates_should_modernize_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oay3cb/cmv_political_debates_should_modernize_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The way the US currently runs political debates is kinda a clusterfuck. Politicians are throwing numbers around left and right. After the debate is over you have another 30-45 minutes of programming dedicated to fact-checking what they said, again without any sources. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of a political debate, politicians should be allowed to prepare a presentation for each of the big questions that are released beforehand. These should be backed up by easily accessible sources, so that the viewers can verify the claims if they want to, while they are watching the debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it goes into the shorter rapid-fire debates between two candidates this obviously isn&amp;#39;t feasible. Instead, I feel like the respective campaigns should be forced to put out a statement afterward citing sources for as many of the points their candidate made as is possible. If they said something that can&amp;#39;t be backed up, then they issue an apology and a clarification. This would preferably be done at the next debate or some other televised event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that this is far from perfect and that it&amp;#39;s possible to find sources supporting most opinions. However, politicians have been known to just spout random &amp;quot;facts&amp;quot; that are later proven false. I think this would go a small way to deter this type of behavior, without decreasing the viewability or essence of a political debate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[cmv: 營養、睡眠和其他 "身體 "方面的自我護理在改善心理健康方面被極度低估。]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我要說的是，我對營養和睡眠的興趣已經超出了我認爲它們是決定健康的所有因素的程度。
我認爲營養和睡眠是決定健康的所有因素。

但是......我確實堅信，你的感覺（你的能量、前景、情緒、認知、決策能力）與你的身體狀況之間存在着聯繫。
能量、前景、情緒、認知、決策能力）之間的聯繫。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaw37t/cmv_nutrition_sleep_and_other_physical_aspects_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oaw37t/cmv_nutrition_sleep_and_other_physical_aspects_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 14:33:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by saying that I am beyond the point in my interests of nutrition and sleep where I think they are end all be all determiners of health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BUT… I do strongly believe that the connection between how you feel (your energy, outlook, emotions, cognition, decision making abilities) is not brought to the forefront of solving issues like depression, unproductiveness, and aggression like it should. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everybody is willing to acknowledge that diet and sleep have profound effects on health but very few seem to actually realise it and apply it to themselves. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More often than not I feel as though that ‘tiring job’ or ‘draining relationship’ is more a result of a poor diet and sleep regime than it is actual social interactions having an effect. No, you are not tired on Saturday because you ‘just finished an exhausting work week’, you are tired because you eat and sleep like shit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong, hormones can be influenced by social interactions, but over a long period of time I see their effects as minimal in comparison to a good regime. (I’m saying this to attribute more of the effect to diet and sleep, I’m not saying that severe events like a loved one’s passing can’t sometimes overpower the effects of diet and sleep). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mind you, I’m in the prime of my life physically and I don’t expect the entire population to have my level of energy or sharpness so I realise my bias, but I don’t think people without prexisting conditions are doomed to things like midday lethargy and morning grogginess. On a good day of eating and sleeping I have energy throughout and feel cognitively present at all times, regardless of my social context. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah, also, what is with normalising things like lethargy, headaches, and brain fog?? I constantly see people accept things like post-meal lethargy as concrete and unchangeable. People literally plan their days around when they’ll be lethargic instead of actually trying to fix the problem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me started on the neurodepressive effects of eating and sleeping like garbage. Not saying all cases of depression can be solved with those two things alone, but they can certainly be greatly ameliorated by them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realisation translates into action. 2/3rds of the American popular is overweight, if that doesn’t show that this isn’t an unpopular sentiment I don’t know what does. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Kick me down a peg I’ve been lurking pubmed and NCBI for too long. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Also this isn’t intended to invalidate other aspects of self care)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：作爲一個墨西哥人。生活在美國的 "我的文化 "的人對那些並不影響我們的事情太生氣了，甚至到了令人反感的程度。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看到 "拉美文化 "被周圍遠離它的人捍衛，因爲它 "屬於他們"，只是因爲他們的祖先。
因爲他們的祖先就 "屬於他們"，這讓我覺得
我認爲，人們比其他人更努力地推動陳規定型觀念的發展。
來自另一種文化的人希望他們的玉米餅以這樣的方式製作。]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oapwcp/cmv_as_a_mexican_people_from_my_culture_living_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oapwcp/cmv_as_a_mexican_people_from_my_culture_living_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 09:46:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing &amp;quot;latino culture&amp;quot; defended by people as far from it as any other around them because it &amp;quot;belongs to them&amp;quot; just because of their ancestry has made me look into it as people pushing towards stereotypes harder than everyone else. Someone from another culture wants their tacos made in a way that they like? We get to see a buzzfeed article or video from a &amp;quot;Mexican&amp;quot; (who has clearly never been in Mexico) get mad about it while we eat carne asada sushi. As most of the countries in the continent, we have a wide mix of ancestors and races and some people just ignore that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CMV：文化挪用不是一個真正的問題]]></title><description><![CDATA[它可能是老套的，或者傷害了某人的感情，但這就是它的範圍。我能想到的唯一負面後果是
我能想到的唯一負面後果是它會讓人不高興。
但是，我認爲他們不高興的理由並不合法。

如果一個白人開了一家牙買加餐館，這將被認爲是...]]></description><link>https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oamfqf/cmv_cultural_appropriation_is_not_a_real_issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://changemyview.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/changemyview/comments/oamfqf/cmv_cultural_appropriation_is_not_a_real_issue/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 06:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be corny or hurt someone’s feelings,  but that is the extent of it. The only negative consequence i can think of is that it would make someone upset. But, i think their reason for being upset is not legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a white person opens a Jamaican restaurant, that would be considered cultural appropriation. If they have no clue what they’re doing, the business will fail. If they are excellent Jamaican cooks, the business will do well. Both situations seem just to me. So there is no issue with them appropriating Jamaican culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that’s all i have to say about that. Just meeting the character count&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>